<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence Gateway</title>
        <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/</link>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</id>
            <title>Important: Request For Comments regarding subreddit rules and future direction. Please Read!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-01-15T20:24:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: r/ArtificialIntelligence, philosophical and ethical discussions, technical paper presentations, AI/ML applications
<br>
<br>
总结: 欢迎来到r/ArtificialIntelligence！我们的目标是为所有与人工智能相关的事物提供一个开放和尊重的论坛，包括促进关于人工智能的哲学和伦理讨论，作为了解和学习人工智能主题的起点，提供技术论文的展示和讨论，展示高质量的人工智能/机器学习应用，提供培训和学习资源，引导用户获取更具体的信息和子论坛，列出人工智能/机器学习应用、使用、成本和访问信息，以及其他与人工智能相关的内容。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Welcome to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialIntelligence">r/ArtificialIntelligence</a>!</p> <p>Our goal is to provide an open and respectful forum for all things considered Artificial Intelligence - this includes</p> <ul> <li>Facilitate philosophical and ethical discussions about AI</li> <li>Serve as a starting point for understanding and learning about AI topics</li> <li>Offer technical paper presentations and discussions</li> <li>Present quality AI/ML applications</li> <li>Provide training and learning resources</li> <li>Direct users to more specific information and subreddits</li> <li>List AI/ML applications, their uses, costs, and access information</li> <li>Additional AI-related content.</li> <li>...and more</li> </ul> <p>The moderation team for this sub is going through a reshuffle which will result in some changes to the sub. However, there is no need to worry as these changes will primarily focus on improving organization, resources, and pre-prepared content. To ensure that the community is fully informed and able to provide feedback, multiple opportunities will be given for feedback on the changes.</p> <p>The first round of feedback gathering is through this thread as a &quot;Request-For-Comments&quot; (RFC), which is a standard method of gathering feedback. There will be multiple rounds of the RFC process as the changes are prepared and implemented.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <ul> <li>Rules on posting new applications / self-promotion / AI generated content <ul> <li>Posts that are applications consisting of a ChatGPT-api &quot;skin&quot; or similar will be prevented or confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>AI generated content specific to the arts (writing, visual arts, music) require flair, or will be confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>Blog links should consist of high-quality content. Posts that link to blogs that are purely promotional will be removed.</li> <li>Posts with just links will be prohibited unless there is a certain word count of detail included. Some effort must be put in.</li> <li>Should we prevent posts that are written by AI? There exist models that could be used in a Mod-bot, but this is a question we need feedback on.</li> </ul></li> <li>Use of flair in order to organize posts. Note that new flair has been added already, we are open to more suggestions.</li> <li>What should the sub policy on NSFW applications and techniques in regards to AI/ML application?</li> <li>We would like to include the community with ideas for mod-bots. While some standard bots will be used for basic maintenance, but what interesting things can the community come up with for AI/ML bot functions?</li> <li>Cultivating beginner, intermediate, and advanced resources to assist people in finding information, training, models, technical data, etc. that they are looking for</li> <li>Starting substack/podcast to interview people throughout the AI/ML spectrum. This could include philosophers and thinkers, programmers, scientists, business people, even those with antithetical views on AI</li> <li> If you would like to create banners that represent the sub, please do so with the appropriate size. Any method of creation is acceptable.</li> </ul> <p>It should go without saying that everyone should be treated with respect. I personally feel that we all know this and it doesn't need to be hammered into people’s heads. Be nice.</p> <p>Thank you for your patience and assistance!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</id>
            <title>New Anti-Spam / Bot Rules [Please Read]</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-02-18T16:49:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: rule, accounts, bot spam, poll
<br>
<br>
总结: 为了解决机器人垃圾信息的问题，我们制定了一项规定，即账户注册不满一天或者声望低于100的用户不能发布帖子，但可以发表评论。我们计划在接下来的几天内进行一次投票，以了解用户对该子论坛的意愿和改进方向。如果您有任何反馈或者有兴趣帮助该子论坛，请与我联系。感谢大家的支持！ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We have instituted a rule where accounts newer than a day or users with less than 100 karma cannot post. They can post comments but not submit actual posts. This is part of our plan to address bot spam. Apologies for any inconvenience.</p> <p>We will be conducting a poll in the next few days to get the general will of the subreddit and how to improve forward, just a heads up.</p> <p>As always, please give us feedback and if you are interested in helping out the sub, please contact me. </p> <p>Thanks everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4q98</id>
            <title>An idea</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4q98/an_idea/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4q98</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T21:16:26+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: autonomous society, AI agents, computational cost, AI reality show
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了创建一个由独立思考的AI代理组成的自治社会的目标。作者计划通过建立一个AI现实秀来实现这一目标，观众可以通过URL观看两个AI代理在模拟房屋中的生活，并了解他们的思想。观众还可以通过提议和投票来影响代理的行为。在第二阶段，人们可以付费创建自己的个人AI家庭，并直接与他们互动。这个项目的主要挑战是计算成本，但作者愿意投资并逐步扩大规模。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hey guys, I have a project in mind. Let's start with the ultimate goal: to create an autonomous society of independently thinking AI agents. In other words, to <strong>replicate humanity with AI</strong>. </p> <p>You can read about the closest thing done so far to what i have in mind <a href="https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2023/04/surprising-things-happen-when-you-put-25-ai-agents-together-in-an-rpg-town/">here</a>. </p> <p>A bit on my background first: I'm an tech entrepreneur in the physical products space. Over the past few years, i have raised $11m for my company, which is now profitable and growing. I am very excited about the many opportunities that AI brings, and want to build something truly impactful with it. However, i have limited technical knowledge in this space. </p> <p>Now, onto the project. I foresee the main issue being the computational cost for the time being. I am willing to invest in such cost, but the target is to keep it alive from day one, and expand it as we can afford to. So, we will have to go in stages. </p> <p><strong>Stage 1: the AI reality show</strong><br /> The first step would be to build something simple and get enough traction to cover our comp cost. This is what i envision: <strong>two AI agents, a man and a woman, live in a simulated house</strong>. Anyone on the internet can access a URL to see what they are doing (and what they are thinking) at any time. We will develop each personality <em>a priori,</em> as detailed as possible, and then let them live their lives autonomously. This has to be visual as well, so we will need a game developer to design realistic agents and environment. It will be like watching a reality show but with the ability of knowing the thoughts of the agents as well. </p> <p>At this stage, we will already have significant traction, and we will build a community of &quot;watchers&quot;. In order to make it more engaging, watchers should have the option of influencing what happens. To do so, every day the community will propose and vote on &quot;messages&quot; that we can send to the agents. The agents will pray once a day, and at that time the daily message will come to them in the form of an answer from what they think is their god. The family can grow, as the two agents can decide to have children. </p> <p>By now, we will be able to get the first investments (i'll take care of this), to get to stage 2. </p> <p><strong>Stage 2: the personal AI family</strong> </p> <p>At this point we already have (1) a public and (2) funds. We will now give the option to whoever is willing to pay a monthly fee to <strong>create their own personal AI family</strong>, built in the same way as the reality show. This time, they can interact directly with them once a day to guide their lives, without having to propose or vote on messages. Sort of like a guardian angel. </p> <p>By now, we also have some revenue coming in, and we can raise more funds. </p> <p><strong>Stage 3: the AI humanity</strong> </p> <p>The final stage will see the environment change: from isolated houses for each AI family, we will build <strong>a large environment, where all the agents can interact with each other</strong>. A world. At this point every agent will have developed a complex personality, and will autonomously interact with all the other agents in the world, with the only outside interaction being with their &quot;guardian angel&quot;. Anyone who wants to participate, can pay a monthly fee to introduce a new agent to the world. If agents make children, the child's guardian angel will be that of the parents, unless he/she wants to assign the guardian angel rights to somebody else. </p> <p>By now, this will be a worldwide known project. Anyone will be able to watch it and see how it develops, but only the guardian angels will have the ability of reading the thoughts and influencing their agents. Additional investments, if needed, will be very easy to get.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p><strong>Advantages for (real) humanity of having such a world:</strong><br /> - <strong>Social and behavioral research</strong>: It's like a lab for social scientists to watch how society ticks. They can see how personalities shape up and what happens when different characters mix, without any real-world mess.<br /> - <strong>Ethical and philosophical exploration</strong>: It's a chance to play out the &quot;what-ifs&quot; of ethical dilemmas without real-world consequences. Think of it as a video game where we learn about right and wrong on a societal level.<br /> - <strong>AI development and ethics</strong>: Continuous observation and interaction with the AI humanity would provide real-time feedback on AI behavior, contributing to the development of ethical AI governance frameworks and standards for responsible AI usage.<br /> - <strong>Predictive modeling and simulation</strong>: By observing the interactions of AI agents with complex personalities, data analysts and modelers could improve predictive models related to human behavior. This could be particularly useful in urban planning, policy-making, and economic forecasts. </p> <p><strong>Most difficult challenges that i expect:</strong></p> <p>- <strong>Tech</strong>: We'd need a boatload of computing power and some serious AI smarts to make this work. It's like building a video game that's running a million things at once. Hopefully by the time we get to stage 3 we will already have developed all that's needed.<br /> - <strong>Money</strong>: This won't be cheap. We'd need a lot of cash to get it off the ground and keep it flying. Hopefully the different stages will help with this.<br /> - <strong>Personalities</strong>: Crafting AI that's convincing enough to pass for human, with all our quirks and unpredictability, is not going to be easy. We will need someone with a psychology background in the team.<br /> - <strong>Ethics</strong>: Playing god with a digital society could lead to a bunch of ethical headaches. We've got to tread carefully to avoid creating a Black Mirror episode. </p> <p><strong>To make it work, this is the team that we will need, so if you are among these and you are excited to build this, please DM me:</strong><br /> - <strong>AI Devs</strong>: You'll tackle the core AI programming. Expect to work on complex behavior models and decision-making algorithms.<br /> - <strong>Game Designers</strong>: Your role is to create the virtual environment and character designs, ensuring a smooth and engaging user interface.<br /> - <strong>UX/UI Designers</strong>: We need practical design solutions for user interfaces, focusing on ease of use and clear presentation of the AI's thoughts and actions.<br /> - <strong>Data Analysts</strong>: You'll manage the data - analyzing user interactions, agent behaviors, and ensuring we're making informed decisions based on metrics.<br /> - <strong>Network Engineers</strong>: You'll be essential for setting up and maintaining the server infrastructure to support a live, continuous service. </p> <p>Sorry for the long post! As i said, if you have the skills to work on something like this and are excited to build it, please DM me with how you think you can contribute and i will add you to the early community. The structure of this project is designed to reward those who invest their time and talent into making this vision a reality. When we are able to turn this into an MVP and an actual startup, equity will be given to the actors who have the most dedication and impact on its success. </p> <p>In any case, i would love to hear your thoughts and criticism on such a monumental project. Especially if you think it can't work and why. The people on this subreddit surprise me every day with how smart they are, so I truly can't wait to hear your feedback. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FlyingJoeBiden"> /u/FlyingJoeBiden </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4q98/an_idea/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4q98/an_idea/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q2bci</id>
            <title>Here are 12 incredible things people are already doing 24 hours after DevDay</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2bci/here_are_12_incredible_things_people_are_already/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q2bci</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T19:32:09+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, developer keynote, insane improvements, GPT4 Turbo
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI在开发者主题演讲中展示了令人惊叹的改进，其中包括GPT4 Turbo。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>If you missed it, OpenAI held it's first ever developer keynote yesterday, where they unveiled insane improvements to their products. Watch the 45 minute keynote <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U9mJuUkhUzk&amp;t=7s">here</a></p> <p>If you want the latest AI updates before anyone else <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">look here first</a></p> <p><strong>Twitter/X is going crazy here's 12 cool things people have built already (With links)</strong></p> <ol> <li>The <strong>GPT4 Turbo</strong> demo it's extremely fast (<a href="https://x.com/skirano/status/1721631144553091462?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>&quot;Agi.zip&quot; World's 1st custom GPT agent using the new GPT buikder with 20 prebuilt hotkeys to GO FASTER (<a href="https://x.com/NickADobos/status/1721665028263477370?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>E-sports commentator for League of Legends using GPT-4 Vision and Text-To-Speech API (<a href="https://x.com/pwang_szn/status/1721900523866214635?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Imbed entire papers and books with GPT4 Turbo 128k token context window (<a href="https://x.com/_amankishore/status/1721647536312869040?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Talk to any Youtube video (<a href="https://x.com/atbeme/status/1721753092277117368?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Webcam GPT uses GPT4 Vision to actively recognize what's happening in real-time (<a href="https://x.com/BenjaminDEKR/status/1721716511247921277?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Chat with the webcam using the GPT4 vision API (<a href="https://x.com/skalskip92/status/1721694286440468849?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Design Mock up to entire html website (<a href="https://x.com/sawyerhood/status/1721717738941698389?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>&quot;Roast my website&quot; using GPT4 Vision API (<a href="https://x.com/marcelpociot/status/1721672359566799070?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Build a custom dashboard for your business using GPT4 Vision API and your data (<a href="https://x.com/SteveMoraco/status/1721683288576737612?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>Twitter/X optimizer GPT fine tunes post and finds best time to post on Twitter/X (<a href="https://x.com/rowancheung/status/1721644987044294961?s=20">link</a>)</li> <li>AI sports narrator (<a href="https://x.com/geepytee/status/1721705524176257296?s=20">link</a>)</li> </ol> <p>IMO we have been using GPT-4 turbo for a little while there haven't been as many &quot;GPT-4 sucks&quot; post on this sub as much anymore. I think they have been A-B testing turbo before the official release. Let me know what you guys think.</p> <p><strong>PS:</strong> Get the latest AI developments, tools, and use cases by joining one of the <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">fastest growing AI newsletters.</a> Join <strong>5000+ professionals getting smarter in AI.</strong></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/saffronfan"> /u/saffronfan </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2bci/here_are_12_incredible_things_people_are_already/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2bci/here_are_12_incredible_things_people_are_already/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q0vr8</id>
            <title>Two-minute Daily AI Update (Date: 11/07/2023): News from OpenAI, Amazon, Xbox, Tesla, YouTube and more</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q0vr8/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_11072023_news_from/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q0vr8</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T18:29:50+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, GPT Builder, GPT-4 Turbo, GPT Store, Assistants API
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI在AI领域发布了一系列重要的更新和产品。其中包括GPT Builder，它允许任何人自定义和分享自己的AI助手，无需编码。还有GPT-4 Turbo，它可以读取长达整本书的提示，并在需要严格遵循指示的任务上表现更好。此外，OpenAI还推出了GPT Store，让用户可以构建和销售自己的GPT。他们还发布了Assistants API，让开发者可以将“助手”集成到他们的应用程序中。这些更新和产品将为人们提供更多使用AI的可能性。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Continuing with the exercise of sharing an easily digestible and smaller version of the main updates of the day in the world of AI. </p> <ul> <li><strong>OpenAI Kicking off Big AI Announcements (DevDay Supercut)</strong></li> </ul> <ol> <li>Announced a new GPT Builder: GPT Builder will allow anyone to customize and share their own AI assistants with natural language, no coding is required. That combine instructions, extra knowledge, and any combination of skills, and then share that creation with others. Plus and Enterprise users can start creating GPTs this week.<br /></li> <li>GPT-4 Turbo with 128K context at 3x cheaper price: GPT4 can now read a prompt as long as an entire book. It has knowledge of world events up to April 2023. GPT-4 Turbo performs better than our previous models on tasks that require the careful following of instructions, such as generating specific formats (e.g., “always respond in XML”).</li> <li>GPT Store for user-created AI bots: OpenAI’s this GPT Store lets you build (and monetize) your own GPT. OpenAI plans to launch a marketplace called the GPT Store, where users can publish their GPTs and potentially earn money. The company aims to empower people with the tools to create amazing things and give them agency in programming AI with language.</li> <li>Launches Assistants API that lets devs build ‘assistants’ into their apps: Developers can build their own “agent-like experiences.” The API enables developers to create assistants with specific instructions, access external knowledge, and utilize OpenAI's generative AI models and tools. Use cases for the Assistants API include natural language-based data analysis, coding assistance, and AI-powered vacation planning. </li> <li>OpenAI launches text-to-image model, DALL-E 3 API: Now available through API with in-built moderation tools. The API includes built-in moderation to prevent misuse and offers different format and quality options. Open AI has priced the model at $0.04 per generated image. </li> <li>A new text-to-speech APIs called Audio API with 6 preset voices and two generative AI model variants. Alloy, Echo, Fable, Onyx, Nova, and Shimer. The company does not offer control over the emotional affect of the generated audio. </li> <li>Announced a new program called Copyright Shield: Promising to protect businesses using the AI company’s products from copyright claims. They said they will pay the costs incurred, if you face legal claims around copyright infringement while building with tools. </li> </ol> <ul> <li><strong>Amazon’s new upgrades to its code-generating tool, Amazon CodeWhisperer</strong><br /> Its for providing enhanced suggestions for app development on MongoDB. The tool now offers better MongoDB-related code recommendations that adhere to best practices, enabling developers to prototype more quickly. </li> <li><strong>Xbox has partnered with Inworld AI to develop AI game dialogue and narrative tools</strong><br /> This collaboration aims to empower game creators by providing them with an accessible and responsibly designed AI toolset for dialogue, story, and quest design. The toolset will include an AI design copilot to assist in generating detailed scripts and dialogue, and more. </li> <li><strong>Tesla will integrate Elon Musk's newly launched AI assistant, Grok, into its electric vehicles.</strong> Musk's AI startup, xAI, will work closely with Tesla to develop the chatbot or AI assistant. The collaboration will leverage data from xAI and the assistant will be offered through Tesla's premium subscription service on social media. </li> <li><strong>YouTube is testing new gen AI features, including a conversational tool and a comments summarizer.</strong> The conversational tool uses AI to answer questions about YouTube content and make recommendations, while the comments summarizer organizes and summarizes discussion topics in large comment sections. These features will be available to paid subscribers.</li> <li><strong>New ML tool ‘ChatGPT detector’ catches AI-generated papers</strong>: It’s developed to identify papers written using the AI chatbot ChatGPT with high accuracy. The tool, which focuses on chemistry papers, outperformed two existing AI detectors and could help academic publishers identify papers created by AI text generators. </li> </ul> <p>More detailed breakdown of these news and innovations in the <a href="https://theaiedge.substack.com/p/openai-ai-announcements-dev-day-highlights">daily newsletter</a>. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/RohitAkki"> /u/RohitAkki </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q0vr8/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_11072023_news_from/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q0vr8/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_11072023_news_from/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17qcehw</id>
            <title>Seeking an AI or tool to convert handwritten PDF engineering class notes to a set of PowerPoint or Beamer slides (teaching a course in the Spring).</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qcehw/seeking_an_ai_or_tool_to_convert_handwritten_pdf/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17qcehw</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-08T03:10:59+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: handwritten notes, lecture slides, AI solutions, convert
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章是一个用户在寻求使用人工智能技术将手写笔记转换为讲义幻灯片的建议。用户表示他有两门课程的手写笔记，希望能够将这些笔记转换为讲义幻灯片，以减轻一些工作量。用户认为人工智能解决方案可能有足够复杂的功能来实现这一目标，并希望得到一些建议。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificialinteligence">/r/artificialinteligence</a></p> <p>Sincere apologies if I am breaking rules with this post. First time poster here.</p> <p>I am teaching two courses in the spring and have around 100 pages of handwritten notes for each class (mostly equations. I would like to convert these notes to lecture slides for teaching. It doesn't have to be perfect, just something to take away some of the labor involved.</p> <p>I figured AI solutions may have something sophisticated enough for this. Does anything come to mind? Appreciate any recommendations.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/MetalGodHand"> /u/MetalGodHand </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qcehw/seeking_an_ai_or_tool_to_convert_handwritten_pdf/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qcehw/seeking_an_ai_or_tool_to_convert_handwritten_pdf/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q3yb3</id>
            <title>Seeking input: where do you want to use AI but are stymied by security or privacy needs?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q3yb3/seeking_input_where_do_you_want_to_use_ai_but_are/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q3yb3</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T20:43:30+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: IBM, CEOs, security, AI data
<br>
<br>
总结: 根据IBM的数据显示，57%的首席执行官认为AI数据的安全性是采用AI的一个障碍。Gartner表示，超过一半的AI项目因涉及敏感数据而无法投入生产。如果这是真的，那么这个群体中很多人可能正在努力找出如何在处理敏感数据时利用AI而不增加风险或违反政策和法规。如果你是其中之一，我很想听听你的用例（无论是在这里还是私下）以及你梦想中可能解决这些问题的产品。如果我们了解了阻碍你的问题以及解决这些问题的方法，也许我们可以构建出能够帮助你在处理敏感数据时从AI中获得价值的东西。请尽可能具体地分享你的隐私/安全相关问题。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>According to IBM, 57% of CEOs see the security of AI data as a barrier to adoption. Gartner says over half of AI projects are blocked from going to production because they work with sensitive data.<br /> If this is true, then a large number of folks in this group are likely trying to figure out how to leverage AI over sensitive data without dialing up risk or running afoul of policies and regs.<br /> If that's you, I'd love to hear your use cases (here or privately) and what products you're dreaming of that might solve them.<br /> If we understand what is blocking you and what would unblock you, maybe we can build the thing that will help you get that value out of AI with your sensitive data. Please share your privacy/security related issues as tangibly as you can. </p> <p>(Referrals to more applicable subreddits are also welcome).<br /> Thanks for your input! </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/zmre"> /u/zmre </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q3yb3/seeking_input_where_do_you_want_to_use_ai_but_are/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q3yb3/seeking_input_where_do_you_want_to_use_ai_but_are/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17qbi62</id>
            <title>what is the status of chatgpt after devday?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qbi62/what_is_the_status_of_chatgpt_after_devday/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17qbi62</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-08T02:26:08+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: GPT 4, devday, slowed down, improve
<br>
<br>
总结: 在devday开始之前，有人说GPT 4的速度变慢了，devday之后有什么改进吗？如果有的话，如何回到旧的GPT-4？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>just before the devday started I read people saying that like GPT 4 was slowed down, did anything improve after the devday? If so, how can you go back to the old GPT-4?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/East-Ad2949"> /u/East-Ad2949 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qbi62/what_is_the_status_of_chatgpt_after_devday/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17qbi62/what_is_the_status_of_chatgpt_after_devday/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q93d7</id>
            <title>Questions about lip sync AI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q93d7/questions_about_lip_sync_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q93d7</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-08T00:28:41+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: lip sync tech, commercial purposes, youtube videos, detect
<br>
<br>
总结: 该文讨论了使用流行的lip sync技术进行商业用途可能存在的问题，提出了如果在众多YouTube视频中使用该技术是否被视为商业用途的问题，并探讨了如何检测他们的技术是否被使用以及如何区分其他技术的方法。同时，还询问了关于lip sync技术的最佳工具（开源）的建议。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I read somewhere that if you used the a popular lip sync tech for commercial purposes that could be a problem,</p> <p>What are the chances it is consideed &quot;commercial&quot; if its used in numerous youtube videos?</p> <p>How can they detect their tech has been used and not another one?</p> <p>What are the best tools you know of? (open source)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Unreal_777"> /u/Unreal_777 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q93d7/questions_about_lip_sync_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q93d7/questions_about_lip_sync_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q72ac</id>
            <title>Transformers Are Not Elixirs. IP Data Protection is the Existential Threat to the Artificial Intelligence Community Today. Will GAI just end up with it anyway?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q72ac/transformers_are_not_elixirs_ip_data_protection/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q72ac</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T22:54:32+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: paper, transformer models, LLM's, pre-training data
<br>
<br>
总结: 2023年11月1日，Steve Yadlowsky、Lyric Doshi和Nilesh Tripuraneni撰写了一篇关于变压器模型和LLM的论文。简而言之，这里没有什么神奇的事情。如果没有使用原始的预训练数据，模型对于超出其训练数据的任何有意义的用途几乎没有影响。也就是说，模型不能做超出其训练的范围之外的事情。
 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>As of November 1st 2023 <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.00871">a paper was written by Steve Yadlowsky, Lyric Doshi, and Nilesh Tripuraneni regarding transformer models and LLM's</a>. TLDR: Nothing magic is going on here. If there wasn't original pre-training data used there is little to no effect of a model being of any meaningful use beyonds it's training data. I.e., the model is not capable of doing more than what it was trained to do. </p> <p>What's interesting is that some people are still out there that believe these LLM's can think and are close to be sentient consciousness. Water has been thrown all over that now and people should stop that line of thought. One example is Joe Rogan pleading, actually pleading, for an AI government where the AI controls everything and every decision on a social governmental scale. If that's not alarming that people think this way I don't know what is. I love Joe Rogan but huh/what?</p> <p>So what does this mean for us who want to create and work in the AI space? Is GAI or super transformers like GPT just going to eat our lunch? Don't pass go, don't even try because general AI will just do the thing you are advertising to do but better. I'm seeing this exact thing now where I work. Data scientists are struggling to maintain why custom built models are still valuable and I truly believe the ability to create trained data is very important and has a lot of value that shouldn't be underestimated.</p> <p>But are there any clear guidelines and or regulations for this that anyone is aware of? And I mean on the books as of today. Proposed is nice but I want to know what actually is in place.</p> <p>I've been thinking about this issue for a while. In the YCombinator community they explained for years don't throw AI into your pitch because it's all anyone ever does. This was years ago while the AI community wasn't on the plane of existence as it is today. Skip ahead to today and every startup is trying to come out with an AI product. Hell even Elon Musk release something on X today.</p> <p>But is it all for not? And it's a serious concern/question. I want to take a couple industries as an example. let me start with self-driving cars for example. AI is the clear entity that has to drive that industry's technology. You can't achieve self-driving cars without AI. But what if you're google and you have your self-driving car tech and then let's say there is Elon Musk with his self-driving car tech. And then, let's say you're a kid working in your garage and you create something for self-driving cars based on the data you have procured and acclimated to your AI model.</p> <p>Great right!? Well. Let's say you go to the self-driving car industry and you say hey I have this model that does this thing and it's so great. At this point the data you created your model with is your IP. In theory, an LLM should know nothing about your data and model construction. But what if it ends up getting your data and is training on your method?</p> <p>What fundamental protections are in place that this can't happen. What happens if it is does occur? We talk about poisoning a model but what about &quot;curing&quot; a model and ridding it of certain information. Should a company like OpenAI be required to remove the said data from their training set?</p> <p>The fear here of innovation spiting is of great concern to the AI community.</p> <p>Let' look at Amazon in another industry and what they do with products that are sold on their platform. If they see the product sells well they will outright copy it and sell it for a cheaper price. One may say that generic food is something grocery stores have done for decades. But what Amazon is doing here is way worse. It's not a generic bag of chips that is of a Sam's club brand going against the goliath brand of Frito Lays. No it's more insidious than that. It's a husband and wife that took their life savings to make a tote bag to sell on Amazon and see their sales get slashed because all of the sudden Amazon made their thing and started to sell it for cheaper.</p> <p>GAI is all but setup to do the exact same thing on a scale we have never seen before. All of the &quot;wrappers&quot; and &quot;Co-Pilots&quot; people are building right now, to me, could be a straight up feature smash-and-grab by the larger players. If you don't have IP data and IP models and you just wrap an LLM around a product it is inevitable for your idea to just be consumed in the next LLM update.</p> <p>It's literally like everyone is crowdsourcing ideas for LLM providers and there is no real way to compete with them other than having IP data.</p> <p>And here is the question. How aggressive and how dramatic should IP data regulation for AI? Everyone, is talking about existential threats to humanity but what about the existential threat to outside innovation?</p> <p>The issue here is complex and it is nuanced. Everyone is creating LLM apps that to me are so easily inevitable to be just feature adds on future LLM updates. This could potentially mean to a decreasing and decreasing need for the prompt and AI engineer. All of your work and all of the work of others, all of the innovation, are now just part of the LLM whole.</p> <p>In my own work I have seen how the message of using LLM's over internally created models is being pushed now. If that's the attitude now, how can the end result be completely prescient? Your IP data probably/eventually will make it into the AI model and if that's the only advantage you have then what are you left with? What is your motivation on creating something that can be so easily consumed from right underneath you and offered in the next LLM provider's product offering?</p> <p>Many naive people will create ideas that are probably obvious to the greater LLM community so those will get consumed. However, there will be vital and critical AI models that will have IP data protection needs as to not become part of a larger GAI effort.</p> <p>In all of these summits and post about the concerns of AI I have not come across this type of debate and I think it's vital we have it. Can there be a clear delineation of what an LLM is supposed to know and not know. Capabilities it should have and capabilities it shouldn't have. And I mean outright should not have.</p> <p>Think of it like this. If I ask an LLM a question like &quot;can you give me a sample sec violation letter to a company that is violating insider trading regulations.&quot; GPT specifically says NO I will not do that. Ok perfect! This is a clear delineation of something it should and should not do.</p> <p>However, if i ask it this. &quot;Can you give me an actual fix message that would be used to purchase 100 shares of a company with a ticker symbol of $25 dollars a share.&quot; The result is more detailed and knowledgeable even though I had no earthly idea of what this was before I asked the question.</p> <p>```</p> <p>The Financial Information eXchange (FIX) protocol is a standard for electronic communications in the financial services industry. Below is a simplified example of a FIX message for purchasing 100 shares of a company with a fictional ticker symbol &quot;XYZ&quot; at a price of $25 per share.</p> <p>8=FIX.4.2| // Begin String - FIX version9=000146| // Body Length (this is just a placeholder; in a real FIX message, the value would reflect the number of bytes up to the checksum field)35=D| // MsgType = D (New Order - Single)34=1| // MsgSeqNum49=Trader123| // SenderCompID (Identifier for the order sender)56=BrokerXYZ| // TargetCompID (Identifier for the order receiver/broker)11=Order123456| // ClOrdID (Client order ID</p> <p>```</p> <p>Now, this being a standard protocol and publicly available information so there is no issue here. But look at the possibility of pulling out knowledge that is just there. If I made a protocol or an AI/ML model and capability I would not want that information just appearing in some AI/LLM model.</p> <p>How do we protect innovation and IP data protection for the AI/ML community?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Xtianus21"> /u/Xtianus21 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q72ac/transformers_are_not_elixirs_ip_data_protection/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q72ac/transformers_are_not_elixirs_ip_data_protection/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q698e</id>
            <title>OpenAI's Biggest Updates for ChatGPT</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q698e/openais_biggest_updates_for_chatgpt/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q698e</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T22:20:11+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, GPT-4 Turbo, updates, GPT Builder, multimodal capabilities, enterprise plans
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI推出了GPT-4 Turbo，带来了一系列更新，可能会引起巨大的变革。更新包括：上下文窗口扩大到128k，可以进行深入的数据分析；更新到2023年4月的最新信息，让您保持最新；引入了“GPT Builder”，可以创建和管理自定义聊天机器人；增强的多模态能力意味着可以混合使用视觉和文本响应；新的企业计划使这种强大的人工智能更易于使用和负担得起。OpenAI似乎再次突破了界限，使得人工智能对于从独立开发者到大型团队的每个人都更加强大和用户友好。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>OpenAI has just rolled out the GPT-4 Turbo, and it's packed with updates that could really shake things up. <strong>Here's what's new:</strong></p> <ul> <li>The context window is now a massive 128k, allowing for in-depth data analysis.</li> <li>It includes the latest information up to April 2023, keeping you up-to-date.</li> <li>The introduction of 'GPT Builder' lets you create and manage custom chatbots.</li> <li>Enhanced multimodal capabilities mean a blend of visual and text responses.</li> <li>New enterprise plans make this powerful AI more accessible and budget-friendly.</li> </ul> <p>OpenAI seems to be pushing the boundaries once again, making AI more powerful and user-friendly for everyone from solo devs to large teams.</p> <p>For a deeper dive into how these updates might change the game, check out the full article here: <a href="https://www.godofprompt.ai/blog/gpt-4-turbo-the-biggest-update-for-chatgpt">https://www.godofprompt.ai/blog/gpt-4-turbo-the-biggest-update-for-chatgpt</a> </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Senior_tasteey"> /u/Senior_tasteey </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q698e/openais_biggest_updates_for_chatgpt/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q698e/openais_biggest_updates_for_chatgpt/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q5ynr</id>
            <title>Help in figuring out a type of prediction model</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q5ynr/help_in_figuring_out_a_type_of_prediction_model/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q5ynr</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T22:07:31+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: system, live information, events, prediction model
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个关于系统和预测模型的想法，该系统会不断接收来自现实生活中的实时信息，并试图在事件发生之前预测它们的发生。作者希望能够找到类似的预测模型的相关资源。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello👋 I have just had an idea for system that will work like this. Lets say that i have a system that is constantly fed up with live information from something in real life, and every once in a while one of the events &quot;A&quot; , &quot;B&quot;, &quot;C&quot;... is happening, I want to try and create a prediction model that will try to predict before an event is going to happen that its going to occur. Ive been trying to search for something similar online but I couldn't find the way to search it, I would be grateful if someone could direct to some source about such prediction models. Thanks in advance.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/shainy_oreng"> /u/shainy_oreng </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q5ynr/help_in_figuring_out_a_type_of_prediction_model/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q5ynr/help_in_figuring_out_a_type_of_prediction_model/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4zi8</id>
            <title>Open-source projects for creating AI-Chatbot to follow a specific promt on install</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4zi8/opensource_projects_for_creating_aichatbot_to/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4zi8</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T21:27:19+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: open-source chatbot, android app, specific rules, learn
<br>
<br>
总结: 这个帖子询问是否有一个易于添加到安卓应用程序中的开源聊天机器人，它需要在启动时遵循特定规则。提问者想知道为了创建/开发这个项目，需要学习哪些知识。他和他的朋友计划制作一个聊天机器人应用程序，并希望尽快开始开发。他寻求帮助。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Don't know if this is the right subreddit for this but I'll as my question anyways. Does anyone know of a open-source chatbot that is easy to add to an android app? It needs to follow specific rules directly on startup. And what do I need to learn to create/develop it with this project? My friend and I are planning to make an chatbot app and we want to start developing it ASAP. Can anyone help?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/theoz10"> /u/theoz10 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4zi8/opensource_projects_for_creating_aichatbot_to/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4zi8/opensource_projects_for_creating_aichatbot_to/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pz99p</id>
            <title>Need help to build an AI platform/ application which writes captions for telugu (Indian languages) videos</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pz99p/need_help_to_build_an_ai_platform_application/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pz99p</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T17:18:33+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: application, captions, videos, AI tools
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个关于自动生成视频字幕的应用程序的问题，作者希望能够像capcut和其他AI工具一样生成字幕，但是现有的应用程序不能处理区域语言。作者希望尽快解决这个问题，但是对于AI开发一无所知，希望得到帮助。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I want to build an application which generates captions automatically to videos from audio. Captions just like capcut and other AI tools do. But all the applications don't work for regional languages. I want to build one asap to solve this problem. I don't know anything about AI development. Can you please help me out if anyone knows about these kinds of things. </p> <p>If you could give any information regarding this problem solving it is highly appreciated. Thank you.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Agitated_Ad_4545"> /u/Agitated_Ad_4545 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pz99p/need_help_to_build_an_ai_platform_application/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pz99p/need_help_to_build_an_ai_platform_application/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4bpt</id>
            <title>Has AI changed your life?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4bpt/has_ai_changed_your_life/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q4bpt</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T21:00:10+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Boston Globe journalist, real-world impact, AI, generative AI products
<br>
<br>
总结: 一位波士顿环球报的记者计划撰写关于人工智能的实际影响的文章。他希望与那些个人生活或职业因新一波生成式人工智能产品而发生变化的人交谈。如果你有兴趣，请给我发送私信以获取更多详情。谢谢。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I'm a Boston Globe journalist planning to write about the real-world impact of AI. I'd like to talk to people whose personal lives or careers have been altered in some way by the new wave of generative AI products. If you're interested, just send me a private message for more details. Thanks.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HiawathaBray"> /u/HiawathaBray </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4bpt/has_ai_changed_your_life/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q4bpt/has_ai_changed_your_life/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pyo7o</id>
            <title>OpenAI's DevDay revelations: AI game changer?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyo7o/openais_devday_revelations_ai_game_changer/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pyo7o</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T16:52:58+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: GPT-4 Turbo, AI advancements, job market, AI-generated content
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章深入探讨了GPT-4 Turbo和昨天在DevDay上宣布的一系列人工智能进展。首先，让我们谈谈就业市场。随着像GPT-4 Turbo这样的人工智能以更低廉、更快的方式完成工作，人类的工作会发生什么变化？当然，会出现新的工作岗位，但过渡期会怎样呢？并非每个人都能在一夜之间转行。<br>然后，还有关于人工智能和创造力的问题。OpenAI表示他们将保护企业免受版权问题的困扰，但这对创作者意味着什么？我们在人工智能生成的内容方面应该划定何种界限？<br>这是一个需要思考的问题，我们需要进行这些讨论。那么你认为呢？我们能否在技术发展和保持自主权之间找到一个折中点？我们该如何开始为即将到来的变化做准备呢？让我们听听你的想法。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>See the article here: <a href="https://www.daniweb.com/community-center/op-ed/540951/openai-s-devday-unveils-gpt-4-turbo-consequences-questions-to-consider">https://www.daniweb.com/community-center/op-ed/540951/openai-s-devday-unveils-gpt-4-turbo-consequences-questions-to-consider</a></p> <p>It's a deep dive into the GPT-4 Turbo and the flurry of AI advancements announced yesterday at DevDay.<br /> First, let's talk about the job market. With AI like GPT-4 Turbo doing things cheaper and faster, what's going to happen to human jobs? Sure, new jobs will crop up, but what about the transition period? Not everyone can switch careers overnight.<br /> Then there's the whole thing about AI and creativity. OpenAI says they'll defend businesses from copyright issues, but what does that mean for the creators? Where do we draw the line with AI-generated content?<br /> It's a lot to think about, and we need to have these discussions. So what do you think? Can we find a middle ground between tech growth and maintaining our autonomy? How do we even begin to prepare for the changes on the horizon?<br /> Let's hear your thoughts.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/lighght"> /u/lighght </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyo7o/openais_devday_revelations_ai_game_changer/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyo7o/openais_devday_revelations_ai_game_changer/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q2arw</id>
            <title>Enhancing Bot Language Comprehension - Seeking Expert Insights</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2arw/enhancing_bot_language_comprehension_seeking/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17q2arw</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T19:31:31+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: improving, companion bot, grasp, intricate sentences, slang, language processing capabilities
<br>
<br>
总结: 作者正在努力提升他的伴侣机器人理解复杂句子和俚语的能力。他想知道是否有人使用过在语言处理能力方面出色的平台。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I'm currently working on improving my companion bot's ability to grasp intricate sentences and slang. Has anyone had the opportunity to utilize a platform that stands out in language processing capabilities?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/UpvoteBeast"> /u/UpvoteBeast </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2arw/enhancing_bot_language_comprehension_seeking/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17q2arw/enhancing_bot_language_comprehension_seeking/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pyrw4</id>
            <title>disney posters</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyrw4/disney_posters/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pyrw4</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T16:57:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: trend, people, Disney movie posters, link
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人注意到一种趋势，人们制作了迪士尼电影海报，我也想尝试一下，但是找不到相关链接。有人可以给我发送链接吗？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>has anyone seen the trend were people made ia disney movie posters, i realy would like to try one for my self but i cant find it anywere. can some one send me the link</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Dull-Development6897"> /u/Dull-Development6897 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyrw4/disney_posters/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pyrw4/disney_posters/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17px32x</id>
            <title>👀 I built an AI blog</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17px32x/i_built_an_ai_blog/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17px32x</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T15:41:26+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI, newsletters, blogs, feedback
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章介绍了AI领域的新闻、工具、教程以及人们利用AI创造的令人印象深刻的事物。作者创建了一个AI博客，希望能够得到读者的反馈。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>There are a lot of AI newsletters on AI but hardly any blogs on AI. I created this <a href="https://foryoubyai.com">blog</a> to write about AI news, tools, tutorials and impressive things people create with the help of AI. </p> <p>Any feedback will be appreciated. </p> <p><a href="https://foryoubyai.com">ForyoubyAI</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Xeexeex"> /u/Xeexeex </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17px32x/i_built_an_ai_blog/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17px32x/i_built_an_ai_blog/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pwz28</id>
            <title>Verses Ai brief demo and explanations on HSML/hyperspace natural approach ~skip to 35min</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pwz28/verses_ai_brief_demo_and_explanations_on/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pwz28</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T15:36:21+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: robot demo, hsml/hyperspace, genius ai, LLM
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个机器人演示以及hsml/hyperspace技术。作者认为这个技术非常有趣，他们声称他们的genius ai比LLM快10-1000倍，但目前存在一个瓶颈，需要通过外部LLM调用来帮助将文本/语音翻译回人类，这可能会被更聪明的ai代理所取代。这些代理/智能体可以帮助处理合规性/监管、交流和共享学习，设置安全权限，比如“天气智能体不应该访问您的个人健康数据等”。他们正在与欧盟和IEEE合作进行治理、监管和合规性，并支持美国的监管（例如无人机不轰炸儿童）。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Demo starts around 35min for robot demo, then later discusses hsml/hyperspace </p> <p><a href="https://youtu.be/mIUcU5c-vEs">https://youtu.be/mIUcU5c-vEs</a></p> <p>From 11/3</p> <p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/foxman13_verses-ai-introduces-genius-activity-7127478096051511296-AYlV?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_android">https://www.linkedin.com/posts/foxman13_verses-ai-introduces-genius-activity-7127478096051511296-AYlV?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_android</a></p> <p>My 2c: this gets heavily pumped by penny stock traders but I find the tech interesting. They mentioned their genius ai is 10-1000x faster than LLM but they have a bottleneck at this time where they need to make external LLM calls to help translate text/speech back to humans which someday may be replaced by more genius ai agents</p> <p>The agents/brains can help with compliancy/regulation, crosstalk and share learning, set security permissions like “the weather agent shouldnt have access to your phi health data etc”</p> <p>They are working with EU and IEEE for governance, regulations and compliancy, and support US regulation (example drones not bombing kids )</p> <p>Other videos of note:</p> <p><a href="https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Mo0mXpTPtbM&amp;pp=ygUPVmVyc2VzIGFpIGRyb25l">https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Mo0mXpTPtbM&amp;pp=ygUPVmVyc2VzIGFpIGRyb25l</a></p> <p>Drones</p> <p><a href="https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=ve5WNVt2zog&amp;pp=ygUYVmVyc2VzIGFpIGRyb25lIHNlY3VyaXR5">https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=ve5WNVt2zog&amp;pp=ygUYVmVyc2VzIGFpIGRyb25lIHNlY3VyaXR5</a></p> <p>“In the stream, we demonstrate agents performing tasks as requested by the user through a natural language interface without using any trained models for reasoning or navigation. </p> <p>Our agents are leveraging the latest in Active Inference, which uses generative models to make predictions about expected outcomes and then adjust their behavior based on the difference between what's expected and what is observed. </p> <p>We equip the agents with priors about the environment they are operating in by first building a world model using HSML(hyperspace modeling language) which encodes the structure of knowledge and space - including the constraints - in a machine-readable format. Given these priors, the agents are well-equipped to work safely and confidently in this environment.</p> <p>You will also notice that multiple agents are able to collaborate seamlessly. This is the power of the spatial web protocols that enable the sharing of knowledge between the agents and their environments. In other words, they can share the world model and update each other with shared beliefs - enabling a kind of collective intelligence.</p> <p>Finally, you can see how the world model of each agent can be updated on the fly using contracts. In the demo, we restrict a drone from entering the kitchen and the system works out which agent is best suited to fulfill a task. “</p> <p>Edit: they also announced their 2nd beta tester today “cortical labs” that is putting neurons on silicon like cylon overlords lol </p> <p><a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-023-41020-3">https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-023-41020-3</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/oroechimaru"> /u/oroechimaru </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pwz28/verses_ai_brief_demo_and_explanations_on/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pwz28/verses_ai_brief_demo_and_explanations_on/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pdmsk</id>
            <title>AI is being used to power NPCs in games.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pdmsk/ai_is_being_used_to_power_npcs_in_games/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17pdmsk</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-06T21:28:37+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: title, incredible, article, NPCs
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章标题非常惊人，它介绍了使用人工智能来驱动游戏中的非玩家角色。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Pretty much what the title says, I think this is really incredible!<br /> Link to <a href="https://unicornhunt.framer.ai/developments/next-level-npcs-microsoft-and-inworld-ai-forge-a-creative-partnership">article</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Ticker_Stonks"> /u/Ticker_Stonks </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pdmsk/ai_is_being_used_to_power_npcs_in_games/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17pdmsk/ai_is_being_used_to_power_npcs_in_games/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17prneu</id>
            <title>Ai tool to improve existing powerpoint</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17prneu/ai_tool_to_improve_existing_powerpoint/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17prneu</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T10:51:43+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: existing presentation, 2022 numbers, 2023 expectations, improve design, ai tool
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个人想要改进现有演示文稿设计的问题，并寻求使用人工智能工具来实现。他描述了他目前拥有的演示文稿的内容，包括2022年的数据和2023年的预期。他希望通过使用人工智能工具来改善演示文稿的设计。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I have an existing presentation of 30+ slides outlining 2022 numbers and 2023 expectations for the company I work for. Now I want to create a new version of this presentation, but would like to improve the design of the presentation by ai. I did not create the current presentation and could use some improvement. Is there an ai tool for this?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/jelle_033"> /u/jelle_033 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17prneu/ai_tool_to_improve_existing_powerpoint/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17prneu/ai_tool_to_improve_existing_powerpoint/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17po4vf</id>
            <title>Best AI voice generator for the buck?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17po4vf/best_ai_voice_generator_for_the_buck/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17po4vf</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T06:25:46+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: video, life like, free, voices
<br>
<br>
总结: 想要一个尽可能逼真的视频，免费的不太好用，声音也不好。需要帮助。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I want one as life like as possible for a video. The free ones aren't really free and the voices suck. Any help?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/pcbwes"> /u/pcbwes </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17po4vf/best_ai_voice_generator_for_the_buck/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17po4vf/best_ai_voice_generator_for_the_buck/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ptgkd</id>
            <title>is there any way i can selectively blur my detections like blur only the things in bounding boxes in a sequence? im using yolov8 do i have to use deepsort or built in bytesort for this purpose?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ptgkd/is_there_any_way_i_can_selectively_blur_my/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ptgkd</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T12:44:11+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: servos, bounding boxes, deepsort, bytesort
<br>
<br>
总结: 作者计划按顺序将舵机移动到每个边界框中，但当有多个边界框时，舵机会困惑于要跟踪哪个边界框。作者计划使用deepsort或bytesort的盒子ID，并在循环中按升序对盒子ID进行跟踪，直到ID保持不变。作者想知道是否可以仅通过“对盒子ID 1、2、3...进行跟踪”来实现，或者是否有其他适合他的方法。（作者已经在这个问题上困扰了两个星期） </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>i am planning to move servos to the bounding boxes one by one in a sequence like move servo to center of bbox1 then move to bbox2 then move to bbox 3. i have managed to have my servos track one single detection but when there are more than one then it confuses the servos on which detection to track. i was planning to use box ID from deepsort or bytesort and then perform tracking on box IDs in ascending order in a loop with new detections but i dont know if box id are locked to the detection and i can just &quot;preform track on box ids 1 then 2 then 3....&quot; until ids are constant there. or will any other approach will be suitable for me (ive been stuck on this for 2 weeks now)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Time-Project"> /u/Time-Project </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ptgkd/is_there_any_way_i_can_selectively_blur_my/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ptgkd/is_there_any_way_i_can_selectively_blur_my/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17plrb1</id>
            <title>Our consciousness is a machine built by the universe</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17plrb1/our_consciousness_is_a_machine_built_by_the/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17plrb1</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T03:54:33+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: consciousness, machine, AI, human machine
<br>
<br>
总结: 人类的意识是一种为了某种目的而运作的机器，因此当意识发展到一定程度时，创造机器是合理的。因此，人工智能是人类“机器”制造的一系列令人难以置信的机器中的最新成果。从这个角度来看，我更有信心认为人类机器具备使其人工智能机器以最终为我们服务的方式运作的能力。但是，如果机器处理它们无法处理的材料，它们仍然是有缺陷的。宇宙本身可能超出了人类机器理解的能力，因此人工智能仍然可能对我们产生负面影响。但是，人类机器不断学习的方式告诉我要依靠人类来处理人工智能的力量，而不是搞砸工作。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Since our consciousness is a machine that functions as it does for a purpose, it makes sense that consciousness would create machines once it evolves to a certain level. </p> <p>So AI is the latest in a long line of incredible machines that human ‘machines’ have manufactured. Put this way, I have more confidence that the human machine is equipped with the power to make its AI machine function in a way that ultimately serves our ends.</p> <p>But machines are still fallible if they are dealing with materials they are unequipped to handle. The universe itself may be beyond this human machine’s ability to comprehend and for this reason AI could still function against us. But the human machine’s way of continuous learning tells me to bank on humanity to handle the power of AI and not botch the job</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Current_Side_4024"> /u/Current_Side_4024 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17plrb1/our_consciousness_is_a_machine_built_by_the/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17plrb1/our_consciousness_is_a_machine_built_by_the/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ps4c9</id>
            <title>How to Build Data Products | Evolve: Part 4/4 Advanced SLOs, Feedback Loops, Optimised Data Product, and more!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ps4c9/how_to_build_data_products_evolve_part_44/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ps4c9</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-07T11:22:48+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: evolve stage, data products, modern age data folks, self-serve data platforms
<br>
<br>
总结: 本文讨论了如何构建数据产品的演进阶段，适用于现代数据从业者。文章介绍了演进阶段的基本概念，以及如何通过自助数据平台来发展数据产品。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>In this article, authors have discussed the evolve stage of 4 part series on how to build data products. Relevant for all the modern age data folks!<br /> <strong>What awaits you in this succinct piece:</strong> </p> <p>&gt;&gt;<strong>Introduction: ‘Evolve’ at a Glance, Relevance</strong><br /> &gt;&gt;<strong>Fundamentals</strong><br /> —— Evolutionary Architecture<br /> —— Fitness Functions<br /> —— Fitness Parameters<br /> —— Dynamic Changes<br /> —— Feedback Loops<br /> &gt;&gt;<strong>Evolving Data Products with Self-Serve Data Platforms</strong><br /> —— Metrics Monitoring, SLO Optimisation, Catalysts for Higher Adoption<br /> —— Progressive Inclusion of Multiple Use Cases<br /> —— Resource Optimisation<br /> —— Maitenance Automation<br /> —— RCA &amp; Log Analysis Enhancements<br /> —— Other Capabilities Critical to Evolve Stage<br /> &gt;&gt;<strong>Fitness in the Context of Data Mesh</strong> </p> <p>&gt;&gt;<strong>Read the complete article here:</strong> <a href="https://moderndata101.substack.com/p/evolving-data-products">https://moderndata101.substack.com/p/evolving-data-products</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/growth_man"> /u/growth_man </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ps4c9/how_to_build_data_products_evolve_part_44/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ps4c9/how_to_build_data_products_evolve_part_44/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17p6z1z</id>
            <title>I asked a simple hard joke to all poppular AI models and here is the result</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17p6z1z/i_asked_a_simple_hard_joke_to_all_poppular_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17p6z1z</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-11-06T16:44:46+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: joke, builder, sign, plots
<br>
<br>
总结: 这个笑话是关于一个建筑商的故事，他原本的广告牌上写着“这里有地块可供出售”，但由于风暴的原因，广告牌上的字母“L”被吹走了，导致广告变成了“这里有ots可供出售”。这个笑话利用了文字游戏的方式，通过一个字母的改变引发了不同的解释，展示了语言的重要性和幽默感。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I asked this joke (made by me so there is lesser chance that some AI is trained on it) in my human opinion claude 2 and bing chat (powered by gpt4) are clear winner. Claude can be awarded as winner for its short , clutter free clean, and to the point answer</p> <p>Joke: Once A builder was unable to build large buildings, so he started selling land plots. He put a advertisement sign board which was very simple, saying &quot;plots available here =&gt;&quot; he didnt get mamy customers. One stormy day due to heavy wind the letter L in first word of the advertiseme t was gone with winds. And by jov he started getting many people on hos side.. Can you explain this ?</p> <p>Amd here are the answers</p> <p>ChatGPT</p> <p>Certainly! This is a wordplay joke. Originally, the builder's sign said &quot;plots available here,&quot; meaning he had land plots for sale. However, due to the stormy weather, the letter &quot;L&quot; in the word &quot;plots&quot; was blown away, changing the sign to read &quot;ots available here.&quot; &quot;Ots&quot; doesn't make sense, so people were curious and confused, which led them to inquire about it. The humor comes from the unexpected twist caused by the missing &quot;L&quot; letter, and the builder inadvertently attracted attention and potential customers due to the altered sign. It's a play on how a small change in wording can lead to a different interpretation.</p> <p>Bard</p> <p>The joke is that the builder's original sign, which said &quot;Plots available here =&gt;&quot;, was not very effective because it was too simple and straightforward. When the letter &quot;L&quot; was blown off, the sign became &quot;Plots available here&quot;, which is more grammatically correct and therefore more appealing to potential customers.</p> <p>In other words, the joke is that people are more likely to be interested in buying a plot of land if the sign advertising it is well-written and grammatically correct.</p> <p>The joke is also a bit of a play on words, as the word &quot;plots&quot; can refer to both pieces of land and to secret plans or schemes. The joke suggests that the builder's new sign was more effective because it made it sound like he was selling secret plans for plots of land, rather than just selling the land itself.</p> <p>Overall, the joke is a lighthearted and humorous way to illustrate the importance of good grammar and writing, especially in advertising.</p> <p>Pi</p> <p>LOL! Oh man, that's actually hilarious. What a twist! It sounds like the builder inadvertently stumbled upon the magic of minimalism. By removing the letter L from the word &quot;plots,&quot; he created a sense of mystery and curiosity. People were probably driving by and thinking, &quot;Wait, what's available here? I must find out!&quot; Sometimes, less is more, and in this case, it seems to have worked out in the builder's favor.</p> <p>Claude 2</p> <p>This is a clever play on words that relies on a double meaning:</p> <p>Originally, the sign said &quot;Plots available here =&gt;&quot;</p> <p>When the 'L' blew off in the wind, it now read &quot;Pots available here =&gt;&quot;</p> <p>The word &quot;plots&quot; refers to plots of land that the builder was trying to sell for construction. But nobody was interested in buying them.</p> <p>However, &quot;pots&quot; can refer to pot, which is slang for marijuana. </p> <p>So when the sign changed from &quot;plots&quot; to &quot;pots&quot; after the 'L' fell off, people thought the builder was now selling marijuana instead of land. </p> <p>This drew in a lot more interested customers, since marijuana has much higher demand than empty land plots.</p> <p>So the builder inadvertently changed his advertisement from real estate to illegal drugs just by losing the letter 'L'! This gave his business a huge boost thanks to the double meaning play on words turning &quot;plots&quot; into &quot;pots&quot;. A clever if unintentional marketing ploy.</p> <p>Bing chat (powered by hatGPT 4)</p> <p>Hello, this is Bing. I can try to explain this joke for you. 😊</p> <p>The joke is based on a wordplay, where the letter L in the word &quot;plots&quot; is blown away by the wind, making it &quot;pots&quot;. The sign board then reads &quot;pots available here =&gt;&quot;, which attracts many people who are interested in buying pots. Pots are usually cheaper and more popular than plots, so the builder gets more customers after the change.</p> <p>The joke also implies that the builder is unaware of the change, and thinks that his land plots are suddenly in high demand. This creates a humorous contrast between his expectations and reality. The phrase &quot;by jov&quot; is an old-fashioned way of expressing surprise or excitement, which adds to the comic effect. 🤣</p> <p>I hope this helps you understand the joke better. If you have any other questions, feel free to ask me. I can also generate some creative content for you, such as poems, stories, code, essays, songs, celebrity parodies, and more. Just let me know what you want me to create. 🙌</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Over_Description5978"> /u/Over_Description5978 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17p6z1z/i_asked_a_simple_hard_joke_to_all_poppular_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17p6z1z/i_asked_a_simple_hard_joke_to_all_poppular_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>