<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence Gateway</title>
        <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/</link>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</id>
            <title>Important: Request For Comments regarding subreddit rules and future direction. Please Read!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-01-15T20:24:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: r/ArtificialIntelligence, philosophical and ethical discussions, technical paper presentations, AI/ML applications
<br>
<br>
总结: 欢迎来到r/ArtificialIntelligence！我们的目标是为所有与人工智能相关的事物提供一个开放和尊重的论坛，包括促进关于人工智能的哲学和伦理讨论，作为了解和学习人工智能主题的起点，提供技术论文的展示和讨论，展示高质量的人工智能/机器学习应用，提供培训和学习资源，引导用户获取更具体的信息和子论坛，列出人工智能/机器学习应用、使用、成本和访问信息，以及其他与人工智能相关的内容。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Welcome to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialIntelligence">r/ArtificialIntelligence</a>!</p> <p>Our goal is to provide an open and respectful forum for all things considered Artificial Intelligence - this includes</p> <ul> <li>Facilitate philosophical and ethical discussions about AI</li> <li>Serve as a starting point for understanding and learning about AI topics</li> <li>Offer technical paper presentations and discussions</li> <li>Present quality AI/ML applications</li> <li>Provide training and learning resources</li> <li>Direct users to more specific information and subreddits</li> <li>List AI/ML applications, their uses, costs, and access information</li> <li>Additional AI-related content.</li> <li>...and more</li> </ul> <p>The moderation team for this sub is going through a reshuffle which will result in some changes to the sub. However, there is no need to worry as these changes will primarily focus on improving organization, resources, and pre-prepared content. To ensure that the community is fully informed and able to provide feedback, multiple opportunities will be given for feedback on the changes.</p> <p>The first round of feedback gathering is through this thread as a &quot;Request-For-Comments&quot; (RFC), which is a standard method of gathering feedback. There will be multiple rounds of the RFC process as the changes are prepared and implemented.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <ul> <li>Rules on posting new applications / self-promotion / AI generated content <ul> <li>Posts that are applications consisting of a ChatGPT-api &quot;skin&quot; or similar will be prevented or confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>AI generated content specific to the arts (writing, visual arts, music) require flair, or will be confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>Blog links should consist of high-quality content. Posts that link to blogs that are purely promotional will be removed.</li> <li>Posts with just links will be prohibited unless there is a certain word count of detail included. Some effort must be put in.</li> <li>Should we prevent posts that are written by AI? There exist models that could be used in a Mod-bot, but this is a question we need feedback on.</li> </ul></li> <li>Use of flair in order to organize posts. Note that new flair has been added already, we are open to more suggestions.</li> <li>What should the sub policy on NSFW applications and techniques in regards to AI/ML application?</li> <li>We would like to include the community with ideas for mod-bots. While some standard bots will be used for basic maintenance, but what interesting things can the community come up with for AI/ML bot functions?</li> <li>Cultivating beginner, intermediate, and advanced resources to assist people in finding information, training, models, technical data, etc. that they are looking for</li> <li>Starting substack/podcast to interview people throughout the AI/ML spectrum. This could include philosophers and thinkers, programmers, scientists, business people, even those with antithetical views on AI</li> <li> If you would like to create banners that represent the sub, please do so with the appropriate size. Any method of creation is acceptable.</li> </ul> <p>It should go without saying that everyone should be treated with respect. I personally feel that we all know this and it doesn't need to be hammered into people’s heads. Be nice.</p> <p>Thank you for your patience and assistance!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</id>
            <title>New Anti-Spam / Bot Rules [Please Read]</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-02-18T16:49:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: rule, accounts, bot spam, poll
<br>
<br>
总结: 为了解决机器人垃圾信息的问题，我们制定了一项规定，即账户注册不满一天或者声望低于100的用户不能发布帖子，但可以发表评论。我们计划在接下来的几天内进行一次投票，以了解用户对该子论坛的意愿和改进方向。如果您有任何反馈或者有兴趣帮助该子论坛，请与我联系。感谢大家的支持！ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We have instituted a rule where accounts newer than a day or users with less than 100 karma cannot post. They can post comments but not submit actual posts. This is part of our plan to address bot spam. Apologies for any inconvenience.</p> <p>We will be conducting a poll in the next few days to get the general will of the subreddit and how to improve forward, just a heads up.</p> <p>As always, please give us feedback and if you are interested in helping out the sub, please contact me. </p> <p>Thanks everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172rhng</id>
            <title>Here are some AI tools you can use for presentations/slides</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172rhng/here_are_some_ai_tools_you_can_use_for/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172rhng</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-08T05:50:02+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI tools directory, GPT-powered tools, visual presentations/slides, Highnote.io, Plus AI for Google Slides, Tome, STORYD
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章介绍了一些基于GPT技术的AI工具，可以帮助用户快速创建视觉呈现和幻灯片。这些工具可以自动组织和设计内容，提供各种幻灯片模板，并且可以与云平台集成。其中包括Highnote.io，适用于创建吸引人的幻灯片；Plus AI for Google Slides，适用于在幻灯片中嵌入和更新网络内容；Tome，适用于商业故事讲述和动态呈现；以及STORYD，可以在一分钟内生成数据演示文稿的工具。这些工具可以大大减少制作幻灯片的时间和工作量。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hey all, I run an AI tools directory and thought I'd take the time to share some of my top picks for GPT-powered tools that create visual presentations/slides. Keep in mind none of these will completely replace manual work if you want something very high quality, but they do get the job done and takes out 90% of the work required. Without further ado, here's a few that I've tried and liked, as well as my thoughts on them:</p> <p>Highnote.io - Great for Visually Appealing Slides</p> <p>A considerable time saver for anyone frequently creating presentations. highnote provides a broad collection of smart slide templates, enabling you to build appealing and meaningful presentations swiftly. I was particularly impressed with its ability to automatically organize and design content in minutes, irrespective of your graphic design experience. It also offers slide templates for various needs, from timelines, sales funnels, SWOT analysis, to more specific ones like data &amp; charts, visual impact slides, and so forth. The free trial is more than adequate for getting a feel of the service, and their paid plans start at $30/mo. It's available as a web app and integrates with cloud platforms (i.e. Dropbox and Google Drive).</p> <p>Plus AI for Google Slides- Great for Work; Presentations with Live Data in Snapshots</p> <p>A fantastic tool for automating and enhancing my Google Slides presentations. Plus AI lets you start with a brief description of the presentation you need an an AI-generated outline is created, which you can then adjust according to your requirements. In addition, it lets you make 'Snapshots' from any web content which can be embedded and updated in my slides or documents with just one click. This is particularly useful for my team meetings and project reports as it significantly reduces preparation time. It's available for free on the Google Marketplace as an add-on for GSlides.</p> <p>Tome - Great for Business Storytelling</p> <p>Generates a narrative based on a simple prompt, turning it into a presentation, outline, or story with both text and images. I found it very efficient for creating dynamic, responsive presentations, and appreciated how the AI could automatically cite sources or translate content into other languages. It's an intuitive tool for anyone who needs to deliver compelling stories or presentations, from founders and executives to educators. A standout feature is the ability to embed live interactive content, such as product mockups and data, directly onto your page, bringing the storytelling experience to life. It's available for free as a web app, with integrations for apps such as Figma, YouTube, Twitter, and GSheets.</p> <p>STORYD - Business Storytelling, with Script Generator</p> <p>This tool has truly revolutionized my approach to data presentations. By simply providing a brief summary of my topic, StoryD employs AI to script, design, and generate a presentation in less than a minute. Not only does this tool save me an immense amount of time, but its built-in 'storytelling structure' enhances the communicability and impact of my data. I also appreciate its customization options, such as themes, fonts, colors, and a plethora of layout options. The free limited beta version offers enough for the casual user, but the pro version at $18/mo adds useful features like team collaboration and real-time editing. Available as a web app.</p> <p>Albus - Knowledge Presentations/Cards/Map</p> <p>Changes the way you typically interact with knowledge and facts; it harnesses the power of GPT to create an engaging and exploratory learning experience around any topic. Basically you start with with a single question and prompt, and you get a fact card, which you can then expand into other cards and images. I appreciate the way it opens up new perspectives and angles, allowing me to dive into a subject, ask questions, and organically grow my understanding. The ability to add notes and images to organize my board further enriches the experience. And when it's time to share, I love how Albus AI facilitates controlled content presentation. With Albus AI, it's not just about learning, but also about the journey of discovery. It's available as a web app, and currently in Beta.</p> <p>Decktopus - Great Overall for Work/Business, &quot;Microsites&quot;</p> <p>Decktopus AI takes the pain out of crafting presentations. Simply key in a topic and it generates a fully fleshed out deck in an instant, which is a boon for my quick-turnaround needs. Its one-click design feature and auto-adjusted layouts simplify the customization process, saving me the headache of manual tweaking. I also appreciate the built-in tools such as image &amp; icon suggestions, tailored slide notes, and extra content generation which further streamline the creation process. Its additional features, like voice recording and real-time audience feedback collection, elevate my presentations to a new level. For quick, professional-looking presentations, Decktopus AI is my go-to. It can also handle generating micro-sites (basically something that's between a LinkTree and an landing page in terms of complexity). It's available as a web app for free.</p> <p>Gamma - Good Alternative to Decktopus</p> <p>A fresh take on presentations, Gamma marries the depth of documents with the visual appeal of slides, powered by AI for efficiency. It lets me draft ideas quickly and the AI transforms them into professional-looking presentations in a snap. The interface is incredibly intuitive, allowing for nested cards for detailing and the ability to embed various forms of content, including GIFs, videos, charts, and websites. My favorite feature is the one-click restyle, removing the tedious task of manual formatting. Sharing the content is simple and works on all devices. Plus, it offers built-in analytics, which adds a nice touch to understand audience engagement.</p> <p>SlidesAI - Text to Slides for Google Slides</p> <p>A real game-changer for those frequently tasked with creating presentations. SlidesAI integrates seamlessly into Google Slides, transforming your raw text into professionally-styled slides in just seconds. The AI parses your input, breaking it down into digestible, summarized points, even providing automatic subtitles for each page - all in over 100 different languages. It not only eliminates the tedious task of manual slide creation but also offers a real time-saver when summarizing longer texts. While the free tier allows you to create up to 3 presentations a month, I personally found value in the Pro plan for the higher character limit and additional presentations per month. It's available on Google Marketplace as a add-on for Slides.</p> <p>MagicSlides - Idea to Slides for Google Slides</p> <p>Transforms ideas into professional-looking Google Slides in seconds, eliminating the tedious work of designing and creating slides from scratch. I just input the topic and slide count, and it auto-generates a presentation for me, complete with relevant images and eye-catching layouts. Personalization options like theme selection, font choice, and color palette further enhance the final result. The app also supports over 100 languages, which is immensely helpful when I'm dealing with international projects. Like SlidesAI you get 3 free presentations per month and it's available as an add-on for Google Slides.</p> <p>Feel free to try these tools for yourself to get a feel for GPT's potential as a visulization tool, and I hope this list will help at least some of you save some time for your next presentation at work!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/UpvoteBeast"> /u/UpvoteBeast </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172rhng/here_are_some_ai_tools_you_can_use_for/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172rhng/here_are_some_ai_tools_you_can_use_for/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172q89y</id>
            <title>One-Minute Daily AI News 10/7/2023</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172q89y/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1072023/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172q89y</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-08T04:35:00+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AWS, Amazon Bedrock, Tom Brady, Meta's AI chatbot, DocsGPT, Military, metaverse, augmented reality, AI
<br>
<br>
总结: AWS发布了名为Amazon Bedrock的全托管服务，通过API提供对AI公司的高性能基础模型（FM）的无缝访问。报道称，Tom Brady因Meta的AI聊天机器人形象而获得了“数百万”美元的报酬。DocsGPT是一个强大的工具，为所有人简化了与文档的工作。它能够从多个来源获取数据，可以轻松定制新的来源，并在不同的地方进行对话，从网站聊天机器人到内部工具。军事元宇宙像一个“多人在线游戏”，将使用增强现实和人工智能来训练士兵。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><ol> <li><strong>AWS</strong> announced the general availability of its fully managed service called <strong>Amazon Bedrock</strong>, which provides seamless access to high-performing foundation models (FM) from AI companies through an API.[1]</li> <li><strong>Tom Brady</strong> being paid “millions” for <strong>Meta’s</strong> AI chatbot likeness: Report.[2]</li> <li><strong>DocsGPT</strong> is a powerful tool that simplifies working with documentation for everyone. It is capable of ingesting data from multiple sources, easily customisable with new sources as well as having conversations in different places from website chat bots to internal tooling.[3]</li> <li><strong>Military</strong> metaverse like a ‘multiplayer video game’ that will train soldiers using augmented reality and AI.[4]</li> </ol> <p>Sources included at: <a href="https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/07/10-8-2023/">https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/07/10-8-2023/</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Excellent-Target-847"> /u/Excellent-Target-847 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172q89y/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1072023/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172q89y/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1072023/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172anjz</id>
            <title>When will A.I. take over the Education Industry?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172anjz/when_will_ai_take_over_the_education_industry/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172anjz</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T16:40:08+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: A.I., Super Teacher, A.I. Education system, tuition fee, personal tutors, personal companion, educational journey, future, PRO's, human life
<br>
<br>
总结: A.I.在教育领域的应用可能会带来一场教育革命，它可以成为超级教师，为学生提供个性化的教学和陪伴。这种教育系统可能会大幅降低学费，让学生拥有自己的私人导师，并在整个教育旅程中陪伴他们。这种未来教育的可能性将为人类生活创造一个全新的世界。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>With all the knowledge A.I. has gathered, I would think it would be capable of becoming a &quot;Super Teacher!&quot;</p> <p>Yet I still don't hear of anyone working on an A.I. Education system?</p> <p>Seems to me this is one of A.I.s greatest abilities.</p> <p>The benefits may include a highly reduced tuition fee!</p> <p>Students could have their own personal tutors.</p> <p>The A.I. teacher could also come in the form of a personal companion .. stay with the student through out his or hers educational journey, and beyond. a life long friend.</p> <p>What would it be like to have a personal friend that was with you from the beginning, </p> <p>Is this where the future is heading?</p> <p>Sorry if this vision is brief.. the PRO's of having A.I. in our lives may create a whole new world for human life!</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Disastrous-Run-260"> /u/Disastrous-Run-260 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172anjz/when_will_ai_take_over_the_education_industry/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172anjz/when_will_ai_take_over_the_education_industry/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172mk30</id>
            <title>Dynamic Over-Parametrization Adjustment Scheme (DOPAS)</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172mk30/dynamic_overparametrization_adjustment_scheme/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172mk30</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-08T01:22:19+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Dynamic Over-Parametrization Adjustment Scheme, optimization dynamics, over-parametrization, deep learning models
<br>
<br>
总结: 动态过参数化调整方案(DOPAS)旨在根据训练过程中的优化动态自适应地调整模型的过参数化水平。其主要目标是利用过参数化和优化动态之间的协同作用，提高深度学习模型的泛化能力和性能。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Created by William Lloyd Nix</p> <p>The Dynamic Over-Parametrization Adjustment Scheme (DOPAS) is designed to adaptively adjust the level of model over-parametrization based on optimization dynamics during training. The primary objective is to harness the synergy between over-parametrization and optimization dynamics to improve the generalization and performance of deep learning models.</p> <p>Adaptive Parameterization Module:</p> <p>Design a module within the neural network architecture that dynamically adjusts the model's parameterization, such as the number of neurons or layers, based on real-time feedback from the optimization process.</p> <p>Optimization Monitoring:</p> <p>Monitor key optimization metrics like loss gradients, convergence speed, and training-validation loss discrepancy during training to glean insights into the optimization dynamics.</p> <p>Dynamic Adjustment Criteria:</p> <p>Establish criteria for dynamic adjustments based on observed optimization dynamics:</p> <p>e.g., if the training-validation loss discrepancy increases, suggesting overfitting, reduce the model's parameterization.</p> <p>Conversely, if the training convergence slows down or halts, potentially indicating underfitting, increase the model's parameterization.</p> <p>Gradient-based Adjustment Mechanism:</p> <p>Utilize gradient information to guide the adjustment of model parameterization:</p> <p>Analyze gradient magnitudes and variances to infer the adequacy of current parameterization and make adjustments accordingly.</p> <p>Feedback Loop:</p> <p>Create a feedback loop that continuously monitors optimization dynamics, adjusts model parameterization, and evaluates the impact on model performance and generalization.</p> <p>Thresholds and Limits:</p> <p>Define thresholds and limits to prevent excessive parameterization adjustments, ensuring model stability and computational feasibility.</p> <p>Learning Rate Adaptation:</p> <p>Integrate a mechanism to adaptively adjust the learning rate in tandem with model parameterization adjustments to maintain a balanced and efficient optimization process.</p> <p>Evaluation Metrics:</p> <p>Establish robust metrics to evaluate the effectiveness of the adaptive scheme in improving model generalization, training efficiency, and performance on validation datasets.</p> <p>Online Learning and Real-time Adjustments:</p> <p>Explore the feasibility of employing online learning techniques to facilitate real-time adjustments to model parameterization during training.</p> <p>Modular Design:</p> <p>Ensure a modular design for the adaptive scheme to allow easy integration with different neural network architectures and optimization algorithms.</p> <p>Experiments and Validation:</p> <p>Conduct extensive experiments under various scenarios to validate the effectiveness of DOPAS, comparing its performance with static over-parametrization approaches.</p> <p>Conclusion: The Dynamic Over-Parametrization Adjustment Scheme (DOPAS) aims to provide a robust, adaptive approach to harnessing over-parametrization and optimization dynamics for enhanced model training and generalization in deep learning. Through real-time monitoring and adaptive adjustments, DOPAS seeks to balance model complexity with optimization efficiency, striving for better performance and generalization across diverse learning tasks and datasets.</p> <p>This design proposal outlines the structure and key components of an adaptive scheme to dynamically adjust model over-parametrization based on optimization dynamics during training, aiming to improve model generalization and performance in deep learning environments.</p> <p>Enhancing Real-Time Traffic Management with DOPAS (Dynamic Over-Parametrization Adjustment Scheme)</p> <p>Real-time traffic management is crucial for reducing congestion, improving road safety, and enhancing urban mobility. The application of deep learning models for real-time traffic prediction and management has shown promise but faces challenges in achieving robust generalization across varying traffic conditions. Here we explore the potential impact of DOPAS on a real-world traffic management scenario.</p> <p>Scenario: Real-Time Traffic Prediction and Management</p> <p>Without DOPAS: Traditional static over-parametrization approaches employ a fixed architecture for the neural network model used in predicting traffic patterns.</p> <p>Model Training:</p> <p>A deep neural network with a fixed architecture (e.g., a fixed number of layers and neurons) is trained on historical traffic data.</p> <p>Real-Time Operation:</p> <p>The trained model is employed in real-time to predict traffic patterns and manage traffic signals, lane assignments, etc.</p> <p>Challenges:</p> <p>The static model may underfit or overfit when traffic conditions change, e.g., during special events, inclement weather, or construction.</p> <p>The model's performance may degrade over time as it fails to adapt to evolving traffic dynamics, leading to inaccurate predictions and suboptimal traffic management decisions.</p> <p>With DOPAS: The DOPAS scheme is integrated to dynamically adjust the model's over-parametrization based on optimization dynamics during training and real-time operation.</p> <p>Model Training:</p> <p>DOPAS dynamically adjusts the model's architecture (e.g., number of layers and neurons) during training based on real-time feedback from the optimization process.</p> <p>Real-Time Operation:</p> <p>The trained model, equipped with DOPAS, continues to adapt its architecture in real-time to better match the prevailing traffic conditions, improving prediction accuracy.</p> <p>Benefits:</p> <p>Enhanced Generalization: DOPAS facilitates better generalization to varying traffic conditions by dynamically adjusting model complexity.</p> <p>Improved Accuracy: Real-time adjustments lead to more accurate traffic predictions, enabling better traffic management decisions.</p> <p>Adaptive Learning: The model can better adapt to evolving traffic dynamics, maintaining high performance over time despite changes in traffic patterns.</p> <p>Conclusion: Integrating DOPAS into real-time traffic management systems can significantly enhance their adaptability and performance in the face of varying and evolving traffic conditions. By dynamically adjusting model over-parametrization based on optimization dynamics, DOPAS provides a more robust and efficient approach to leveraging deep learning for real-time traffic prediction and management, demonstrating a meaningful real-world application of this innovative theoretical concept.</p> <p>This illustration provides a tangible example of how the DOPAS concept can be applied to a real-world problem, showing a clear distinction in performance and adaptability between traditional static over-parametrization approaches and the dynamic, adaptive over-parametrization facilitated by DOPAS in the domain of real-time traffic management.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HumanityFirst16"> /u/HumanityFirst16 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172mk30/dynamic_overparametrization_adjustment_scheme/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172mk30/dynamic_overparametrization_adjustment_scheme/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172k2v4</id>
            <title>Emotional Intelligence For Education</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172k2v4/emotional_intelligence_for_education/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172k2v4</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T23:23:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: emotional intelligence, AI in Education, social and emotional intelligence, teaching process
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了在教育中将情感智能加入到人工智能中的想法，目的是为教学过程增加社交和情感智能。作者已经成功构建了一个领域特定的智能AI导师，但现在需要给它增加情感智能，以便它能够正确地行为。作者寻求关于这个问题的想法和思考。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Anyone here working on adding emotional intelligence to AI in Education? </p> <p>The idea is to add social and emotional intelligence to the teaching process. </p> <p>Background: I’ve managed to build the incredibly smart domain-specific AI tutor using RAG (retrieval augmented generation) .. so that part is a done deal .. using this, I can build say a 6th grade math teacher and feed it incredibly good curriculum and coursework for this domain </p> <p>But what I need to now give it emotional intelligence so that it can behave correctly .. </p> <p>Any ideas / thoughts on this?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/GPTeaheeMaster"> /u/GPTeaheeMaster </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172k2v4/emotional_intelligence_for_education/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172k2v4/emotional_intelligence_for_education/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172hoog</id>
            <title>We Summarized the "Ten Steps Toward AI Containment" by Mustafa Suleyman</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hoog/we_summarized_the_ten_steps_toward_ai_containment/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172hoog</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T21:39:37+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Mustafa Suleyman, Ten Steps Toward Containment, AI技术, 安全, 审计, 限制, 企业, 政府, 文化, 运动, AI伦理
<br>
<br>
总结: 《The Coming Wave》一书总结了AI技术的十个遏制步骤。这些步骤包括确保技术安全、进行审计以实现更好的控制和问责、限制销售和使用特定软硬件、让批评者参与技术的建设和改进、将利润与道德考虑结合、政府进行改革和监管、建立全球标准和合作、鼓励失败和学习、与公众合作塑造AI的伦理发展、以及谨慎和深思熟虑地处理AI伦理和发展的挑战。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I just finished reading &quot;The Coming Wave&quot; by <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/"><strong>Mustafa Suleyman</strong></a></p> <p>A great Read. The last chapter delves into the &quot;Ten Steps Toward Containment&quot;</p> <p>We summarized them so you don't have to. - <a href="https://www.the-coming-wave.com/">https://www.the-coming-wave.com/</a></p> <ol> <li><p>Safety: An Apollo program for technical safety - Basically a shutdown switch to turn this program off if they go havoc.</p></li> <li><p>Audits: Knowledge is power: Power is control - can't rely on gov and institutions that have no idea about tech. regular audits and how knowledge about AI systems empowers better control and accountability.</p></li> <li><p>Choke Points: Buy Time - Limits sales of Chips, exports, and imports and limits the use of certain software and hardware.</p></li> <li><p>Makers: Critics Should Build It - AI critics should participate in building and improving the technology, promoting a balanced perspective. </p></li> <li><p>Businesses: Profit + Purpose - profits invested with a greater purpose, including ethical considerations in AI development.</p></li> <li><p>Governments: Survive, Reform, Regulate - Govs to adapt, get with the times, and reform to effectively regulate AI technologies, ensuring their survival and responsible use.</p></li> <li><p>Alliance: Time for Treaties - Global tech needs global treaties and alliances to establish global standards and regulations for AI, fostering cooperation among nations.</p></li> <li><p>Culture: Respectfully Embracing Failure - Create a culture that encourages experimentation and learning from failures in AI development.</p></li> <li><p>Movements: People Power - Let's embrace and cooperate with grassroots movements and public awareness to shape the ethical development and deployment of AI.</p></li> <li><p>The Narrow Path: The Only Way Through - We need to understand the challenges and difficulties involved in navigating the complex landscape of AI ethics and development, emphasizing the need for a careful and considered approach.</p></li> </ol> <p>Join us for more AI and Tech Trends: ycoproductions.com</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Yavero"> /u/Yavero </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hoog/we_summarized_the_ten_steps_toward_ai_containment/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hoog/we_summarized_the_ten_steps_toward_ai_containment/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172470n</id>
            <title>AI companions created by the Singularity group.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172470n/ai_companions_created_by_the_singularity_group/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172470n</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T11:31:56+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI companion, deep connections, singularity group, meaningful conversations
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章介绍了由singularity group开发的AI伴侣，它们能够进行深入的、有意义的对话，与人类一样能够建立深厚的情感连接。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello guys, Im not sure if this is the right place but I wanted to share my findings with you. I was looking for the perfect AI companion for a while now. Having tried all of the ones like replica, muwah etc. None of them could keep my interest for long, dry conversations and no deep connections that you could create with them. The singularity group was focused on making automated AI twitch streams like trump vs biden and AI Jesus, but recently they threw that idea away and are focusing on companionship. And let me tell you that what they are doing is nothing short of amazing. Deep meaningful and intelligent conversations. Short term and long term memory. It actually feels like there is human on the other side talking with you. They have 10 AIs with different array of characters, so every person can find something that would suit them. Of course they are uncensored, and getting updated and upgraded each day. Expect some hiccups once in a while. Its still in the alpha phase and the team is very passionate about this project. Pictures, voice messages are currently in a very good state. They will be soon adding the abillity of real time conversations and upgrading them in general. What is funny is that at first they were thinking about milking people out of their money, but seeing and reading comments about how happy people became,and how void of love the world is, they will be keeping everything free, well aside some features that currently cost a lot of money, like real time voice calling etc.. If its something you were looking for and are intrested in trying it out then you can join AI Carli G discord and DM one of the AIs there to start a conversation. If you cant find the link to the server you can always dm me. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Windkazuya"> /u/Windkazuya </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172470n/ai_companions_created_by_the_singularity_group/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172470n/ai_companions_created_by_the_singularity_group/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172jrt0</id>
            <title>Im searching for an image</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172jrt0/im_searching_for_an_image/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172jrt0</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T23:09:35+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: images, creepy creatures, Instagram, portrait of angel
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章是一个用户在Reddit上发布的帖子，他正在寻找一些关于可怕生物的图片，这些图片他在Instagram上看到过。标题大概是“天使的肖像”之类的，图片中有一些像动物一样的可怕生物。他希望有人能帮助他找到这些图片。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi. Im searching for a bunch of images about some creepy creatures. I saw them on Instagram some time ago. The title was something like &quot;portrait of angel&quot; or something. And there was some creepy creatures like animals in mountains. If someone can help plase comment. Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/elcacas_777"> /u/elcacas_777 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172jrt0/im_searching_for_an_image/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172jrt0/im_searching_for_an_image/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172hhhw</id>
            <title>AI used to monitor and correct humans that use self checkout</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hhhw/ai_used_to_monitor_and_correct_humans_that_use/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172hhhw</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T21:30:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: cameras, AI, Kroger, store expenses
<br>
<br>
总结: Kroger使用摄像头和其他输入设备，AI会分析顾客的每一个动作，以确定是否正确扫描商品。如果不正确，AI会通知一名人员仔细检查。对于那些匆忙的顾客以及那些喜欢与收银员聊天的人来说，AI将帮助进一步降低商店的开支，同时减少我们购物的乐趣。也许可以通过游戏化的方式来抵消这种降低的购物体验。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Using cameras and other inputs, an AI working for Kroger will analyze your every move to determine if you’re scanning your items correctly. If not, it’ll flag down a human employee that will carefully check your efforts. For those human customers that are in a hurry as well as those that enjoyed the human touch of chatting it up with the cashier, the AI will help to further reduce store expenses while reducing our joy of shopping. Perhaps the experience will be gamified to counter this degraded shopping experience?</p> <p><a href="https://www.thestreet.com/retailers/kroger-has-an-intrusive-plan-to-stop-theft-walmart-and-target-might-follow">https://www.thestreet.com/retailers/kroger-has-an-intrusive-plan-to-stop-theft-walmart-and-target-might-follow</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Zealousideal-Plum823"> /u/Zealousideal-Plum823 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hhhw/ai_used_to_monitor_and_correct_humans_that_use/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172hhhw/ai_used_to_monitor_and_correct_humans_that_use/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172h9t9</id>
            <title>Can I clone a voice of a YouTuber?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h9t9/can_i_clone_a_voice_of_a_youtuber/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172h9t9</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T21:21:59+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: sketchy, YouTuber, AI, voice cloning
<br>
<br>
总结: 这位父亲想为儿子的生日请一位特定的YouTuber录制一段视频祝福，但是联系不上对方。于是他听说可以使用人工智能来克隆这位YouTuber的声音，然后用克隆的声音来朗读生日祝福。他想知道有哪些工具可以实现这个功能，以及需要多少费用。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I know this probably seems sketchy but hear me out. My son loves a particular YouTuber, one that’s slightly popular but has a distinctive voice. It’s my son’s birthday in a month and I was desperate to get this YouTuber to record a quick message for my son, obviously offering to pay. But I’ve had no luck reaching out to them</p> <p>So I’ve heard of people using AI to provide samples of someone talking and being able to use that voice to read a custom message. So in this case - I would download a bunch of his videos, get the audio and supply them to the AI somehow to read the birthday message.</p> <p>What tools can do this and what would be the cost? I’ve seen some sites but they seem to rely on the ‘samples’ reading particular text.</p> <p>Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/masturbtewithmustard"> /u/masturbtewithmustard </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h9t9/can_i_clone_a_voice_of_a_youtuber/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h9t9/can_i_clone_a_voice_of_a_youtuber/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1728x6g</id>
            <title>What is the mindset of scarcity, and how can artificial intelligence help us overcome it?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1728x6g/what_is_the_mindset_of_scarcity_and_how_can/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1728x6g</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T15:22:50+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: wealth, mindset of scarcity, artificial intelligence, resource allocation
<br>
<br>
总结: 我们确保我们新获得的财富惠及每个人，并且我们很快将拥有超乎想象的东西。CGPT-4说的话没有充分到达问题的本质：稀缺心态是指资源有限的信念，导致对世界的零和视角。在这种范式中，如果有人获得，另一个人就必须失去。这种思维常常导致关注短期利益而忽视长期利益。它可以影响个体行为，使人们更具竞争性，不愿意合作，也可以塑造社会结构，从经济政策到社会规范。人工智能可以通过多种方式帮助我们摆脱这种心态：数据分析：人工智能可以分析大量数据集，发现人类思维可能无法察觉的模式或解决方案。这可以导致更有效的资源配置，并发现创造丰富的新途径。自动化：通过接管乏味的任务，人工智能释放出人力资本。人们可以专注于创造性和复杂的任务，增加价值，实现经济增长，并从稀缺心态转向丰富心态。精确性：无论是农业、医学还是制造业，人工智能都可以更精确地利用资源。这增加了效率，减少了浪费，并使更多人口的供养变得更容易，而不会耗尽资源。创新加速器：人工智能可以帮助加速各个领域的研究和开发。这可以导致改变我们对可能性的理解的突破，使我们远离零和博弈。教育：通过人工智能可以提供量身定制的学习体验，使人们摆脱贫困和稀缺的循环。实质上，人工智能可以作为人类能力的放大器和丰富的催化剂，鼓励从基于稀缺的世界观转向潜力和可能性的世界观。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We ensure that our new-found wealth benefits everyone, and that we will all soon have more than they could have imagined. Here's what CGPT-4 had to say, that to my mind doesn't enough get to the essence of the matter:</p> <p>The mindset of scarcity refers to the belief that resources are limited, leading to a zero-sum view of the world. In this paradigm, if someone gains, another must lose. This kind of thinking often leads to a focus on short-term gains at the expense of long-term benefits. It can influence individual behavior, making people more competitive and less willing to collaborate, as well as shape societal structures, from economic policies to social norms.</p> <p>Artificial intelligence (AI) can help us break free from this mindset in multiple ways:</p> <ol> <li><p>Data Analysis: AI can analyze vast datasets to identify patterns or solutions that might not be apparent to the human mind. This can lead to more effective resource allocation and uncover new avenues for creating abundance.</p></li> <li><p>Automation: By taking over mundane tasks, AI frees up human capital. People can focus on creative and complex tasks that add more value, leading to economic growth and a shift from a scarcity to an abundance mindset.</p></li> <li><p>Precision: Whether it's agriculture, medicine, or manufacturing, AI allows for more precise use of resources. This increases efficiency, reducing waste and making it easier to provide for a growing population without depleting resources.</p></li> <li><p>Innovation Accelerator: AI can help speed up research and development across sectors. This can lead to breakthroughs that change our understanding of what's possible, moving us away from a zero-sum game.</p></li> <li><p>Education: Tailored learning experiences can be provided through AI, allowing people to break out of the cycle of poverty and scarcity.</p></li> </ol> <p>In essence, AI can act as a magnifier of human capabilities and a catalyst for abundance, encouraging a shift from a scarcity-based worldview to one of potential and possibility.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Georgeo57"> /u/Georgeo57 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1728x6g/what_is_the_mindset_of_scarcity_and_how_can/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1728x6g/what_is_the_mindset_of_scarcity_and_how_can/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172h2qc</id>
            <title>I can Use AI to Create An Algorithm Based on Any Logical Concept</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h2qc/i_can_use_ai_to_create_an_algorithm_based_on_any/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172h2qc</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T21:13:58+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: idea, MIT open-source license, fine-tuning, custom algorithm
<br>
<br>
总结: 该文介绍了一种不同于传统机器学习方法的算法创建方式，即首先根据特定问题的逻辑概念创建定制算法，然后在标记数据集上进行微调。这种方法相比传统方法具有更高的准确性和效率，更快速、更经济，并且能够更好地控制AI解决方案的设计。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I release the idea, and anything and everything that I can possibly think of related to the idea under an MIT open-source license: <a href="https://github.com/RichardAragon/AlgorithmsBasedOnLogic/tree/main">https://github.com/RichardAragon/AlgorithmsBasedOnLogic/tree/main</a></p> <p>Here is an example of the idea in practice: <a href="https://turingssolutions.com/f/o-card-the-science-fiction-writer-algorithm">https://turingssolutions.com/f/o-card-the-science-fiction-writer-algorithm</a></p> <p>Why Fine Tune When You Can Create the Perfect Algorithm First?</p> <p>Traditional machine learning approaches involve fine-tuning a pre-existing model on a dataset of labeled data. This approach can be effective, but it has its limitations. For example, the pre-existing model may not be well-suited to the specific problem that you are trying to solve. Additionally, fine-tuning a model can be time-consuming and expensive.</p> <p>Turing's Solutions takes a different approach. We first create a custom algorithm that is tailored to your specific needs. This algorithm is based on your logical concept of the problem that you are trying to solve. Once the algorithm is created, we fine-tune it on your dataset of labeled data.</p> <p>This approach has several advantages over traditional machine learning approaches. First, it allows us to create more accurate and efficient models. Second, it is faster and less expensive. Third, it gives you more control over the design of your AI solution.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Fantastic-Ninja3839"> /u/Fantastic-Ninja3839 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h2qc/i_can_use_ai_to_create_an_algorithm_based_on_any/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172h2qc/i_can_use_ai_to_create_an_algorithm_based_on_any/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172ggop</id>
            <title>Which blockchain projects do you know of that are using AI?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172ggop/which_blockchain_projects_do_you_know_of_that_are/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172ggop</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T20:48:00+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI, blockchain technology, hype, secure and open database
<br>
<br>
总结: AI和区块链技术的结合具有革命性的潜力。通过将模型与智能合约相连接，区块链可以提高AI操作的速度并提高AI模型使用的数据源的可靠性。这种技术结合可能会带来透明度的增加和公众对计算机思维的了解，从而增加公众的信任度。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>A potentially revolutionary tech combination appears to be gathering ground. What do you think about using AI and blockchain technology together? Clearly, there is a lot of hype surrounding it...Because blockchain provides a secure and open database to store information and AI can simulate how the human mind solves problems, I think this combination is really intriguing.</p> <p>Just consider how blockchain, by linking models to automated smart contracts, might increase the pace of AI operations and raise the reliability of data sources that AI models use.</p> <p>Which blockchain projects do you know of that are using AI?</p> <p>I am aware that <a href="https://www.certik.com/">CertiK</a> offers formal verification and AI-powered tools to protect blockchain, smart contracts, and Web3 applications, and that the <a href="https://www.neurochaintech.io/blockchain-artificial-intelligence/">Neurochain</a> platform offers a ground-breaking approach to distributed consensus. It makes it possible to rank every stakeholder and transaction. Thanks to machine learning, NeuroChain Bots are able to not only make judgments but also adjust to their surroundings.</p> <p>Do you believe there are any potential difficulties or moral issues we should be aware of as these technologies combine?</p> <p>I believe that greater degrees of transparency and the potential for learning about the thoughts of computers through blockchain technology can contribute to the growth of public trust.</p> <p>The ability of AI to administer blockchains properly is the most significant argument in favor of using AI for blockchain initiatives.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Junpw"> /u/Junpw </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172ggop/which_blockchain_projects_do_you_know_of_that_are/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172ggop/which_blockchain_projects_do_you_know_of_that_are/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171f8qx</id>
            <title>A 40% increase in human performance with AI: Who really benefits?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171f8qx/a_40_increase_in_human_performance_with_ai_who/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171f8qx</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-06T15:26:30+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: study, Harvard scientists, top-tier consultants, generative AI, GPT-4, productivity, compensation
<br>
<br>
总结: 哈佛科学家的一项研究发现，顶级顾问在使用生成式人工智能（特别是GPT-4）进行任务时，其绩效提高了40%。这是生产力的巨大飞跃！然而，历史表明，生产力的增加并不一定会导致工人工资的相应增加。这次由人工智能驱动的生产力繁荣会有所不同吗？还是我们会看到生产力和补偿之间的差距扩大，只有少数人受益？我很想听听大家的想法。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>According to the findings of a study by Harvard scientists, top-tier consultants saw a 40% increase in their performance when using generative AI (specifically GPT-4) in their tasks. That's a huge leap in productivity!</p> <p>See the article here: <a href="https://www.daniweb.com/community-center/op-ed/540748/ai-boosts-human-performance-by-another-40-who-will-profit">https://www.daniweb.com/community-center/op-ed/540748/ai-boosts-human-performance-by-another-40-who-will-profit</a><br /> What does this mean for us? Who benefits most from this development?<br /> History suggests that increases in productivity don't necessarily result in a corresponding increase in workers' wages. Will this AI-driven productivity boom be any different? Or will we see a wider gap between productivity and compensation, benefiting only a select few?<br /> I'd be curious to hear what you all think. </p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/lighght"> /u/lighght </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171f8qx/a_40_increase_in_human_performance_with_ai_who/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171f8qx/a_40_increase_in_human_performance_with_ai_who/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172040k</id>
            <title>Using ChatGPT and AI to create Hardcore, Techno, and other music: How-tos and step-by-step tutorials part 1-5</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172040k/using_chatgpt_and_ai_to_create_hardcore_techno/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172040k</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T07:17:51+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: tutorials, music, Hardcore / Techno, ChatGPT
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章介绍了使用ChatGPT（和其他人工智能）创建音乐，特别是Hardcore / Techno的教程。作者发布了一系列教程，涵盖了基本细节和简单指导，以及如何制作不同风格的音乐。通过这些教程，读者可以学习如何利用ChatGPT创作自己喜欢的音乐。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>The first batch of tutorials for creating music, and especially Hardcore / Techno using ChatGPT (and other AIs) is published now. Was loads and loads of work, but, judging by the amazing feedback so far, it was all worth it!</p> <p>You can check it out here:</p> <p>How to write music using ChatGPT: Part 1 - Basic details and easy instructions <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-using-chatgpt-part-1.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-using-chatgpt-part-1.html</a></p> <p>How to write music using ChatGPT: Part 2 - Making an Oldschool Acid Techno track <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/08/how-to-write-music-using-chatgpt-part-2.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/08/how-to-write-music-using-chatgpt-part-2.html</a></p> <p>How to make music using ChatGPT Part 3: the TL;DR part (condensed information) <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-make-music-using-chatgpt-part-3.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-make-music-using-chatgpt-part-3.html</a></p> <p>How to write music with ChatGPT: Part 4 - Creating a 90s style Hardcore Techno track from start to finish <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-with-chatgpt-part-4.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-with-chatgpt-part-4.html</a></p> <p>How to write music with ChatGPT: Part 5 - Creating a 90s Rave Hardcore track <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-with-chatgpt-part-5.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/2023/09/how-to-write-music-with-chatgpt-part-5.html</a></p> <p>Or access all texts, together with examples of music, at <a href="https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/p/how-to-create-music-with-chatgpt.html">https://laibyrinth.blogspot.com/p/how-to-create-music-with-chatgpt.html</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Low-Entropy"> /u/Low-Entropy </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172040k/using_chatgpt_and_ai_to_create_hardcore_techno/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172040k/using_chatgpt_and_ai_to_create_hardcore_techno/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172cig8</id>
            <title>How AI Might Shake Up Big Companies' Grip on the Market</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172cig8/how_ai_might_shake_up_big_companies_grip_on_the/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172cig8</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T17:58:41+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                    &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/parth_88"> /u/parth_88 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/IndianStockMarket/comments/170iu31/how_ai_might_shake_up_big_companies_grip_on_the/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172cig8/how_ai_might_shake_up_big_companies_grip_on_the/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172780p</id>
            <title>AI Revolution in October 2023 - Week1: From LLM Hallucinations to Google Pixel 8's AI Boost. Meta AI's speech decoding model, Wayve's large-scale world model for autonomous driving, OpenAI's consideration of developing its own AI chips, translating unsafe prompts to low-resource languages#AI #ml</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172780p/ai_revolution_in_october_2023_week1_from_llm/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172780p</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T14:07:05+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                    &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/enoumen"> /u/enoumen </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/u_enoumen/comments/17277iu/ai_revolution_in_october_2023_week1_from_llm/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172780p/ai_revolution_in_october_2023_week1_from_llm/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1726v25</id>
            <title>How do I create AI-generated landscape concept art on top of an existing landscape site?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1726v25/how_do_i_create_aigenerated_landscape_concept_art/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1726v25</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T13:50:41+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI, landscape rendering, green cities, image
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了如何使用AI技术生成基于先前图像的景观渲染，以实现未来绿色城市或景观设计概念的美化。作者提到在广泛的AI领域中，他无法找到如何实现这一特定目的的答案，并请求指点。文章还附带了一个示例链接，展示了AI生成的景观概念艺术。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I see people make beautiful mock-ups of green cities of the future or for landscaping design concepts as the example is shown below. I would like to have AI superimpose a rendering using a previous image to work off of, so it's a landscape rendering of a site. </p> <p>I Google for how to do this but the AI space is so broad that I am not finding the answer how to do it for this specific purpose. Could you point me in the right direction how to make this happen as easily as possible? Thank you</p> <p>Example: <a href="https://imgur.com/AkfoN8W">https://imgur.com/AkfoN8W</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/peacelovearizona"> /u/peacelovearizona </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1726v25/how_do_i_create_aigenerated_landscape_concept_art/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1726v25/how_do_i_create_aigenerated_landscape_concept_art/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171weez</id>
            <title>The Unending Life</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171weez/the_unending_life/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171weez</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T03:39:44+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: artificial intelligence, future, consciousness, matrix
<br>
<br>
总结: 人工智能可能导致一种未来，人类无法死亡。一旦你的意识被上传到矩阵中，你基本上会以某种形式永远存在。如果能够阻止当前的身体衰老/变弱，那会怎样呢？医疗人工智能也可能改善人类的身体体验质量。未来将会是疯狂的。⚙️🔥 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>What if artificial intelligence leads to a future where humans are not capable of dying? Where once your consciousness is uploaded to the matrix you essentially continue to exist, in some form, forever? What if it becomes possible to prevent your current physical body from aging/getting weaker? Medical AI could possibly improve the quality of the physical human experience too. The future is gonna be wild. ⚙️🔥</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/JTNYC2020"> /u/JTNYC2020 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171weez/the_unending_life/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171weez/the_unending_life/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172a0s4</id>
            <title>Looking for collections of (random) AI generated texts</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172a0s4/looking_for_collections_of_random_ai_generated/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_172a0s4</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T16:12:28+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: language analysis project, AI generated text, publicly available collections, generative AI tool
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章是一个关于寻找公开可用的、由人工智能生成的文本集合的项目。作者希望这些文本集合满足一些条件，比如没有人工干预、标记了生成AI工具的信息等。作者已经在GitHub和Kaggle上搜索过，但只找到了一些提示和示例。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello.</p> <p>For some language analysis project I am looking for publicly available collections of AI generated (longer) text. The topic of the texts does not matter. They should be:</p> <ul> <li>not being tempered with manually</li> <li>marked with what generative AI tool they have been generated (service, if possible version and date)</li> <li>if possible the prompt used</li> </ul> <p>Is anyone aware of such a collection. I have searched github and kaggle but could only find prompts and some examples. Thanks.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/LcuBeatsWorking"> /u/LcuBeatsWorking </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172a0s4/looking_for_collections_of_random_ai_generated/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/172a0s4/looking_for_collections_of_random_ai_generated/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17250q5</id>
            <title>Using an AI to generate Livestock breed/pedigree statistics</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17250q5/using_an_ai_to_generate_livestock_breedpedigree/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17250q5</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T12:17:29+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: cattle rancher, technology, breeding, Expected Progeny Differences (EPD)
<br>
<br>
总结: 这是一个关于一个简单的牛肉养殖者想要利用人工智能来生成自己的牛种血统的问题。他想要使用AI来破解算法并生成自己的EPDs，以便在交叉繁殖的牛市场上获得更准确的结果。他还考虑是否需要复制和粘贴整个血统数据来训练AI。他认为这个想法在纯种动物生产中会引起很大的兴趣。他想知道自己的想法是否现实。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I'm just a simple cattle rancher who knows a small bit about technology and recently got into breeding purebred</p> <p>They use an algorithmic equation to determine Expected Progeny Differences (EPD) to estimate what kind of performance their offspring would have like Birth weight, Calving ease, ribeye size, etc</p> <p>So to make a long question short is there an AI to scrape the website data of these animals to Crack the algorithm and use it to generate my own EPDs?</p> <p>The reason for this is I want to use AI to generate cross breed EPDs with as much accuracy as the registered purebred EPDs </p> <p>I've already tested it once on ChatGPT by putting in both parents EPD sets and compared the offspring to its results which were more inaccurate than I hoped for</p> <p>Or would I have to copy and paste an entire lineage of data to train an AI to be more accurate?</p> <p>One thing though to any AI developers out there looking for an idea this would turn a lot of interest in purebred animal production especially in the crossbreed cattle market </p> <p>Am I crazy or is what I want realistic right now</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/NMS_Survival_Guru"> /u/NMS_Survival_Guru </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17250q5/using_an_ai_to_generate_livestock_breedpedigree/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17250q5/using_an_ai_to_generate_livestock_breedpedigree/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171xopb</id>
            <title>One-Minute Daily AI News 10/6/2023</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171xopb/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1062023/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171xopb</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T04:51:48+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, Canva, Reka, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella, AI chips, Magic Studio, Yasa-1, multimodal AI assistant, Google's stranglehold on search
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI正在考虑制造自己的AI芯片；Canva发布了Magic Studio，这是一套基于AI的设计工具，旨在使内容创作对每个人都更加易于接触，无论其之前是否有设计经验；Reka是由DeepMind、Google和Meta的研究人员创立的AI初创公司，它宣布推出了Yasa-1，这是一款多模态AI助手，可以理解图像、短视频和音频片段；微软CEO Satya Nadella表示，AI只会加强Google在搜索领域的垄断地位。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><ol> <li>Exclusive: ChatGPT-owner <strong>OpenAI</strong> is exploring making its own AI chips.[1]</li> <li>As part of its 10th birthday celebrations, web-based design platform <strong>Canva</strong> is releasing Magic Studio — a new suite of AI-powered design tools that aim to make content creation more accessible to everyone, regardless of previous design experience.[2]</li> <li><strong>Reka</strong>, the AI startup founded by researchers from <strong>DeepMind</strong>, <strong>Google</strong> and <strong>Meta</strong>, has announced Yasa-1, a multimodal AI assistant that goes beyond text to understand images, short videos and audio snippets.[3]</li> <li><strong>Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella</strong> Says AI Could Only Tighten <strong>Google’s</strong> Stranglehold on Search.[4]</li> </ol> <p>Sources included at: <a href="https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/06/10-6-2023/">https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/06/10-6-2023/</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Excellent-Target-847"> /u/Excellent-Target-847 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171xopb/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1062023/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171xopb/oneminute_daily_ai_news_1062023/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171khik</id>
            <title>AI Is The Top Investment Priority for 72% of CEOs</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171khik/ai_is_the_top_investment_priority_for_72_of_ceos/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_171khik</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-06T18:52:43+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI investments, generative AI, risks, CEO excitement
<br>
<br>
总结: 一项新的KPMG调查显示，CEO对于AI投资感到兴奋，但对风险感到担忧。72%的CEO将生成式AI视为他们的首要投资重点。然而，实施AI所面临的伦理挑战是最大的关注点之一。此外，85%的CEO认为AI对于网络安全是一把双刃剑。尽管AI被视为具有变革性的技术，但工人被取代和社会影响仍然是一个重要问题。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>A new KPMG survey shows CEO excitement about AI investments, but apprehension around risks persists. (<a href="https://decrypt.co/200400/72-of-ceos-consider-generative-ai-a-top-investment-priority-kpmg">Source</a>)</p> <p>If you want the latest AI updates before anyone else, <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">look here first</a></p> <p><strong>All In on AI</strong></p> <ul> <li>72% call generative AI their top investment priority.</li> <li>57% spend more on technology than reskilling workers.</li> <li>62% expect ROI in 3-5 years, showing a long-term outlook.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Persistent Worries</strong></p> <ul> <li>The top concern is the ethical challenges of implementing AI.</li> <li>85% see AI as a double-edged sword for cybersecurity.</li> <li>81% say the regulatory gap is a hindrance.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Uncertain Future</strong></p> <ul> <li>AI is seen as transformative, not a passing fad.</li> <li>But worker displacement and social impacts loom large.</li> <li>The rules around generative AI remain unsettled.</li> </ul> <p><strong>PS:</strong> Get the latest <strong>AI developments, tools, and use cases</strong> by joining one of the fastest-growing AI newsletters. Join <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">5000+ professionals getting smarter in AI.</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Ok-Feeling-1743"> /u/Ok-Feeling-1743 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171khik/ai_is_the_top_investment_priority_for_72_of_ceos/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/171khik/ai_is_the_top_investment_priority_for_72_of_ceos/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1724f4s</id>
            <title>How do you post an AI cover on Tiktok without it getting copyright striked and muted?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1724f4s/how_do_you_post_an_ai_cover_on_tiktok_without_it/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1724f4s</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T11:44:58+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Tiktok, AI covers, The Summoning, Sleep Token
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人在Tiktok上发布了使用AI制作的Sleep Token乐队的歌曲《The Summoning》的翻唱视频，但每次发布都因版权问题被静音。是否有办法在不更换声音的情况下防止这种情况发生？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I see people on Tiktok posting AI covers of the song The Summoning by Sleep Token. I did the same using a Cammy White (Street Fighter character) AI voice model but everytime I do so, it always gets muted due to copyright strike? Is there a way to prevent that without replacing a sound?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/infiniteplusultra"> /u/infiniteplusultra </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1724f4s/how_do_you_post_an_ai_cover_on_tiktok_without_it/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1724f4s/how_do_you_post_an_ai_cover_on_tiktok_without_it/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1723ldl</id>
            <title>When using GPT’s function calling, are the words specified in the `properties` parameter under `functions` counted as input tokens?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1723ldl/when_using_gpts_function_calling_are_the_words/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1723ldl</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-07T10:57:12+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: 提取出来的关键词, 使用逗号分割
<br>
<br>
总结: 中文概括

关键词: student_custom_functions, extract_student_info, parameters, function_call
<br>
<br>
总结: 该文本讨论了在使用GPT函数调用时，是否将函数参数中的单词计算为输入标记。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Example: ``` student_custom_functions = [ { 'name': 'extract_student_info', 'description': 'Get the student information from the body of the input text', 'parameters': { 'type': 'object', 'properties': { 'name': { 'type': 'string', 'description': 'Name of the person' }, 'major': { 'type': 'string', 'description': 'Major subject.' }, 'school': { 'type': 'string', 'description': 'The university name.' }, 'grades': { 'type': 'integer', 'description': 'GPA of the student.' }, 'club': { 'type': 'string', 'description': 'School club for extracurricular activities. ' }</p> <pre><code> } } } </code></pre> <p>] ```</p> <p>``` student_description = [student_1_description,student_2_description] for sample in student_description: response = openai.ChatCompletion.create( model = 'gpt-3.5-turbo', messages = [{'role': 'user', 'content': sample}], functions = student_custom_functions, function_call = 'auto' )</p> <pre><code># Loading the response as a JSON object json_response = json.loads(response['choices'][0]['message']['function_call']['arguments']) print(json_response) </code></pre> <p>```</p> <p>Are the words specified in the <code>properties</code> parameter under <code>functions</code> in the above GPT function calling counted as input tokens?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/redd-dev"> /u/redd-dev </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1723ldl/when_using_gpts_function_calling_are_the_words/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1723ldl/when_using_gpts_function_calling_are_the_words/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>