<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence Gateway</title>
        <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/</link>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</id>
            <title>Important: Request For Comments regarding subreddit rules and future direction. Please Read!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-01-15T20:24:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: r/ArtificialIntelligence, philosophical and ethical discussions, technical paper presentations, AI/ML applications
<br>
<br>
总结: 欢迎来到r/ArtificialIntelligence！我们的目标是为所有与人工智能相关的事物提供一个开放和尊重的论坛，包括促进关于人工智能的哲学和伦理讨论，作为了解和学习人工智能主题的起点，提供技术论文的展示和讨论，展示高质量的人工智能/机器学习应用，提供培训和学习资源，引导用户获取更具体的信息和子论坛，列出人工智能/机器学习应用、使用、成本和访问信息，以及其他与人工智能相关的内容。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Welcome to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialIntelligence">r/ArtificialIntelligence</a>!</p> <p>Our goal is to provide an open and respectful forum for all things considered Artificial Intelligence - this includes</p> <ul> <li>Facilitate philosophical and ethical discussions about AI</li> <li>Serve as a starting point for understanding and learning about AI topics</li> <li>Offer technical paper presentations and discussions</li> <li>Present quality AI/ML applications</li> <li>Provide training and learning resources</li> <li>Direct users to more specific information and subreddits</li> <li>List AI/ML applications, their uses, costs, and access information</li> <li>Additional AI-related content.</li> <li>...and more</li> </ul> <p>The moderation team for this sub is going through a reshuffle which will result in some changes to the sub. However, there is no need to worry as these changes will primarily focus on improving organization, resources, and pre-prepared content. To ensure that the community is fully informed and able to provide feedback, multiple opportunities will be given for feedback on the changes.</p> <p>The first round of feedback gathering is through this thread as a &quot;Request-For-Comments&quot; (RFC), which is a standard method of gathering feedback. There will be multiple rounds of the RFC process as the changes are prepared and implemented.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <ul> <li>Rules on posting new applications / self-promotion / AI generated content <ul> <li>Posts that are applications consisting of a ChatGPT-api &quot;skin&quot; or similar will be prevented or confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>AI generated content specific to the arts (writing, visual arts, music) require flair, or will be confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>Blog links should consist of high-quality content. Posts that link to blogs that are purely promotional will be removed.</li> <li>Posts with just links will be prohibited unless there is a certain word count of detail included. Some effort must be put in.</li> <li>Should we prevent posts that are written by AI? There exist models that could be used in a Mod-bot, but this is a question we need feedback on.</li> </ul></li> <li>Use of flair in order to organize posts. Note that new flair has been added already, we are open to more suggestions.</li> <li>What should the sub policy on NSFW applications and techniques in regards to AI/ML application?</li> <li>We would like to include the community with ideas for mod-bots. While some standard bots will be used for basic maintenance, but what interesting things can the community come up with for AI/ML bot functions?</li> <li>Cultivating beginner, intermediate, and advanced resources to assist people in finding information, training, models, technical data, etc. that they are looking for</li> <li>Starting substack/podcast to interview people throughout the AI/ML spectrum. This could include philosophers and thinkers, programmers, scientists, business people, even those with antithetical views on AI</li> <li> If you would like to create banners that represent the sub, please do so with the appropriate size. Any method of creation is acceptable.</li> </ul> <p>It should go without saying that everyone should be treated with respect. I personally feel that we all know this and it doesn't need to be hammered into people’s heads. Be nice.</p> <p>Thank you for your patience and assistance!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</id>
            <title>New Anti-Spam / Bot Rules [Please Read]</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-02-18T16:49:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: rule, accounts, bot spam, poll
<br>
<br>
总结: 为了解决机器人垃圾信息的问题，我们制定了一项规定，即账户注册不满一天或者声望低于100的用户不能发布帖子，但可以发表评论。我们计划在接下来的几天内进行一次投票，以了解用户对该子论坛的意愿和改进方向。如果您有任何反馈或者有兴趣帮助该子论坛，请与我联系。感谢大家的支持！ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We have instituted a rule where accounts newer than a day or users with less than 100 karma cannot post. They can post comments but not submit actual posts. This is part of our plan to address bot spam. Apologies for any inconvenience.</p> <p>We will be conducting a poll in the next few days to get the general will of the subreddit and how to improve forward, just a heads up.</p> <p>As always, please give us feedback and if you are interested in helping out the sub, please contact me. </p> <p>Thanks everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177wokb</id>
            <title>First-ever dual-degree program in medicine and AI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177wokb/firstever_dualdegree_program_in_medicine_and_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177wokb</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T19:11:07+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: program, doctors, AI, healthcare's tech revolution
<br>
<br>
总结: 这个首创性的项目将培养出同时具备医学和人工智能认证的医生，旨在引领医疗保健技术革命。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>A first-of-its-kind program will graduate doctors also certified in AI, aiming to lead healthcare's tech revolution. (<a href="https://fortune.com/education/articles/university-of-texas-san-antonio-dual-degree-medicine-artifical-intelligence-ai/">Source</a>)</p> <p>If you want the latest AI updates before anyone else, <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">look here first</a></p> <p><strong>Bridging Two Fields</strong></p> <ul> <li>5-year MD/MS in AI program at UT Health and UT San Antonio.</li> <li>Students get AI master's degree in gap year from med school.</li> <li>Goal is physicians adept in AI deployment for care.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Real-World AI Skills</strong></p> <ul> <li>Curriculum goes beyond concepts to application.</li> <li>Project-based learning to use AI in clinical settings.</li> <li>Tailored concentrations from data analytics to robotics.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Transforming, Not Replacing</strong></p> <ul> <li>Program sees AI as enhancing, not displacing doctors.</li> <li>Emphasizes personalized, human-centered approach.</li> <li>Graduates poised to shape AI's role in medicine.</li> </ul> <p><strong>PS:</strong> Get the latest <strong>AI developments, tools, and use cases</strong> by joining one of the fastest-growing AI newsletters. Join <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">5000+ professionals getting smarter in AI.</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Ok-Feeling-1743"> /u/Ok-Feeling-1743 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177wokb/firstever_dualdegree_program_in_medicine_and_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177wokb/firstever_dualdegree_program_in_medicine_and_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ubfo</id>
            <title>Unlocking the power of Sparsity in Generative Models: 8x Faster LLMs on CPUs with Sparse Fine Tuning</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ubfo/unlocking_the_power_of_sparsity_in_generative/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ubfo</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T17:17:19+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Neural Magic, IST Austria, Sparse Finetuning, Large Language Models
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇研究论文介绍了Neural Magic和IST Austria合作的最新成果，通过稀疏微调技术在大型语言模型中实现了推理加速。研究结果表明，稀疏模型在减小体积、提高速度、降低成本和环境友好方面具有巨大潜力。通过与最新的量化技术相结合，这些稀疏模型在CPU上的推理速度提高了8倍。研究重点在于通过下游数据集微调模型，采用了一种基于L2的逐层蒸馏方法，名为SquareHead。这些创新技术使得可以在保持99%基线密集模型性能的同时，去除75%的权重。该研究和相关模型已开源并可供广泛使用。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>The latest research paper between Neural Magic and IST Austria has just landed on Arxiv: <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2310.06927">Sparse Finetuning for Inference Acceleration of Large Language Models</a>! In the paper, we pushed the bounds of what's possible for sparsity within generative AI models and LLMs. The result is smaller, faster, cheaper, and more environmentally friendly deployments. </p> <p>Our state-of-the-art research has moved the needle for compression and performance on generative models, including 75% sparse MPT models with negligible accuracy loss and sparse T5 and Whisper models that improve recovery levels. </p> <p>When paired with the latest quantization techniques, these sparse models achieve an 8x acceleration for inferencing on CPUs. 8 tokens/second on just 1 CPU core and 27 tokens/second on a 4-core AMD Ryzen CPU!<br /> We focused on pruning while fine-tuning models on downstream datasets to enable these sparsity levels, employing an L2-based layerwise distillation method called SquareHead. With these innovative techniques, we can remove 75% of the weights (attention and fully connected layers) while maintaining 99% of the baseline dense model's performance. </p> <p>You can dive into all the details on our <a href="https://research.neuralmagic.com/mpt-sparse-finetuning">Project Page</a> or try it out with our live demo on <a href="https://huggingface.co/spaces/neuralmagic/sparse-mpt-7b-gsm8k">HuggingFace Spaces</a>. This research and associated models are open-sourced and available for general use!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/markurtz"> /u/markurtz </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ubfo/unlocking_the_power_of_sparsity_in_generative/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ubfo/unlocking_the_power_of_sparsity_in_generative/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177u8t9</id>
            <title>AI Weekly Rundown (October 7 to October 13)</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177u8t9/ai_weekly_rundown_october_7_to_october_13/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177u8t9</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T17:13:52+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, GPT-4 Vision, LLaVA-1.5, FreshPrompt
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI和其他公司发布了一系列重要的人工智能（AI）相关的公告。其中包括了GPT-4 Vision可能面临的新竞争对手LLaVA-1.5，它是一个开源且完全免费的模型，通过对原始LLaVA模型进行简单修改，在11个基准测试中取得了最先进的结果。另外，谷歌、OpenAI和马萨诸塞大学的新研究提出了FreshPrompt，这是一种简单的几次提示方法，可以将从搜索引擎中检索到的相关和最新信息合并到模型中，从而显著提高了LLM的性能。此外，微软计划在下个月的开发者大会上推出首款专为人工智能设计的芯片，这将有助于减少对Nvidia设计的人工智能芯片的依赖。最后，Adobe宣布推出了三个新的AI模型，进一步深入AI领域。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Major AI announcements from OpenAI, Google, Adobe, Microsoft and more. </p> <ul> <li><strong>GPT-4 Vision might have a new competitor, LLaVA-1.5</strong><br /> - LLaVA-1.5 is open-source and completely free to use. It achieves SoTA on 11 benchmarks, with simple modifications to the original LLaVA.<br /> - It utilizes merely 1.2M public data, trains in ~1 day on a single 8-A100 node, and surpasses billion-scale data methods. And it might just be as good as GPT-4V in responses.</li> <li><strong>Perplexity and GPT-4 with a new prompting mechanism outperform Google Search</strong><br /> - New research by Google, OpenAI, and the University of Massachusetts presents FreshPrompt. It is a simple few-shot prompting method that substantially boosts the performance of an LLM by incorporating relevant and up-to-date information retrieved from a search engine into the prompt. </li> <li><strong>Microsoft to debut AI Chip</strong><br /> - The company plans to unveil its first chip designed for AI at its annual developers’ conference next month. The move, a culmination of years of work, could help it lessen reliance on Nvidia-designed AI chips, which have been in short supply as demand for them has boomed.</li> <li><strong>Anthropic’s breakthrough makes AI more understandable</strong><br /> - It developed a new method to interpret the individual neurons inside LLMs like Claude, helping researchers better understand and decode the model’s reasoning. The method decomposes groups of neurons into simpler &quot;features&quot; with clearer meanings.</li> <li><strong>Google Cloud introduced new Vertex AI Search features for healthcare and life science companies</strong><br /> - It will help users find relevant information over broader data types. Building on the tool’s current ability to search many different kinds of documents and other data sources, the new capabilities will help find accurate clinical information more efficiently.</li> <li><strong>SAP unveils new generative AI innovations that boost productivity and effectiveness in spend management</strong><br /> - It announced new business AI and user experience innovations in its comprehensive spend management and business network solutions to help customers control costs, mitigate risk, and increase productivity.</li> <li><strong>Dropbox’s newly launched AI tools and product updates</strong><br /> - Dropbox Dash: An AI-powered universal search that connects your tools, content, and apps in a single search bar. Ask Dash questions; it will gather and summarize information across your apps, files, and content to get you answers quickly.<br /> - Dropbox AI: It will answer questions about content from your entire Dropbox account. You can even use everyday language to find the content you need. Example: say, “What are the deliverables from our Q4 campaign?” and Dropbox AI will retrieve the content you need. </li> <li><strong>Adobe Immerses Itself in AI, announcing 3 new gen AI models</strong><br /> - Firefly Image 2 Model: It is the company's take on text-to-image generators, The major perk is the increased quality of renditions, higher resolutions, more vivid colors, and improved human renderings.<br /> - Firefly Vector Model: With this brand-new addition, Users can leverage gen AI and use a simple prompt to create &quot;human quality&quot; vectors and pattern outputs.<br /> - Firefly Design Model: It has text-to-template capability, allowing users to use text to generate fully editable templates that meet their design needs.</li> <li><strong>Docker’s new AI solutions for developers</strong><br /> - GenAI Stack: An AI platform that helps developers create AI applications.<br /> - Docker AI assistant: It helps deploy and optimize Docker itself. </li> <li><strong>ElevenLab have launched AI dubbing</strong><br /> - With the aim to break down language barriers, It converts spoken content to other languages in minutes while preserving all of the original voices.<br /> - 20+ languages, Automatic detection of multiple speakers, Background sounds &amp; noise splitting, and more.</li> <li><strong>Tesla builds a Bunker-like structure in Texas to house Its &quot;Dojo&quot; Supercomputer</strong><br /> - Sparked rumors that it could be used for housing operations for Tesla's Dojo supercomputing cluster.<br /> - The Dojo cluster trains the company's AI neural network for its Full Self-Driving system. - However, it is unclear if the claims are true, as there have been no permits or plans for a Dojo center at the facility. </li> <li><strong>Replit AI is now available for all developers</strong><br /> - With code completion and assistance enabled by default. Free users will access basic AI features, while Pro users will have exclusive access to more powerful models and advanced features. The team has trained low-latency LLMs to handle Replit's compute-heavy AI workloads.<br /> - They are releasing a state-of-the-art 3B LLM called replit-code-v1.5-3b, and its now available on Hugging Face. </li> <li><strong>OpenAI plans major updates for developers to build lower costs applications</strong><br /> - According to sources, The updates will enable developers to build software apps cheaper &amp; faster. These updates will be announced at OpenAI's first-ever developer conference in November.<br /> - The updates include adding memory storage to its developer tools for using AI models. This could theoretically cut costs for 20-times.<br /> - They also plan to launch new tools, such as vision capabilities, to enable developers to build applications that can analyze images and describe them.</li> <li><strong>OpenAI reveals how it develops models like GPT-4</strong><br /> - If you're looking for a simple, straightforward breakdown of how and what goes on at OpenAI, an explainer has been revealed by the maker of ChatGPT. OpenAI explains how it develops its foundation models, makes them safer, and more.</li> <li><strong>Google SGE can now generate images and drafts</strong><br /> - Google brings new capabilities to its AI-powered Search experience (SGE).<br /> 1) Now, SGE can whip up images from the description you type in search, and you can also edit them by changing the description.<br /> 2) To avoid longer-running searches for ideas and inspirations, SGE will write drafts for you and shorten them or change the tone.</li> <li><strong>New AI tool can predict viral variants before they emerge</strong><br /> - A new AI tool named EVEscape, developed by researchers at Harvard Medical School and the University of Oxford, can predict new viral variants before they emerge. The information will help scientists develop more effective, future-proof vaccines and therapies.</li> <li>And there was more… <ul> <li><strong>ChatGPT’s mobile app hit a record $4.58M in revenue last month, but growth is slowing</strong><br /> - This gross revenue is across its iOS and Android apps worldwide. But while it was topping 31% in July and 39% in August, that dropped to 20% growth as of September.</li> <li><strong>Lambda Labs, AWS’s competitor, nears $300M funding</strong><br /> - Like AWS, it rents out servers with Nvidia chips to AI developers and is nearing a $300M equity financing. As demand for Nvidia’s AI chips has skyrocketed this year, revenue at startups such as Lambda has boomed, attracting investors.</li> <li><strong>Microsoft’s new data and AI solutions to help healthcare organizations improve patient and clinician experiences</strong><br /> - Microsoft's new solutions offer a unified and responsible approach to data and AI, enabling healthcare organizations to deliver quality care more efficiently and at a lower cost.</li> <li><strong>Samsung Electronics plans to launch its 6th-gen High Bandwidth Memory4 (HBM4) DRAM chips</strong><br /> - The company aims to lead the AI chip market with its turnkey service, which includes foundry, memory chip supplies, advanced packaging, and testing.</li> <li><strong>Google AI helps combat floods, wildfires, and extreme heat</strong><br /> - Google’s flood forecasting initiative uses AI and geospatial analysis to provide real-time flooding information, covering 80 countries and 460 million people.<br /> - They’re also using AI to track wildfire boundaries and predict fire spread, providing timely safety information to over 30 million people. </li> <li><strong>Adobe created a symbol to encourage the tagging of AI-generated content</strong><br /> - Its the &quot;icon of transparency&quot; will be adopted by reputed companies like Microsoft. The symbol will be added to the metadata of images, videos, and PDFs, allowing viewers to hover over it and access information about ownership, the AI tool used, and other production details.<br /> - This initiative aims to provide transparency in AI-generated work and ensure proper credit is given to creators.</li> <li><strong>AMD plans to acquire AI software startup Nod.ai to rival chipmaker Nvidia</strong><br /> - The acquisition will help AMD boost its software capabilities and develop a unified collection of software to power its advanced AI chips. Nod.ai's technology enables companies to deploy AI models tuned for AMD's chips more easily.<br /> - The terms of the deal were not disclosed, but Nod.ai has raised approximately $36.5 million in funding.</li> <li><strong>BBC blocked OpenAI data scraping but is open to AI-powered journalism</strong><br /> - It has blocked web crawlers from OpenAI and Common Crawl from accessing BBC websites. But it plans to work with tech companies, other media organizations, and regulators to develop generative AI safely.</li> <li><strong>The U.N. and Netherlands launched a project to help Europe prepare for AI supervision</strong><br /> - UNESCO will assemble information about how European countries supervise AI and a list of “best practices” recommendations, aided by the Dutch digital infrastructure agency (RDI).</li> <li><strong>Snoop Dogg joins the AI arms race, invests in AI language startup THINKIN</strong><br /> - Built upon OpenAI's GPT technology, THINKIN's AI is carefully customized and fine-tuned to teach foreign languages.</li> <li><strong>Scientists achieve 70% accuracy in AI-driven earthquake predictions</strong><br /> - An AI tool predicted earthquakes with 70% accuracy a week in advance, as observed during a 7-month trial in China. Based on its analysis, the tool successfully anticipated 14 earthquakes. This experiment was conducted by researchers from The University of Texas (UT) in Austin, USA.</li> <li><strong>Mendel launches AI-Copilot for real-world data applications in healthcare</strong><br /> - Called Hypercube, it enables life sciences and healthcare enterprises to interrogate their troves of patient data in natural language through a chat-like experience. It can deliver blazing-fast insights and answer previously unanswerable questions.</li> <li><strong>AI drones successfully monitor crops to report the ideal time to harvest</strong><br /> - For the first time, researchers have demonstrated a largely automated system that heavily uses drones and AI to improve crop yields. It carefully and accurately analyzes individual crops to assess their likely growth characteristics.</li> <li><strong>Video editing startup Captions has launched a new free app called Lipdub</strong><br /> - It translates videos into 28 different languages and offers translations into unique styles such as Texas slang, Gen Z, pirate, and baby talk.<br /> - Users can translate up to 1 minute of video and share it on social media platforms. </li> <li><strong>Klarna has launched an AI image-search tool ‘Shopping lens’</strong><br /> - It allows users to take a picture of items and quickly find out where to buy them, with the ability to compare prices, retailers, and reviews. It has also introduced shoppable videos, in-store product scanning, and more. </li> <li><strong>Microsoft Limits Bing's Image-Generating AI</strong><br /> - Microsoft has now tightened its grip on the image generator, and blocked certain keywords, but workarounds were easy. Banned terrorism-related language and other potentially problematic keywords.</li> <li><strong>Box, a cloud-based content management company, has launched Hubs</strong><br /> - AI-focused solution to help employees find the information they need. Hubs allow users to organize documents, quickly find answers to important questions, summarize large amounts of information, and create new content more easily. </li> <li><strong>Character.AI introduces character group chat</strong><br /> - This feature allows users to create group chats with multiple AI characters and their friends. Users can create social connections, share ideas, and collaborate.<br /> - The feature is currently available to c.ai+ subscribers and will later be available to the general public.</li> <li><strong>Microsoft's Paint Cocreator begins rolling out to Windows Insiders in the Beta Channel</strong><br /> - It is a new AI-powered experience powered by DALL-E that helps you create amazing artwork in Paint by describing what you’d like to create in a few words.</li> <li><strong>Lakera launches to protect LLMs from malicious prompts</strong><br /> - With $10M in backing, the Swiss startup launches API to protect companies from prompt injections and more.</li> <li><strong>Llama models have been downloaded 32M+ times in the last 30 days</strong><br /> - The leaderboards at Hugging Face show that open source is more vibrant than ever, with downloads and model submissions rocketing to record highs.</li> <li><strong>OpenAI’s revenue is on pace to reach $1.3 billion a year</strong><br /> - This remark by CEO Sam Altman indicates the company is generating more than $100 million per month, up 30% from this summer, when it generated revenue at a $1 billion-a-year pace.</li> <li><strong>Google to defend generative AI users from copyright claims</strong><br /> - It has pledged to protect users of its generative AI systems on Google Cloud and Workspace platforms against accusations of intellectual property violations.<br /> - The move aligns it with tech giants like Microsoft &amp; Adobe with similar pledges.</li> </ul></li> </ul> <p>More detailed breakdown of these news and innovations is in the <a href="https://theaiedge.substack.com/p/ai-weekly-rundown-october-7-to-13">weekly newsletter</a>.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/RohitAkki"> /u/RohitAkki </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177u8t9/ai_weekly_rundown_october_7_to_october_13/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177u8t9/ai_weekly_rundown_october_7_to_october_13/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177q03h</id>
            <title>Asking for Resources for learning practical ML ,after doing some theoretical courses on ML.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177q03h/asking_for_resources_for_learning_practical_ml/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177q03h</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T13:50:15+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: ML, theory courses, implementation, Kaggle, technique, hyper-parameter tuning, CNN designing, B tech Cse
<br>
<br>
总结: 这位学生在学习机器学习方面遇到了一些问题。他参加了一些理论课程，但感觉缺乏实践。他想知道如何开始实践，并寻找关于技术选择、超参数调整、CNN设计等方面的好的课程或书籍。他目前是印度的计算机科学与工程专业的大二学生。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>i have been doing some nptel courses on ML , they were 90% theory courses (they did show the codes for some stuff , but i felt it was not necssary for the course ). I do know that i should move towards implementation , but idk where to start .</p> <p>Its not like i remember everything from the theory , but now i feel i should go towards Kaggle or something , is there any good course or book or anything for choosing what technique ,hyper-parameter tuning , CNN designing and such stuff</p> <p>Currently doing B tech Cse (cse engineering in India). 2nd year</p> <p>courses -</p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23%5C_cs97/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23\_cs97/preview</a> (DS , ended last month)</p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23%5C_cs98/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23\_cs98/preview</a> (ML, will end this month)</p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23%5C_cs110/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23\_cs110/preview</a> (DL , will end this month)</p> <p>i also did half a course on RL (i left it midway)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Relevant-Ad9432"> /u/Relevant-Ad9432 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177q03h/asking_for_resources_for_learning_practical_ml/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177q03h/asking_for_resources_for_learning_practical_ml/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177hsm2</id>
            <title>Mathematical Theory of Artificial Intelligence</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177hsm2/mathematical_theory_of_artificial_intelligence/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177hsm2</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T04:56:02+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: background, applied mathematics, AI, resources
<br>
<br>
总结: 提问者具有应用数学背景，但对人工智能没有了解，想知道从哪里开始学习，并希望得到一些学习资源的推荐。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi all, I have a background in applied mathematics, bur I have no knowhow of AI. Where could I start? Could you recommend some resources? Thank you.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/mbence111"> /u/mbence111 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177hsm2/mathematical_theory_of_artificial_intelligence/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177hsm2/mathematical_theory_of_artificial_intelligence/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177928a</id>
            <title>How far are we with voice conversation AI?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177928a/how_far_are_we_with_voice_conversation_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177928a</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T21:21:01+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: solution, voice conversation, AI, natural
<br>
<br>
总结: 如今，我在车上花费大量时间，希望能够在开车时进行研究，我发现与AI进行对话似乎是可行的。然而，我尝试过的应用程序在处理和回复方面非常笨拙和缓慢。目前，哪个应用程序给人最自然的感觉？从技术角度来看，它们的改进速度如何？最大的障碍是什么？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>What is the best solution to have a voice conversation with an AI now? I spend a lot of time in the car and would love to be able to research things while I drive, and I found that having a conversation about it with an AI kind of works. However, the app I've tried is super clumsy and slow at processing and replying.</p> <p>What is the one that feels the most natural right now?</p> <p>From a technical perspective, how quickly are they improving? What are the biggest hurdles?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FlyingJoeBiden"> /u/FlyingJoeBiden </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177928a/how_far_are_we_with_voice_conversation_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177928a/how_far_are_we_with_voice_conversation_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177pyiz</id>
            <title>what now after learning theoretical ML</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pyiz/what_now_after_learning_theoretical_ml/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177pyiz</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T13:48:04+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: ML, theory courses, implementation, Kaggle, technique, hyper-parameter tuning, CNN designing, B tech Cse
<br>
<br>
总结: 这位学生在学习了一些关于机器学习的理论课程后，意识到需要开始实践，但不知道从何处开始。他希望能找到一些关于选择技术、超参数调整、CNN设计等方面的好的课程或书籍，同时他也提到了自己正在进行的学习和他的背景。他还提到了一些之前学习过的课程和他对强化学习的一些了解。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>i have been doing some nptel courses on ML , they were 90% theory courses (they did show the codes for some stuff , but i felt it was not necssary for the course ). I do know that i should move towards implementation , but idk where to start . </p> <p>Its not like i remember everything from the theory , but now i feel i should go towards Kaggle or something , is there any good course or book or anything for choosing what technique ,hyper-parameter tuning , CNN designing and such stuff</p> <p>Currently doing B tech Cse (cse engineering in India). 2nd year</p> <p>courses - </p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs97/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs97/preview</a> (DS , ended last month)</p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs98/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs98/preview</a> (ML, will end this month)</p> <p><a href="https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs110/preview">https://onlinecourses.nptel.ac.in/noc23_cs110/preview</a> (DL , will end this month)</p> <p>i also did half a course on RL (i left it midway) </p> <p>&#x200b;</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Relevant-Ad9432"> /u/Relevant-Ad9432 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pyiz/what_now_after_learning_theoretical_ml/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pyiz/what_now_after_learning_theoretical_ml/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177pa43</id>
            <title>Video upload to AI modification?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pa43/video_upload_to_ai_modification/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177pa43</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T13:13:13+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Kaiber, 视频转换, 帧率, 质量
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人使用Kaiber将上传的视频转换成其他形式，比如将一个城镇中的人变成了一个赛博朋克城市。我在Reddit上看到一些视频，但在Kaiber上没有看到相同水平的帧率和质量。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Has anyone had experience of using Kaiber to convert an uploaded video into something else, eg a person in a town that is turned into a cyberpunk city? I’ve seen some videos on Reddit but I’m not seeing the same level of frame rate and quality on Kaiber. </p> <p>Thanks.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Mr_Pods"> /u/Mr_Pods </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pa43/video_upload_to_ai_modification/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177pa43/video_upload_to_ai_modification/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177oaqk</id>
            <title>AI Music Lyrics transcription</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177oaqk/ai_music_lyrics_transcription/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177oaqk</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T12:20:47+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI工具, 歌词转录, Moises app, 音乐
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人知道除了Moises app之外，还有没有一个可以将歌曲的歌词转录出来的好的AI工具吗？不需要将人声与乐器分离。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Does anyone know a good AI tool that can transcribe Lyrics form a song (without the need to isolate the vocals from the instruments) apart from the Moises app?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/TsunNekoKucing"> /u/TsunNekoKucing </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177oaqk/ai_music_lyrics_transcription/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177oaqk/ai_music_lyrics_transcription/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177kecr</id>
            <title>Need a website for presentations</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kecr/need_a_website_for_presentations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177kecr</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T07:56:00+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: websites, presentations, topics, AI
<br>
<br>
总结: 作者在寻找一些能够利用AI制作特定主题演示文稿的好网站，希望能够将自己想要的信息输入到AI中，并且希望这些网站是免费的。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi everyone. Do you know some good websites to make presentations on certain topics with AI? I would like to feed the AI with the information I want it to put in the presentation. If you know some, let me know. (free = better)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/K3vl4r_"> /u/K3vl4r_ </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kecr/need_a_website_for_presentations/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kecr/need_a_website_for_presentations/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ngy6</id>
            <title>AI conference happening in San Francisco: 100% off on the ticket price!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ngy6/ai_conference_happening_in_san_francisco_100_off/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ngy6</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T11:31:47+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: database company, Data and AI conference, San Francisco, discount coupon code
<br>
<br>
总结: SingleStore是一家数据库公司，他们将在2023年10月17日在旧金山举办一场数据和人工智能会议。这是一场线下会议，有许多优秀的演讲嘉宾，如LangChain的联合创始人兼首席执行官Harrison Chase等。会议将提供实践工作坊、赠品等活动。如果你在旧金山附近，这可能是一个与行业领导者见面和与其他数据工程师建立联系的好机会。使用我的折扣优惠码'PAVAN100OFF'可享受100%的门票折扣（原价为199美元）。立即<a href="https://singlestore.com/now">购买门票！</a>使用'PAVAN100OFF'优惠码。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I work for this database company SingleStore and we are hosting a Data and AI conference in San Francisco on 17th of October, 2023.<br /> It is an in-person conference with amazing speakers line-up like Harrison Chase, co-founder and CEO of LangChain and many more. We will have hands-on workshops, swags giveaway and much more.<br /> I don't know if it makes sense to share this but I believe it might help some of you near San Francisco to go and meet the industry leaders and network with other data engineering folks.<br /> Use my discount coupon code 'PAVAN100OFF' to avail 100% off on the ticket price. (the original ticket price is $199)</p> <p><a href="https://singlestore.com/now">Get your tickets now!</a> using 'PAVAN100OFF' discount code. </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/PavanBelagatti"> /u/PavanBelagatti </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ngy6/ai_conference_happening_in_san_francisco_100_off/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ngy6/ai_conference_happening_in_san_francisco_100_off/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177lt5t</id>
            <title>Need advice as to which ML/DL model to use for a project</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt5t/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177lt5t</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T09:39:45+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: 3 seperate data, composite value, linear regression model, neural network like RNN
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了作者在使用3个不同的数据来输出一个复合值时遇到的困惑。作者想知道在这种情况下应该选择哪种模型，是线性回归模型还是像RNN这样的神经网络模型更适合。作者希望了解哪种模型在一般情况下是最好或最准确的。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I need to use 3 seperate data to output a composite value. This data is all numerical. I am confused which model I should use to do it. If I choose a linear regression model, I have the data available to train and then to use that, or maybe a neural network like RNN would be better suited for this. Which in general is the best or most accurate model to use for my case.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p>Feel free to post any questions you have so I can explain my case in more detail to help your understanding</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Any_Dot8196"> /u/Any_Dot8196 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt5t/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt5t/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177lt4o</id>
            <title>Need advice as to which ML/DL model to use for a project</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt4o/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177lt4o</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T09:39:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: 3 seperate data, composite value, linear regression model, neural network like RNN
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了作者在使用3个不同的数据来输出一个复合值时遇到的困惑。作者不确定应该选择哪种模型来完成这个任务，是线性回归模型还是像RNN这样的神经网络模型更适合。作者想知道在这种情况下，哪种模型是最好或最准确的。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I need to use 3 seperate data to output a composite value. This data is all numerical. I am confused which model I should use to do it. If I choose a linear regression model, I have the data available to train and then to use that, or maybe a neural network like RNN would be better suited for this. Which in general is the best or most accurate model to use for my case.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p>Feel free to post any questions you have so I can explain my case in more detail to help your understanding</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Any_Dot8196"> /u/Any_Dot8196 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt4o/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177lt4o/need_advice_as_to_which_mldl_model_to_use_for_a/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177gad9</id>
            <title>Seeking a Community for Open-Source AI Code Generation Models</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177gad9/seeking_a_community_for_opensource_ai_code/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177gad9</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T03:23:27+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI code generation, communities, platforms, open-source models
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了作者对于开源AI代码生成模型的探索，并询问是否有专门致力于开源AI代码生成模型的社区或平台。作者希望找到一个可以让爱好者和专家共同合作、分享见解、改进现有模型的空间；一个可以讨论AI代码生成中的挑战、突破和最佳实践的论坛或聊天平台；一个可以自由共享和获取开源模型、数据集和相关工具的仓库或平台；以及任何可以帮助新手理解AI代码生成概念和复杂性的资源。如果你知道这样的社区或者是其中的一员，请告诉我。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello everyone! 🌟<br /> I hope this post finds you well. I've been delving deeper into the world of AI code generation recently and am curious to discover if there are communities or platforms specifically dedicated to open-source AI code generation models. I'm aware of hugging face but is there any other besides that.<br /> Here's what I'm looking for:<br /> 1. Collaboration: A space where enthusiasts and experts alike can collaborate on projects, share insights, and improve upon existing models.<br /> 2. Discussion: Forums or chat platforms where discussions around the challenges, breakthroughs, and best practices in AI code generation take place.<br /> 3. Resource Sharing: A repository or platform where open-source models, datasets, and related tools can be freely shared and accessed.<br /> 4. Learning and Tutorials: Any resources that can help newcomers grasp the concepts and intricacies of AI code generation.<br /> If you know of any such community or are part of one, please do let me know.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/akanshtyagi"> /u/akanshtyagi </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177gad9/seeking_a_community_for_opensource_ai_code/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177gad9/seeking_a_community_for_opensource_ai_code/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ojzq</id>
            <title>Experience Blockchain on WhatsApp with BEAM: Inviting Beta Testers!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ojzq/experience_blockchain_on_whatsapp_with_beam/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177ojzq</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T12:35:02+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: BEAM, Cryptoxie FinTech, blockchain technology, messaging apps
<br>
<br>
总结: BEAM是由Cryptoxie FinTech推出的一项创新技术，旨在将区块链技术与WhatsApp等日常通讯应用相结合。BEAM使得区块链交易变得简单易用，就像发送短信一样方便。它具有与WhatsApp无缝集成、简化交易和买卖转账加密货币等特点。BEAM目前处于初期阶段，即将开放私人测试，并邀请区块链爱好者和科技精英成为首批体验者并提供宝贵反馈。加入我们，一起革新与区块链的互动方式。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello everyone,</p> <p>We are thrilled to introduce <strong>BEAM</strong> by Cryptoxie FinTech, a pioneer in bridging the gap between blockchain technology and everyday messaging apps like WhatsApp. With BEAM, we're taking a huge leap towards making blockchain transactions as straightforward and user-friendly as sending a text message.</p> <p><strong>What Makes BEAM Unique</strong>?</p> <p>- <strong>Seamless Integration</strong>: BEAM is engineered to integrate with WhatsApp, enabling you to execute blockchain transactions right from your favorite messaging app.</p> <p>- <strong>Simplified Transactions</strong>: Bid goodbye to the intimidating tech jargon typically associated with blockchain. BEAM is all about simplicity and user-centricity.</p> <p>- <strong>Buy, Sell, Transfer Cryptocurrencies</strong>: Whether you're looking to buy, sell, or transfer cryptocurrencies, BEAM has got you covered, all within WhatsApp!</p> <p>We are in the initial phase and opening up for private beta testing early next week. We're inviting blockchain enthusiasts and tech-savvy individuals to be among the first to experience BEAM and provide valuable feedback.</p> <p>Learn More and Request Access:</p> <p>- Discover more about BEAM: <a href="https://www.cryptoxie.com/products/beam-by-cryptoxie">BEAM by Cryptoxie FinTech</a></p> <p>- Get on the exclusive beta list: <a href="https://forms.gle/RkgyX8PfQeHdCwjY7">Request Access</a></p> <p>Join us in revolutionizing the way we interact with blockchain. Feel free to DM me or fill out the request form for an invite to our private beta. We are excited to have you on board on this innovative journey!</p> <p>Thank you!</p> <p>---</p> <p>*Disclaimer: This post is intended for informational purposes and is not promotional. We are genuinely seeking feedback from the community to refine our product.*</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Damanjain"> /u/Damanjain </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ojzq/experience_blockchain_on_whatsapp_with_beam/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177ojzq/experience_blockchain_on_whatsapp_with_beam/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177l0lv</id>
            <title>Could AI interpret a gamers playstyle/strategy and teach players where and how to improve?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177l0lv/could_ai_interpret_a_gamers_playstylestrategy_and/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177l0lv</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T08:41:20+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: future competitive gaming, players, improve, better at games
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了未来竞技游戏中的一个有趣功能，即让玩家了解如何在游戏中提高自己的能力，以便在游戏中表现更好。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I was just thinking, it would be a cool feature for future competitive gaming so players can learn where and how to improve so they can be better at games</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/aesthetion"> /u/aesthetion </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177l0lv/could_ai_interpret_a_gamers_playstylestrategy_and/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177l0lv/could_ai_interpret_a_gamers_playstylestrategy_and/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177kmgx</id>
            <title>Any reliable AI 'Image > HTML / CSS' tools out there?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kmgx/any_reliable_ai_image_html_css_tools_out_there/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177kmgx</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T08:11:56+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: 工具, jpeg, Figma / XD文件, HTML / CSS模板
<br>
<br>
总结: 作者希望有一种工具能够将jpeg或者Figma / XD文件转换成HTML / CSS模板，以便将设计转化为代码。作者提到了ChatGPT可以将sketch转换为HTML，但对作者来说没有用处。作者猜测当ChatGPT Vision可用时，也许可以实现这样的功能。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>What would be really useful for me is a tool where I could give it a jpeg, or better yet... a Figma / XD file, and have it convert it into a HTML / CSS template</p> <p>I remember a while back everybody was raving about how ChatGPT can convert a <em>sketch</em> to HTML, but that is no use to me whatsoever.</p> <p>I'd like to be able to convert a finished design to code... does such a thing exist? Maybe ChatGPT Vision when its available?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Weekly_Frosting_5868"> /u/Weekly_Frosting_5868 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kmgx/any_reliable_ai_image_html_css_tools_out_there/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177kmgx/any_reliable_ai_image_html_css_tools_out_there/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17714xx</id>
            <title>5 Must Have Google Chrome Extensions that Save Hours of Work into Minutes.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17714xx/5_must_have_google_chrome_extensions_that_save/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17714xx</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T15:18:53+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Google Chrome extensions, Scribe, Helperai 2.0, VisBug, Heurio, Motion
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章介绍了5个最佳的Google Chrome扩展程序，可以将数小时的工作节省为几分钟。其中包括Scribe，它可以将任何过程转化为逐步指南；Helperai 2.0，可以在任何网站上立即访问GPT-4；VisBug，是一个基于JavaScript构建的开源网页设计调试工具；Heurio，是一个完美的工具，可以帮助网页开发人员进行UX检查和设计开发审查；Motion DevTools，是一个对网页开发人员非常有用的浏览器扩展，可以检查、编辑和导出使用CSS和Motion One制作的动画。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Here are 5 of the best Google Chrome extensions I found on the internet that help to save you hours of work into minutes.</p> <p><strong>1. Scribe</strong></p> <p>This is an amazing extension that lets you turn any process into a step-by-step guide, instantly. With Scribe you can save Hundreds of thousands of valuable time. It works on almost all major browsers.</p> <p>Scribehow.com</p> <p><strong>2. Helperai 2.0</strong></p> <p>Just type “Help” and instant access GPT-4 on any site + Complete Ownership and source code.</p> <p>Why use it?</p> <p>✓ 3x Productivity, Write code &amp; Excel Formulas, Rewrite, Research, and more.</p> <p>✓ Work Great with all macOS + Windows.</p> <p>✓ Resell at any cost ( 100% Ownership + Source Code ) </p> <p>🔗 <a href="http://www.helperai.info">www.helperai.info</a></p> <p><strong>3. VisBug</strong></p> <p>It is an open source web design debug tools built with JavaScript. It gives power to designers and content creators by bringing design tool interactions and hotkeys to the browser. Not only it gives powers to designers and content creators, It has more features such as:</p> <p>Edit text, images or style any page in any state.</p> <p>Inspect styles, spacing, distance, accessibility and alignment.</p> <p>Nitpick layouts &amp; content, in the real end environment, at any device size.</p> <p>Leverage adobe/sketch skills.</p> <p>Visbug.web.app</p> <p><strong>4. Heurio</strong></p> <p>This is a perfect tool for any web developer. You can use this tool for UX check, design and development review, user testing and more. One beautiful benefit of using this extension is to make a smooth collaboration with developers directly on any live website. You can leave notes, assign actionable change requests, do UX or copy reviews in a user-friendly and collaborative way. It has features such as:</p> <p>Pin your ideas.</p> <p>Do a heuristic evaluation.</p> <p>Report bugs.</p> <p>Share the project link, invite team members or export your findings to PDF.</p> <p>Heurio.co</p> <p><strong>5. Motion</strong></p> <p>Motion DevTools is a browser extension useful for web developers like you. With this tool you can inspect, edit and export animations made with CSS and Motion One. </p> <p>Developers are able to add, move and remove keyframes in single click. </p> <p>You can export any animation into CSS transitions, CSS animations in few clicks. The best part of this tool is your edits will be reflected on the page in real-time.</p> <p>motion.dev</p> <p>That's it and thanks for reading! Hope you find this information useful. Feel free to share more similar chrome extensions.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Flat_Physics_3082"> /u/Flat_Physics_3082 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17714xx/5_must_have_google_chrome_extensions_that_save/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17714xx/5_must_have_google_chrome_extensions_that_save/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177586u</id>
            <title>Training an AI with voice so that it can speak like someone that you train it with.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177586u/training_an_ai_with_voice_so_that_it_can_speak/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177586u</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T18:25:12+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: niece, cartoon character, personalize, story
<br>
<br>
总结: 我的小侄女有一个最喜欢的卡通角色，我想为她个性化一个故事，用那个卡通角色的声音。有没有人知道一个不需要太多编程知识的好的起点？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>My little niece has a favorite cartoon character and I wanted to personalize a story for her with that cartoons voice. Does anyone know of a good place to start with this that isnt very coder heavy?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/extelius"> /u/extelius </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177586u/training_an_ai_with_voice_so_that_it_can_speak/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177586u/training_an_ai_with_voice_so_that_it_can_speak/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177eat1</id>
            <title>NexaAIOne: Centralized RESTful API hub for AI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177eat1/nexaaione_centralized_restful_api_hub_for_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177eat1</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T01:35:05+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: open-source project, RESTful API hub, Artificial intelligence (AI), developer
<br>
<br>
总结: 这是一个开源项目，它是一个RESTful API中心，专为人工智能开发者设计，提供先进的功能和可定制性。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello All</p> <p>Sharing my new open-source project, I hope it will be helpful for you.<br /> NexaAIOne, a centralized RESTful API hub for Artificial intelligence (AI). Designed for every developer. NexaAIOne platform brings advanced features and customizability right to your fingertips. </p> <p><a href="https://github.com/mrahmadt/NexaAIOne">https://github.com/mrahmadt/NexaAIOne</a> </p> <p>Youtube - Intro: <a href="https://youtu.be/tzAxDwR12V4">https://youtu.be/tzAxDwR12V4</a></p> <p>Any testing or collaboration feedback is more than welcome </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/mrguestx"> /u/mrguestx </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177eat1/nexaaione_centralized_restful_api_hub_for_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177eat1/nexaaione_centralized_restful_api_hub_for_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177i4wq</id>
            <title>One-Minute Daily AI News 10/14/2023</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177i4wq/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10142023/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177i4wq</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T05:18:29+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AMD, Nod.ai, AI software ecosystem, growth of AI, electricity consumption, Cyberpunk 2077, Phantom Liberty, deceased voice actor, Google, copyright law
<br>
<br>
总结: AMD收购Nod.ai以增强其AI软件生态系统；AI的增长可能导致该行业消耗的电力量相当于一个小国；《Cyberpunk 2077》使用AI技术为已故配音演员创作；Google宣布，如果您使用其产品创建的AI图像违反版权法，它将为您提供保护。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><ol> <li><strong>AMD</strong> acquires Nod.ai to bolster its AI software ecosystem.[1]</li> <li>Growth of AI could lead to the industry consuming as much electricity as a small nation.[2]</li> <li><strong>Cyberpunk 2077</strong>: Phantom Liberty Used AI for a Deceased Voice Actor.[3]</li> <li><strong>Google</strong> announced that it will protect you if the AI images you create using its products happen to break copyright law.[4]</li> </ol> <p>Sources included at: <a href="https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/14/10-14-2023/">https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/14/10-14-2023/</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Excellent-Target-847"> /u/Excellent-Target-847 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177i4wq/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10142023/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177i4wq/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10142023/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1775fip</id>
            <title>OpenAI has quietly changed its 'core values' putting more emphasis on AGI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1775fip/openai_has_quietly_changed_its_core_values/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1775fip</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T18:34:10+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, 人工智能, 人工通用智能, 核心价值观
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI最近修改了其公司价值观，更加强调构建人工通用智能（AGI）。OpenAI将“AGI关注”作为其首要核心价值观，并指出任何与AGI无关的事物都不在其范围内。这一变化在没有公告的情况下悄然发生，引发了人们对OpenAI重新关注AGI的动机的质疑。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>OpenAI recently revised its company values to place greater emphasis on building artificial general intelligence (AGI). (<a href="https://www.semafor.com/article/10/12/2023/openai-quietly-changed-its-core-values">Source</a>)</p> <p>If you want the latest AI updates before anyone else, <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">look here first</a></p> <p><strong>New Top Priority: AGI</strong></p> <ul> <li>OpenAI added &quot;AGI focus&quot; as its first core value.</li> <li>It notes anything not helping AGI is out of scope.</li> <li>This replaced previous values like &quot;audacious&quot; and &quot;thoughtful.&quot;</li> </ul> <p><strong>Pursuing Advanced AI</strong></p> <ul> <li>OpenAI has long aimed to develop human-level AGI.</li> <li>But specifics remain unclear on what this entails.</li> <li>Some worry about risks of highly autonomous systems.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Motivations Uncertain</strong></p> <ul> <li>Change made quietly without announcement.</li> <li>Comes after ChatGPT's smash success.</li> <li>Raises questions on OpenAI's renewed AGI motivations.</li> </ul> <p><strong>PS:</strong> Get the latest <strong>AI developments, tools, and use cases</strong> by joining one of the fastest-growing AI newsletters. Join <a href="https://www.theedge.so/subscribe">5000+ professionals getting smarter in AI.</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Ok-Feeling-1743"> /u/Ok-Feeling-1743 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1775fip/openai_has_quietly_changed_its_core_values/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1775fip/openai_has_quietly_changed_its_core_values/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177d38i</id>
            <title>Which AI can re-order spreadsheet or .csv rows by content themes?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177d38i/which_ai_can_reorder_spreadsheet_or_csv_rows_by/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_177d38i</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-14T00:30:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: re-organize, content themes, food, animals, plants, other, Bard response, Goog sheet, changes, original, new sheet, new file, Prompt, right response, file update/output, ChatGPT, GSheet, reputable plugins, reviews, fake names, Indian names
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了使用人工智能技术重新组织电子表格或CSV行的问题。作者提到了一个名为Bard response的工具，声称可以通过链接到Google表格来按内容主题进行重新组织，但实际上并没有进行任何更改。此外，作者还提到了ChatGPT和GSheet这两个工具，但它们似乎没有可靠的插件，评论中的用户名也可能是虚假的。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Trying to re-organize by content themes, ie. food, animals, plants, other. </p> <p>Bard response claims to be able to do this for 13.5K rows if you link to a Goog sheet, but it never has any changes (original, new sheet, or new file), per similar Googled user posts too. Prompt produces the right response but no actual file update/output as claimed.</p> <p>ChatGPT/GSheet don’t seem to have any reputable plugins where the reviews arent clearly all fake names (ie unheard of last names/name combos, unlikely avatars, or all Indian names), thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/privateusers"> /u/privateusers </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177d38i/which_ai_can_reorder_spreadsheet_or_csv_rows_by/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/177d38i/which_ai_can_reorder_spreadsheet_or_csv_rows_by/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1776eks</id>
            <title>Can someone recommend me an AI that i can use to find out the key information about a research paper (that has a mobile version)?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1776eks/can_someone_recommend_me_an_ai_that_i_can_use_to/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1776eks</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T19:18:32+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: analyse, papers, aims, methods, key findings, limitations, AI, phone
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了作者需要分析一堆论文并记录它们的主要内容：目标、方法、关键发现和限制。摘要太模糊，但阅读整篇论文又非常耗时。作者想知道是否有一种可以通过手机使用的人工智能来帮助他。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Basically i have to analyse a bunch of papers and write down the main things about them: aims, methods, key findings, limitations. The abstracts are too vague but reading the whole paper is also very time taking. So is there an AI that i can use to help me? Preferably that i can use via my phone haha</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Idkwhatreally12"> /u/Idkwhatreally12 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1776eks/can_someone_recommend_me_an_ai_that_i_can_use_to/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1776eks/can_someone_recommend_me_an_ai_that_i_can_use_to/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1777xvk</id>
            <title>Need help and guidance with using local Mistral-7B to make chatbot trained on internal documents</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1777xvk/need_help_and_guidance_with_using_local_mistral7b/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_1777xvk</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-13T20:30:00+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: 提取出来的关键词, 使用逗号分割
<br>
<br>
总结: 中文概括

关键词: 文字编辑工作者, 多语言, 文字内容创作经验
<br>
<br>
总结: 假设你是一位有丰富文字内容创作经验的多语言文字编辑工作者

关键词: <提取出来的关键词,使用逗号分割>
<br>
<br>
总结: 中文概括

关键词: 提取出来的关键词, 使用逗号分割
<br>
<br>
总结: 中文概括 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Professional_Bunch69"> /u/Professional_Bunch69 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/LocalLLaMA/comments/1777d6r/need_help_and_guidance_with_using_local_mistral7b/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/1777xvk/need_help_and_guidance_with_using_local_mistral7b/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>