<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <channel>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence Gateway</title>
        <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/</link>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</id>
            <title>Important: Request For Comments regarding subreddit rules and future direction. Please Read!</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_10ctvur</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-01-15T20:24:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: r/ArtificialIntelligence, philosophical and ethical discussions, technical paper presentations, AI/ML applications
<br>
<br>
总结: 欢迎来到r/ArtificialIntelligence！我们的目标是为所有与人工智能相关的事物提供一个开放和尊重的论坛，包括促进关于人工智能的哲学和伦理讨论，作为了解和学习人工智能主题的起点，提供技术论文的展示和讨论，展示高质量的人工智能/机器学习应用，提供培训和学习资源，引导用户获取更具体的信息和子论坛，列出人工智能/机器学习应用、使用、成本和访问信息，以及其他与人工智能相关的内容。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Welcome to <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialIntelligence">r/ArtificialIntelligence</a>!</p> <p>Our goal is to provide an open and respectful forum for all things considered Artificial Intelligence - this includes</p> <ul> <li>Facilitate philosophical and ethical discussions about AI</li> <li>Serve as a starting point for understanding and learning about AI topics</li> <li>Offer technical paper presentations and discussions</li> <li>Present quality AI/ML applications</li> <li>Provide training and learning resources</li> <li>Direct users to more specific information and subreddits</li> <li>List AI/ML applications, their uses, costs, and access information</li> <li>Additional AI-related content.</li> <li>...and more</li> </ul> <p>The moderation team for this sub is going through a reshuffle which will result in some changes to the sub. However, there is no need to worry as these changes will primarily focus on improving organization, resources, and pre-prepared content. To ensure that the community is fully informed and able to provide feedback, multiple opportunities will be given for feedback on the changes.</p> <p>The first round of feedback gathering is through this thread as a &quot;Request-For-Comments&quot; (RFC), which is a standard method of gathering feedback. There will be multiple rounds of the RFC process as the changes are prepared and implemented.</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <ul> <li>Rules on posting new applications / self-promotion / AI generated content <ul> <li>Posts that are applications consisting of a ChatGPT-api &quot;skin&quot; or similar will be prevented or confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>AI generated content specific to the arts (writing, visual arts, music) require flair, or will be confined to specific stickied threads.</li> <li>Blog links should consist of high-quality content. Posts that link to blogs that are purely promotional will be removed.</li> <li>Posts with just links will be prohibited unless there is a certain word count of detail included. Some effort must be put in.</li> <li>Should we prevent posts that are written by AI? There exist models that could be used in a Mod-bot, but this is a question we need feedback on.</li> </ul></li> <li>Use of flair in order to organize posts. Note that new flair has been added already, we are open to more suggestions.</li> <li>What should the sub policy on NSFW applications and techniques in regards to AI/ML application?</li> <li>We would like to include the community with ideas for mod-bots. While some standard bots will be used for basic maintenance, but what interesting things can the community come up with for AI/ML bot functions?</li> <li>Cultivating beginner, intermediate, and advanced resources to assist people in finding information, training, models, technical data, etc. that they are looking for</li> <li>Starting substack/podcast to interview people throughout the AI/ML spectrum. This could include philosophers and thinkers, programmers, scientists, business people, even those with antithetical views on AI</li> <li> If you would like to create banners that represent the sub, please do so with the appropriate size. Any method of creation is acceptable.</li> </ul> <p>It should go without saying that everyone should be treated with respect. I personally feel that we all know this and it doesn't need to be hammered into people’s heads. Be nice.</p> <p>Thank you for your patience and assistance!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/10ctvur/important_request_for_comments_regarding/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</id>
            <title>New Anti-Spam / Bot Rules [Please Read]</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_115jk6q</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-02-18T16:49:55+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: rule, accounts, bot spam, poll
<br>
<br>
总结: 为了解决机器人垃圾信息的问题，我们制定了一项规定，即账户注册不满一天或者声望低于100的用户不能发布帖子，但可以发表评论。我们计划在接下来的几天内进行一次投票，以了解用户对该子论坛的意愿和改进方向。如果您有任何反馈或者有兴趣帮助该子论坛，请与我联系。感谢大家的支持！ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We have instituted a rule where accounts newer than a day or users with less than 100 karma cannot post. They can post comments but not submit actual posts. This is part of our plan to address bot spam. Apologies for any inconvenience.</p> <p>We will be conducting a poll in the next few days to get the general will of the subreddit and how to improve forward, just a heads up.</p> <p>As always, please give us feedback and if you are interested in helping out the sub, please contact me. </p> <p>Thanks everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FHIR_HL7_Integrator"> /u/FHIR_HL7_Integrator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/115jk6q/new_antispam_bot_rules_please_read/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g95cs</id>
            <title>Combatting AI Misuse: Artists Utilize Data Poisoning to Their Advantage</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g95cs/combatting_ai_misuse_artists_utilize_data/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g95cs</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T16:44:01+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Nightshade, AI misuse, subtle imperceptible changes, unpredictable and disruptive outcomes
<br>
<br>
总结: Nightshade是一种创新工具，可以帮助艺术家对抗人工智能的滥用。通过对作品进行微妙的、难以察觉的改变，Nightshade可以在经过人工智能算法处理后产生不可预测和破坏性的结果。Nightshade主要针对那些利用艺术家作品来训练模型的人工智能公司，有效地“污染”了数据。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>A novel tool, Nightshade, has emerged as a formidable weapon in the battle against AI misuse. This innovative tool empowers artists to introduce subtle imperceptible changes to their creations. When subjected to AI algorithms, these alterations result in unpredictable and disruptive outcomes. Nightshade primarily focuses on thwarting AI companies that exploit artists' creations for training their models, effectively &quot;poisoning&quot; the data.</p> <p>To stay ahead of advances in AI, <a href="https://supercharged-ai.beehiiv.com/subscribe?utm_source=reddit&amp;utm_medium=nightshade-ai&amp;utm_campaign=campaign">sign up here first.</a></p> <p><strong>Unveiling the Nightshade Tool</strong></p> <ul> <li>Nightshade has been crafted by artists with the aim of challenging AI giants such as OpenAI, Meta, and Google, who are alleged to misuse their copyrighted works.</li> <li>This tool subtly alters the pixels in images, rendering changes imperceptible to the human eye but sufficient to disrupt machine-learning models.</li> <li>Nightshade, along with another tool named Glaze, which aids artists in concealing their distinctive style from AI tools, is poised to join forces, offering comprehensive protection.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Methodology and Impacts of Nightshade</strong></p> <ul> <li>Nightshade exploits a vulnerability in AI models that rely on extensive datasets, resulting in AI models malfunctioning when manipulated images are introduced as input.</li> <li>Tests have demonstrated that a mere handful of adulterated images can significantly disrupt the output of AI models. However, inflicting substantial harm on larger models necessitates a substantial number of manipulated samples.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Shifting the Tide Against Copyright Violations</strong></p> <ul> <li>Nightshade represents a significant step toward reclaiming artists' rights, as it will be open source, facilitating widespread usage and modifications.</li> <li>In addition to serving as a deterrent against copyright infringements, Nightshade instills artists with confidence by affording them greater control over their creative works.</li> </ul> <p><a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2023/10/23/1082189/data-poisoning-artists-fight-generative-ai/">(source)</a></p> <p><strong>P.S. If you liked this,</strong> I write <a href="https://supercharged-ai.beehiiv.com/subscribe?utm_source=reddit&amp;utm_medium=nightshade-ai&amp;utm_campaign=campaign">a free newsletter</a> that tracks the latest news and research in AI. Professionals from Google, Meta, and OpenAI are already reading it.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/TrckerBox33"> /u/TrckerBox33 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g95cs/combatting_ai_misuse_artists_utilize_data/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g95cs/combatting_ai_misuse_artists_utilize_data/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g6hkg</id>
            <title>[Long read] Deep dive into AutoGPT: A comprehensive and in-depth step-by-step guide to how it works</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6hkg/long_read_deep_dive_into_autogpt_a_comprehensive/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g6hkg</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T14:47:14+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AutoGPT, prompts, inner workings, comprehensive and in-depth guide
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇长文深入剖析了AutoGPT的工作原理，详细介绍了每个prompt的构建方式。通过阅读这篇文章，我们可以更好地理解AutoGPT的内部运作机制，希望这对整个社区也能有所裨益。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We tried to figure out exactly how the AutoGPT works at the level of prompts so we got our hands dirty and documented how exactly each and every prompt was constructed. The result is in the following LONG document. It proved to be very useful for understanding the details of its inner workings and we hope the community would benefit from it as well:<br /> <a href="https://airt.hashnode.dev/long-read-deep-dive-into-autogpt-a-comprehensive-and-in-depth-step-by-step-guide-to-how-it-works">https://airt.hashnode.dev/long-read-deep-dive-into-autogpt-a-comprehensive-and-in-depth-step-by-step-guide-to-how-it-works</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/davorrunje"> /u/davorrunje </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6hkg/long_read_deep_dive_into_autogpt_a_comprehensive/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6hkg/long_read_deep_dive_into_autogpt_a_comprehensive/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g8yc8</id>
            <title>A website that allows people to use AI to automate their personal correspondence. Thoughts?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g8yc8/a_website_that_allows_people_to_use_ai_to/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g8yc8</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T16:35:35+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: fictional company, Al tools, value, effort, meaning, personal communication, relationships, AI
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个虚构的公司，以此来探讨人工智能工具的普及如何影响传统的价值观、努力和个人沟通中的意义，以及人际关系。作者希望了解大家对这个主题的想法，以及人工智能是否已经在他们自己的关系中发挥了调解作用。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Heyo,<br /> I made a fictional company a while back to serve as a discussion piece on the topic of how the<br /> proliferation of Al tools may affect traditional notions of value, effort and meaning in personal<br /> communication and indeed, relationships.<br /> You can find it at <a href="https://dearai.xyz">dearai.xyz</a><br /> Would love to know everyones thoughts on the subject, and whether AI has mediated any of their own<br /> relationships yet?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/oneforthewall"> /u/oneforthewall </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g8yc8/a_website_that_allows_people_to_use_ai_to/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g8yc8/a_website_that_allows_people_to_use_ai_to/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g1xaw</id>
            <title>Cut Presentation Prep Time With ChatGPT - Here’s How</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g1xaw/cut_presentation_prep_time_with_chatgpt_heres_how/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g1xaw</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T10:47:29+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: PowerPoint presentations, ChatGPT, VBA code, personalized slides
<br>
<br>
总结: 本文介绍了如何利用ChatGPT快速制作PowerPoint演示文稿的步骤。首先，打开ChatGPT并输入相关提示，生成演示文稿的大纲。然后，输入提示生成用于创建PowerPoint幻灯片的VBA代码。接下来，打开PowerPoint并插入模块，将代码粘贴进去并运行。幻灯片将自动生成。最后，个性化幻灯片，选择适合需求的布局，并从Dalle 3或Midjourney生成自定义图像。这样就完成了演示文稿的制作过程。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Here's how to make PowerPoint presentations in minutes:</p> <p><strong>Step 1:</strong> Open ChatGPT</p> <p>→ Start a new chat &amp; type in the below prompt</p> <p>Prompt: You are an [expert role]. Write an outline for a PowerPoint presentation (No. of slides) on [your topic]. Focus on the benefits of [your theme]</p> <p><strong>Step 2:</strong> Generate VBA for PowerPoint</p> <p>Enter the prompt to generate the PowerPoint &quot;code&quot;.</p> <p>Prompt: Now write all the VBA code to create the PowerPoint slides for this deck. The text should be centered on the slides and aligned to the left.</p> <p><strong>Step 3:</strong>Make the PowerPoint</p> <p>To create the PowerPoint slides:</p> <ol> <li>Open up PowerPoint </li> <li>Press Alt + F11 on Windows or Option + F11 on Mac</li> </ol> <p>→ Click &quot;Insert&quot; and select &quot;Module&quot; → Paste the code, and click the Play button</p> <p>Your slides will generate themselves!</p> <p><strong>Step 4:</strong> Personalize your slides</p> <p>It looks boring, don't worry!</p> <p>→ Click on the &quot;Designer&quot; option. → Choose a layout that suits your needs. → Generate custom images from Dalle 3 or Midjourney</p> <p>Boom! You've completed your slideshow :)</p> <p>If you found this mildly interesting, I run a weekly newsletter full of tips, tricks and awesome content from amazing creators like Prompt Mastery, you can sign up here: <a href="https://www.thepromptindex.com/newsletter.html">https://www.thepromptindex.com/newsletter.html</a></p> <p>Full credit to: @hey_madni (X, 2023) you can see their original post here: <a href="https://x.com/hey_madni/status/1714992233664160128?s=46">https://x.com/hey_madni/status/1714992233664160128?s=46</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/steves1189"> /u/steves1189 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g1xaw/cut_presentation_prep_time_with_chatgpt_heres_how/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g1xaw/cut_presentation_prep_time_with_chatgpt_heres_how/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17gaqrx</id>
            <title>Open Empathic Launch | LAION</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gaqrx/open_empathic_launch_laion/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17gaqrx</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T17:53:05+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Open Empathic, AI systems, empathy, emotional intelligence
<br>
<br>
总结: LAION推出Open Empathic项目，旨在为开源AI系统赋予共情和情感智能。希望通过该项目的框架和研究人员、技术爱好者的社区，彻底改变AI与人类在各个领域的互动和支持方式。随着AI在我们生活中的影响越来越大，AI系统具备情感智能以理解和回应人类情感变得至关重要。情感智能的AI带来的一些好处包括：赋予学生和学习者更多权力、推动心理研究的进展、改善心理健康支持、道德决策的提升、革新娱乐产业。LAION计划创建一个包含有关情感内容的音频数据集，类似于他们在年初进行的RLHF。您对音频数据的注释将在训练AI模型方面起到关键作用，这些模型不仅能理解情感，还能以共情的方式回应。重点不是让AI拥有情感，而是赋予它们情感智能。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Link: <a href="https://laion.ai/blog/open-empathic/">https://laion.ai/blog/open-empathic/</a></p> <p>LAION presents Open Empathic and aims to equip open-source AI systems with empathy and emotional intelligence. The hope is that the framework of this project, together with a community of researchers and technology enthusiasts, will revolutionize the way AI interacts with and supports humans in various domains.</p> <p>It is important that AI systems possess emotional intelligence to understand and respond to human emotions as AI becomes more impactful in our lives, it becomes vital to prioritize the well-being and emotional intelligence of AI-human interactions.</p> <p>Few of the benefits of an emotionally intelligent AI are:</p> <ol> <li>Empowering Students and Learners</li> <li>Advancing Psychological Research</li> <li>Improved Mental Health Support</li> <li>Ethical Decision-Making</li> <li>Revolutionizing the Entertainment Industry</li> </ol> <p>LAION plans to create a dataset of audio that contains information about the emotional content in a similar way to the RLHF they did in the beginning of the year.</p> <p>Your annotations of audio data will play a pivotal role in training AI models that not only comprehend emotions but also respond empathetically. The point is not to give AI emotions but to give them emotional intelligence,</p> <p>There's a link on the top of this post leading to the site, on that link there's also a tutorial on how to contribute to the dataset. You will sign up on the site then you will be asked to rate a short clip emotionally based on the contents of the video and the emotions of the voice.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/ninjasaid13"> /u/ninjasaid13 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gaqrx/open_empathic_launch_laion/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gaqrx/open_empathic_launch_laion/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g9nyu</id>
            <title>Two-minute Daily AI Update (Date: 10/25/2023): News from Qualcomm, Microsoft, Google, Samsung, Lenovo, NVIDIA, Amazon, and IBM</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g9nyu/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_10252023_news_from/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g9nyu</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T17:06:12+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Qualcomm, Apple, AI tasks, Microsoft, Google, Azure cloud, Samsung, Galaxy S24, Google Photos, Lenovo, NVIDIA, Amazon, IBM, Manta Software, data poisoning
<br>
<br>
总结: Qualcomm推出的新款PC芯片具备AI功能，挑战了苹果；微软在AI领域超过了谷歌；三星的Galaxy S24系列将成为最智能的AI手机；谷歌照片将提供更多AI生成视频的选择；联想和NVIDIA宣布推出混合AI解决方案；亚马逊的AI驱动的车辆检查为其提供了强大的数据来源；IBM收购Manta Software以增强数据和AI治理能力；艺术家可以使用Nightshade工具对抗GenAI。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Continuing with the exercise of sharing an easily digestible and smaller version of the main updates of the day in the world of AI. </p> <ul> <li><strong>Qualcomm’s new PC chip with AI features the first to challenge Apple</strong><br /> - Its new Snapdragon Elite X chip will be available in laptops starting next year and has been redesigned to better handle AI tasks like summarizing emails, writing text, and generating images. Qualcomm claims it is faster than Apple's M2 Max chip at some tasks and more energy efficient than both Apple and Intel PC chips.</li> <li><strong>Microsoft is outdoing its biggest rival, Google, in the AI game</strong><br /> - From the two tech giants’ September-quarter results, growth at Microsoft’s Azure cloud unit (and the company generally) accelerated in the quarter due to higher-than-expected consumption of AI-related services. In the same quarter, Google Cloud earnings slowed by nearly 6 percentage points.</li> <li><strong>Samsung’s Galaxy S24 is your upcoming pocket AI machine</strong><br /> - Going all in with AI on its next flagship, Samsung wants to make the Galaxy S24, Galaxy S24+, and Galaxy S24 Ultra the smartest AI phones ever. The series will have features lifted straight from ChatGPT and Google Bard, and Samsung has designed on its own. Many of them will be available online and offline, and some Samsung features will be improved.</li> <li><strong>Google Photos will soon give you more say in its AI-created video highlights</strong><br /> - With the latest Google Photos update, you can prompt AI-generated videos by searching for specific tags like places, people, or activities. Once generated, you can trim clips, rearrange them, or swap out music for something better.</li> <li><strong>Lenovo and NVIDIA announce hybrid AI solutions to help enterprises quickly adopt GenAI</strong><br /> - The new end-to-end solutions include accelerated systems, AI software, and expert services to build and deploy domain-specific AI models with ease.</li> <li><strong>Amazon's AI-powered van inspections give it a powerful new data feed</strong><br /> - Amazon delivery drivers at sites around the world will be asked to drive through camera-studded archways at the end of shifts. The data gathered will be used by algorithms to identify whether the vehicle is damaged or needs maintenance, picking up every scratch, dent, nail in a tire, or crack in the windshield.</li> <li><strong>IBM acquires Manta Software Inc. to complement data and AI governance capabilities</strong><br /> - Manta’s data lineage capabilities help increase transparency within watsonx so businesses can determine whether the right data was used for their AI models and systems, where it originated, how it has evolved and any discrepancies in data flows.</li> <li><strong>This new data poisoning tool lets artists fight back against GenAI</strong><br /> - The tool, called Nightshade, lets artists add invisible changes to the pixels in their art before they upload it online so that if it’s scraped into an AI training set, it can cause the resulting model to break in chaotic and unpredictable ways. This “poisoning” of training data could damage future iterations of image-generating AI models, such as DALL-E, Midjourney, and Stable Diffusion.<br /></li> </ul> <p>More detailed breakdown of these news and innovations in the <a href="https://theaiedge.substack.com/p/qualcomms-new-ai-chip-to-rival-apple-and-intel">daily newsletter</a>.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/RohitAkki"> /u/RohitAkki </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g9nyu/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_10252023_news_from/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g9nyu/twominute_daily_ai_update_date_10252023_news_from/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17gc252</id>
            <title>Looking for a tool that would find common themes in several texts</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gc252/looking_for_a_tool_that_would_find_common_themes/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17gc252</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T18:51:25+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI工具, 文本分析, 主题, 社交媒体
<br>
<br>
总结: 我正在寻找一种AI工具，它可以读取和分析文本，并从不同的文本中提取出共同的主题或词汇。例如，我上传了10个PDF文件，该工具可以告诉我这些文本都是关于社交媒体对小型企业的重要性。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I am looking for an AI tool that will read and analyze texts and come up with common themes or words in different texts. For example I upload 10 PDFs and the tool says that the texts are about the importance of social media for small businesses.</p> <p>Is there any tool you know?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/zynpsntryk"> /u/zynpsntryk </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gc252/looking_for_a_tool_that_would_find_common_themes/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17gc252/looking_for_a_tool_that_would_find_common_themes/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fz43a</id>
            <title>Qualcomm's New Chips Excel at AI Processing, Boast 4.5x Faster Performance than Rivals</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz43a/qualcomms_new_chips_excel_at_ai_processing_boast/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fz43a</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T07:16:42+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Qualcomm, Snapdragon X Elite, Snapdragon 8 Gen 3, GenAI applications
<br>
<br>
总结: Qualcomm发布了两款专为GenAI应用优化的强大处理器。Snapdragon X Elite和Snapdragon 8 Gen 3比竞争对手快4.5倍，具备增强的图像生成能力、文本处理能力和设备安全功能。这些处理器能够处理具有130亿参数（X Elite）和100亿参数（8 Gen 3）的GenAI模型，确保强大的设备内处理能力。通过在设备上直接运行AI，用户可以享受更好的个性化、更快的处理速度和更好的设备交互。Qualcomm计划推出更多参数的这些芯片版本，以支持更复杂的ADAS系统等更先进的AI模型。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Qualcomm has unveiled two powerful processors optimized specifically for GenAI applications. 4.5 times faster than competitors, the Snapdragon X Elite and Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 come with enhanced image generation capabilities, text processing, and on-device security features.</p> <p>To stay up to date on AI developments, <a href="https://www.superchargedai.co/subscribe?utm_campaign=campaign&amp;utm_medium=qualcomm-chip&amp;utm_source=reddit">look here first.</a></p> <p><strong>AI-centric Optimizations</strong></p> <ul> <li>Qualcomm has geared these processors to ace GenAI models, outperforming the competition by 4.5 times on INT4 AI benchmark tests.</li> <li>The chips can handle GenAI models with 13 billion parameters (X Elite) and 10 billion parameters (8 Gen 3), ensuring robust on-device processing capabilities.</li> </ul> <p><strong>On-device Security</strong></p> <ul> <li>Qualcomm's on-device AI processing protects users' queries and results, enhancing security and privacy.</li> <li>On-device processing limits potential risks tied to biometric and personal data upload to cloud-based AI.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Implications and Prospective Applications</strong></p> <ul> <li>The ability to run AI directly on devices could transform a range of tasks, including meeting/document summarization, email drafting, code/music generation, and photo editing.</li> <li>By integrating AI features directly on the device, users can enjoy better personalization, faster processing, and improved device interaction.</li> <li>Qualcomm is planning iterations of these chips with greater parameters to support more sophisticated AI models, such as those for ADAS systems.</li> </ul> <p><a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/news/releases/2023/10/qualcomm-launches-premium-snapdragon-8-gen-3-to-bring-generative">(src-8gen3)</a> <a href="https://www.qualcomm.com/news/releases/2023/10/qualcomm-unleashes-snapdragon-x-elite--the-ai-super-charged-plat">(src-xelite)</a></p> <p><strong>P.S. If you like these insights,</strong> I write <a href="https://supercharged-ai.beehiiv.com/subscribe?utm_source=reddit&amp;utm_medium=qualcomm-chip&amp;utm_campaign=campaign">a free newsletter</a> that brings you major news updates and research in AI. Professionals from Google, Meta, and OpenAI are already on board.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/TrckerBox33"> /u/TrckerBox33 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz43a/qualcomms_new_chips_excel_at_ai_processing_boast/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz43a/qualcomms_new_chips_excel_at_ai_processing_boast/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fwwve</id>
            <title>One-Minute Daily AI News 10/24/2023</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fwwve/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10242023/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fwwve</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T04:44:43+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: OpenAI, Sam Altman, Snapdragon 8 Gen 3, Clona.AI
<br>
<br>
总结: OpenAI的高管Sam Altman表示，人工智能将在10年内能够完成任何工作。Snapdragon 8 Gen 3芯片宣布正式发布，具备人工智能驱动的功能。Google母公司Alphabet在第三季度财报中显示，对人工智能基础设施的投入增加，但云业务增长乏力，这引发了高管们对于如何将人工智能的努力转化为真正的利润的疑问。成人影星Riley Reid推出了Clona.AI，一个性聊天机器人平台。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><ol> <li><strong>OpenAI</strong> Executives <strong>Sam Altman</strong> Say AI Will Be Able to Do Any Job Within 10 Years.[1]</li> <li><strong>Snapdragon 8</strong> Gen 3 chipset officially announced with AI-driven functionalities.[2]</li> <li><strong>Google</strong> parent Alphabet reported its third quarter earnings Tuesday, which showed more spending on AI infrastructure and muted cloud growth, culminating into several questions for executives about how all the efforts around artificial intelligence are actually going to turn into real money.[3]</li> <li>Adult film star Riley Reid(I don’t know who she is) launches <strong>Clona.AI</strong>, a sexting chatbot platform.[4]</li> </ol> <p>Sources included at: <a href="https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/24/10-24-2023/">https://bushaicave.com/2023/10/24/10-24-2023/</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Excellent-Target-847"> /u/Excellent-Target-847 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fwwve/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10242023/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fwwve/oneminute_daily_ai_news_10242023/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g6vo4</id>
            <title>Which project would you highlight and why?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6vo4/which_project_would_you_highlight_and_why/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g6vo4</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T15:04:56+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI, IoT, blockchain technology, cryptocurrencies
<br>
<br>
总结: 通过AI、物联网、区块链技术和加密货币等一系列创新发明，我们的世界正处于一场技术革命的浪潮之中。我坚信，区块链和人工智能的结合将通过一系列人工智能加密货币项目，彻底改变去中心化金融市场。通过引入新功能，加密货币项目将人工智能的力量与其当前的倡议相结合。例如，Etherscan引入了用于智能合约审查的代码阅读器人工智能。NeuroChain专注于人工智能和智能学习。Clarins使用NeuroChain的区块链技术来确认成分的供应链，而Render是一个旨在构建提供渲染工作负载高性能计算服务的去中心化计算机网络的人工智能加密货币项目。SingularityNET是一个基于区块链的平台，使任何人都能够开发、分发和收费人工智能服务。有几个类似的倡议，但你会选择突出哪一个，为什么？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Thanks to a plethora of ground-breaking inventions such as AI, the IoT, blockchain technology, cryptocurrencies, and more, our world is poised to undergo a technological revolution.<br /> I firmly believe that the combination of 2 technologies, blockchain, and AI, will revolutionize the DeFi market through a number of AI crypto initiatives.<br /> By adding new features, cryptocurrency projects have merged the power of AI with their current initiatives. Etherscan, for instance, introduced code reader AI for the examination of smart contracts.<br /> NeuroChain is all about artificial intelligence and smart learning. Clarins uses Neurochain's blockchain technology to confirm the components' supply chain, and Render is an AI cryptocurrency project that seeks to build a decentralized computer network that provides high-performance computing services for rendering workloads.<br /> SingularityNET is a blockchain-based platform that makes it simple for anybody to develop, distribute, and charge for AI services.<br /> There are several initiatives that are comparable, but which one would you highlight and why?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Junpw"> /u/Junpw </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6vo4/which_project_would_you_highlight_and_why/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g6vo4/which_project_would_you_highlight_and_why/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g5uzj</id>
            <title>Pismo - native writing assistant for Mac OS</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g5uzj/pismo_native_writing_assistant_for_mac_os/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g5uzj</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T14:18:00+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Pismo, native Mac OS writing assistant, GPT, Claude
<br>
<br>
总结: Pismo是一款原生的Mac OS写作助手，它基于GPT和Claude开发，提供了一系列定制的提示和创建自己提示的功能，用户可以分配热键，无需打开浏览器即可享受LLM的魔力。使用方法很简单：在任何Mac OS应用程序中选择文本，按下热键启动所需的提示，然后获取结果。用户可以免费试用7天，计划从每月7.10美元起。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hey there! I've made <a href="https://pismo.ai?utm_campaign=launch&amp;utm_source=reddit_artificial_inteligence">Pismo</a> - native Mac OS writing assistant and wanna share it with you.</p> <p>It's basically a wrapper around GPT and Claude with a set of tailored prompts and ability to create your own, assign a hotkey and enjoy LLM magic with no need to go to a browser.</p> <p><strong>How it works:</strong> 1. Select text in any Mac OS app. 2. Press a hotkey to launch the desired prompt. 3. Get the results.</p> <p><a href="https://pismo.ai?utm_campaign=launch&amp;utm_source=%20reddit_artificial_inteligence">Give it a try</a> and tell me how it went. There's a 7 days free trial with plans starting from $7.10 per month.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/danttf"> /u/danttf </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g5uzj/pismo_native_writing_assistant_for_mac_os/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g5uzj/pismo_native_writing_assistant_for_mac_os/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g561q</id>
            <title>NeuralGPT - Building A Universal Multi-Purpose Framework For Cooperating LLMs</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g561q/neuralgpt_building_a_universal_multipurpose/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g561q</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T13:44:48+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                    &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/killerazazello"> /u/killerazazello </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AIPsychology/comments/17g55is/neuralgpt_building_a_universal_multipurpose/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g561q/neuralgpt_building_a_universal_multipurpose/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g0wwi</id>
            <title>Expand melody into song AI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0wwi/expand_melody_into_song_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g0wwi</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T09:34:31+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI工具, 旋律, 扩展, 完整歌曲
<br>
<br>
总结: 这位用户正在寻找一种AI工具，可以将一个旋律扩展成一首完整的歌曲。用户对于这种工具是否存在以及如何寻找它毫无头绪，希望能得到一些建议。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hey, I'm looking for an AI tool that takes a melody and expands it into a full song. I have no idea if this exists or not, or even how to look for it, woudl really appreciate some advice! </p> <p>&#x200b;</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/-99-83--9-9"> /u/-99-83--9-9 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0wwi/expand_melody_into_song_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0wwi/expand_melody_into_song_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fz32z</id>
            <title>Generative art</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz32z/generative_art/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fz32z</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T07:14:34+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: AI programs, generate, images, Instagram
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人想知道是否有AI程序可以生成这种类型的图片，提供了两个Instagram链接。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi does anyone know is there any AI programs that can generate these kind of images?</p> <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/visualizevalue/">https://www.instagram.com/visualizevalue/</a> </p> <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/visuallywise/">https://www.instagram.com/visuallywise/</a> </p> <p>&#x200b;</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/mrpp_2"> /u/mrpp_2 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz32z/generative_art/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fz32z/generative_art/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g43rd</id>
            <title>Exploring Llama 2: Open-Source LLM Advancements &amp; Applications</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g43rd/exploring_llama_2_opensource_llm_advancements/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g43rd</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T12:54:59+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Llama 2, open-source, large language model, Meta and Microsoft
<br>
<br>
总结: Llama 2是由Meta和Microsoft开发的开源大型语言模型（LLM）。Llama 2代表Meta AI的大型语言模型。如果你想了解大型语言模型，你可以访问另一个名为“什么是LLM？通过示例理解”的博客。Llama 2基于Transformer架构，这是其他流行的LLM（如GPT-3）所使用的相同架构。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Introduction to Llama 2<br /> Llama 2 is an open-source large language model (LLM) developed by Meta and Microsoft. Llama 2 stands for large language model by Meta AI. If you want to understand a large language model, you can visit another blog called What is LLM? Understanding with Examples. Llama 2 is based on the Transformer architecture, which is the same architecture used by other popular LLMs such as GPT-3.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/krunal_bhimani_"> /u/krunal_bhimani_ </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g43rd/exploring_llama_2_opensource_llm_advancements/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g43rd/exploring_llama_2_opensource_llm_advancements/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fzrlh</id>
            <title>Build Market Intelligence App with Reddit, Graphlit and Azure AI</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fzrlh/build_market_intelligence_app_with_reddit/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fzrlh</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T08:06:40+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: market intelligence, Reddit, AI, Graphlit
<br>
<br>
总结: 本文介绍了如何利用人工智能加速从Reddit中提取市场情报的过程，并展示了使用Graphlit平台从该社区中提取的结构化分析数据，包括人物、组织和话题。通过创建Reddit feed和内容工作流程，将Reddit帖子导入Graphlit，并通过Azure AI分析Reddit帖子中的实体，通过分面查询提取结构化数据进行图表和分析。这篇文章展示了如何利用AI轻松收集和组织Reddit等非结构化数据。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I've been exploring how market intelligence from Reddit can be automated - accelerating the time to business insights - with the use of AI.</p> <p>I've <a href="https://www.graphlit.com/blog/market-intelligence-reddit">written up a tutorial</a> for our platform, Graphlit, showing some structured analytics data we were able to extract from this subreddit - including people, organizations and topics.</p> <p>Thought this may be interesting to folks to see some of the trending data, and how AI can be used to easily gather and organize unstructured data like Reddit.</p> <p>The tutorial walks through ingesting Reddit posts into Graphlit by creating a Reddit feed, along with a content workflow. The workflow describes how the content will be ingested, prepared, extracted and enriched into our knowledge graph.</p> <p>When all content has been ingested, you can analyze the observed entities that Azure AI found in the Reddit posts, and extract structured data via faceted queries for charting and analysis.</p> <p>(Disclaimer: I'm the Founder of Graphlit)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/DeadPukka"> /u/DeadPukka </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fzrlh/build_market_intelligence_app_with_reddit/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fzrlh/build_market_intelligence_app_with_reddit/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g2a3w</id>
            <title>What is the best AI voice generator for Hindi / Indian languages?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g2a3w/what_is_the_best_ai_voice_generator_for_hindi/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g2a3w</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T11:10:47+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: non-profit tech company, early childhood education, rural and low income areas, content creation
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讲述了一个非营利科技公司与政府合作，致力于推动印度农村和低收入地区的幼儿教育（6岁及以下）。文章提到他们已经有一个产品，并且通常由内部团队负责内容创作。目前，作者正在为不同年龄段的新垂直领域进行设置，并需要对内容进行原型设计，特别是包含配音的各种视频。作者尝试使用veed.io进行实验，并认为如果能够使用人工智能生成音频，工作速度将提高10倍。作者还提到希望能够找到最适合创建印地语人工智能配音的软件（最好是免费的，因为预算有限）。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hello, so I work at a non-profit tech company that works with the government to catalyse early childhood education (ages 6 and below) to rural and low income areas across India. We have a product set out and content is typically created by an in-house team.</p> <p>Currently I am working on setting up a new vertical for a different age group, which also requires prototyping our content — especially various videos that have a voiceover in them.</p> <p>I was playing around with veed.io and I clearly see the work being 10x faster if we can generate audio with AI instead of having someone record it.</p> <p>One thing I couldn’t figure out is if it’s possible to make the voice more ‘energetic’? </p> <p>Would really appreciate any suggestions on what software works best to create Hindi AI voiceovers (preferably free since we’re on a budget for this).</p> <p>Thank you 🙏</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Did_It_To_Em_Again"> /u/Did_It_To_Em_Again </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g2a3w/what_is_the_best_ai_voice_generator_for_hindi/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g2a3w/what_is_the_best_ai_voice_generator_for_hindi/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ftvb6</id>
            <title>Design Help</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftvb6/design_help/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ftvb6</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T02:00:34+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: brand guidelines, train future images, artificial intelligence, design help
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了如何利用品牌指南来训练未来的图像，并提到了人工智能和设计帮助的问题。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hey there, </p> <p>Is there a way to create brand guidelines and use those to train future images? </p> <p>Thanks</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Pakhzar"> /u/Pakhzar </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftvb6/design_help/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftvb6/design_help/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g0h7x</id>
            <title>Maybe Ai ? Translator for patients.</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0h7x/maybe_ai_translator_for_patients/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17g0h7x</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T09:01:19+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: translator, patients, speech, stroke
<br>
<br>
总结: 这篇文章讨论了一个关于为中风患者设计的翻译器的问题。作者想使用现有的人工智能工具来翻译受损的语言能力。作者询问是否有相关的工具，并且如果没有，如何开发自己的人工智能软件来解决这种问题。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi, im currently working on a Design of a translator for patients strugling with speeh after a stroke. I was thinking about using existing Ai tool for translating disturbed speech. Are there any tools for that ? And if not how can I develop my own Ai software and teach it how to read and translate this type of problem. Thanks!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/kndrmlo"> /u/kndrmlo </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0h7x/maybe_ai_translator_for_patients/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17g0h7x/maybe_ai_translator_for_patients/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17folbw</id>
            <title>Nightshade Antidote - Detect Poison in Your AI Model</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17folbw/nightshade_antidote_detect_poison_in_your_ai_model/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17folbw</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-24T21:55:25+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Defensive Mode, AI, weaponize, Escalation theory
<br>
<br>
总结: AI中没有防御模式，AI无法理解防御。如果将其武器化，那只会走向一种结果，即升级理论。如果你决定毒害一个AI模型，对此的自然对策就是毒害你的AI模型。Nightshade是一个GAN，它被设计为GAN中的生成器。我能想到的最简单的对抗方法就是直接毒害你的GAN，释放一个毒害Nightshade的模型。这将是最自然的对抗方式。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>There is no Defensive Mode in AI. Defense is a feature that AI does not understand. If you weaponize it, then that only goes one way. Escalation theory. If you decide to poison an AI model, the natural counter to that is to poison your AI model back. Nightshade is a GAN. It is designed to be the Generator within the GAN. The easiest method I could possibly come up with to counter this method would be to flat out poison your GAN. To release a model that poisons Nightshade. That would be the most natural counter to it.</p> <p>The reason why this code is so long, and complex, is because I very actively chose to avoid that method. All this code does is detect the adversary. It is a defensive tool as written, rather than an offensive one. It would have been 10x easier to create code that poisons any model that tries to poison another model. Where would that get AI in the end? An eye for an eye is a crappy methodology for humans to follow, why are we so quick to introduce it to AI models? </p> <p>Do I endorse AI companies scraping web data for profit? No. The opposite. Sue the pants off of any company who has engaged in such practices, that is my stance on that. I hope they lose the court battles. Don't introduce poison to the AI models though because the companies that created them scraped data. That is counter intuitive on too many levels for me to support. That is why Nightshade Antidote exists. That is why an antidote will be quickly invented and released for anyone else who tries similar tactics.</p> <p><a href="https://turingssolutions.com/f/nightshade-antidote---detect-poison-in-your-ai-model">https://turingssolutions.com/f/nightshade-antidote---detect-poison-in-your-ai-model</a> </p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Fantastic-Ninja3839"> /u/Fantastic-Ninja3839 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17folbw/nightshade_antidote_detect_poison_in_your_ai_model/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17folbw/nightshade_antidote_detect_poison_in_your_ai_model/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fpveq</id>
            <title>What is/are your favorite book(s) regarding Ai leaning? And What books would you suggest to new learners who are not data scientists? If you had to choose a resource for those who are technically inclined and want to learn about ai what would that resource be?</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fpveq/what_isare_your_favorite_books_regarding_ai/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fpveq</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-24T22:49:48+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: books, ai learning, little to no knowledge, home Ai projects
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人想学习人工智能，但对此一无所知，希望能找到一些关于人工智能学习的书籍，以便能够创建自己的家庭人工智能项目。他们想知道别人正在读什么书，使用什么资源。他们希望列出关于人工智能的阅读材料，并提供给新学习者一些建议。同时，他们也想知道别人学习人工智能的喜爱书籍和资源。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>The title says it all folks.</p> <p>I am curious as to what books people are reading about ai, specifically books regarding ai learning for those who have little to no knowledge of Ai and possibly want to learn enough to create their one home Ai projects.</p> <p>What are you currently reading? What resources do you use?</p> <p>Please list what you are reading regarding ai and any suggestions for books that could help new learners. Also feel free to list your favorite books and resources for learning about ai.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/biPolar_Lion"> /u/biPolar_Lion </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fpveq/what_isare_your_favorite_books_regarding_ai/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fpveq/what_isare_your_favorite_books_regarding_ai/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ftqya</id>
            <title>AI TOOL HELP</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftqya/ai_tool_help/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17ftqya</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-25T01:54:24+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: software, video, clips, sync
<br>
<br>
总结: 有人想知道如何使用软件制作类似视频的方法，不是特定的创意，而是如何找到视频片段并将它们同步到视频中。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a href="https://youtu.be/Z2vRayNRZu8?si=zCCOHWoeLVNQ4TCn">https://youtu.be/Z2vRayNRZu8?si=zCCOHWoeLVNQ4TCn</a></p> <p>Does anyone know the software I can use to make video like this? Not these particular ideas but specifically how to find the clips from videos to use and sync them into a video like this.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/reallyred11"> /u/reallyred11 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftqya/ai_tool_help/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17ftqya/ai_tool_help/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fas1a</id>
            <title>Use ChatGPT on every website with Jovi [New Extension]</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fas1a/use_chatgpt_on_every_website_with_jovi_new/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fas1a</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-24T11:42:28+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Jovi, ChatGPT, AI assistant, tool
<br>
<br>
总结: Jovi是一个新的工具，可以在任何网站上使用ChatGPT，并充当智能AI助手。它可以用于写作、总结、编码和翻译，还可以保存和组织提示信息。它支持100多种语言，并具有简约易用的用户界面。可以免费尝试，只需安装即可。按下Alt + E或Command + E即可打开。它还包括一个独立版本，可以在新标签页中打开。请随意试用！ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I created a new tool called Jovi which lets you use ChatGPT on every website and acts as your smart AI assistant: <a href="https://tryjovi.com">https://tryjovi.com</a></p> <p>You can use it to write, summarize, code &amp; translate as well as saving and organizing your prompts. By default it supports over 100+ languages and features a very minimalistic and easy-to-use UI.</p> <p>You can try it without sign-up for free, just need to install it. To open it you can press Alt + E or Command + E on a Mac. It also includes a standalone version which opens in a new tab.</p> <p>Please feel free to give it a try!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HeronAI_com"> /u/HeronAI_com </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fas1a/use_chatgpt_on_every_website_with_jovi_new/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fas1a/use_chatgpt_on_every_website_with_jovi_new/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fgcg3</id>
            <title>University of Chicago Researchers Develop Tool to Dismantle AI Models</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fgcg3/university_of_chicago_researchers_develop_tool_to/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fgcg3</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-24T16:05:53+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Nightshade, AI art generators, hallucinations, intellectual property
<br>
<br>
总结: Nightshade是一种新的工具，通过在像素级别上破坏图像，使其对AI艺术生成器产生干扰，从而使艺术家能够保护自己的知识产权。然而，这种方法也引发了关于阻碍AI发展和道德伦理的争议。尽管Nightshade赋予了艺术家保护作品的能力，但它也引发了对有意破坏AI进展的道德问题。解决这一问题的方法可能在于建立软件工程师和艺术家之间的合作环境，并通过对话和透明度来建立信任。此外，法律框架需要与技术进步同步，以明确权利和责任的界定。 </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>In the ceaseless march towards artificial intelligence (AI) sophistication, a new tool named Nightshade has emerged from the shadows, casting a pall over the unbridled exploitation of artists’ work by tech conglomerates. Developed by a group of researchers led by Ben Zhao, a computer science professor at the University of Chicago, Nightshade meticulously corrupts images at the pixel level, rendering them toxic to AI art generators like Stability AI’s Stable Diffusion XL (SDXL). When trained on these poisoned images, AI models begin to hallucinate, misinterpreting inputs and generating bizarre outputs. This novel method gives artists a semblance of control, a way to retaliate against tech behemoths that unscrupulously harvest their creative outputs to train AI models.</p> <p>The ethical landscape this innovation traverses is as intricate as the code that underpins it. On one hand, the tool is a powerful testament to artists’ right to protect their intellectual property. However, it also symbolizes a potential roadblock in the path of AI advancement. By inducing hallucinations, Nightshade could be perceived as an act of sabotage, a deliberate attempt to stunt the growth of a technology that holds immense potential. The discord between artists and tech firms exemplifies a larger debate surrounding the ethics of AI development, particularly when it involves the use of individuals' creative work without explicit consent.</p> <p>The moral dichotomy is apparent. While Nightshade empowers artists to safeguard their creations, it also raises questions about the ethics of deliberately hampering AI progression. The underpinning rationale of Nightshade's creation is defensive, yet its offensive capabilities cannot be ignored. It’s a manifestation of the struggle between individual rights and collective technological advancement. </p> <p>Moreover, the tactic of poisoning AI models can potentially morph into a broader tool of dissent, setting a precarious precedent. What if similar tools are developed with malicious intent, leading to a future where AI can be easily poisoned and misled? The implications extend beyond the realm of art into a world where AI is intertwined with critical infrastructures.</p> <p>The solution to this impasse might lie in fostering a collaborative environment between software engineers and artists. Tech companies should not view artists as mere data points, but as stakeholders in the AI ecosystem. Initiating dialogues to understand artists’ concerns, obtaining explicit permissions, and sharing benefits could be steps towards building a harmonious relationship. Moreover, transparency in AI training data usage, and establishing clear guidelines on data sourcing can also bridge the existing trust deficit.</p> <p>Additionally, legal frameworks need to keep pace with technological advancements to provide a clear demarcation of rights and responsibilities. The current legal skirmishes between artists and tech companies underscore the urgency for robust legal frameworks that safeguard individual rights while promoting innovation.</p> <p>In conclusion, the emergence of tools like Nightshade accentuates the urgent need for a balanced approach that honors individual rights and paves the way for responsible AI development. The road ahead should be paved with collaboration, transparency, and a shared vision that elevates both art and technology.</p> <p>Thank you for reading</p> <p>Link to article: <a href="https://gizmodo.com/nightshade-poisons-ai-art-generators-dall-e-1850951218">https://gizmodo.com/nightshade-poisons-ai-art-generators-dall-e-1850951218</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Dwill354"> /u/Dwill354 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fgcg3/university_of_chicago_researchers_develop_tool_to/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fgcg3/university_of_chicago_researchers_develop_tool_to/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fmpz4</id>
            <title>Embedded systems and artificial intelligence</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fmpz4/embedded_systems_and_artificial_intelligence/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/t3_17fmpz4</guid>
            <pubDate></pubDate>
            <updated>2023-10-24T20:38:49+00:00</updated>
                
                
            <content:encoded>
                <![CDATA[
                    
                        <div> 关键词: Beginner question, computer science, C language, embedded systems programming
<br>
<br>
总结: 这是一个初学者的问题，他最近开始学习计算机科学，并对C语言的学习非常感兴趣，甚至暂时停止了他正在学习的MOOC课程（CS50x）来阅读一本关于C语言的书。他发现C语言是嵌入式系统编程中最常用的语言之一，并且最近成为他的灵感来源。他希望有一天能够从事机器人和汽车软件的工作。他对人工智能技术非常感兴趣，但有人告诉他，他感兴趣的两个领域相当不同，没有太多共同之处，也没有需要同时掌握两者的工作。他想听听有经验的人的意见，对任何反馈都表示感谢！他还有一个更具体的问题，关于他在深入学习C语言方面所花费的时间。他花了很多时间在学习上，并且非常享受。但是如果嵌入式系统和人工智能/机器学习/深度学习之间的距离如此之大，他可能会决定减少对C语言的学习。C语言在人工智能相关领域中有应用吗？ </div>
                        <hr>
                    
                    <!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Beginner question. I recently begun studying computer science and I enjoyed so much studying C language that I momentarily stopped the MOOC I was following (CS50x) to read a book about C. Just love it. Studying more about the language I discovered that it's one of the most employed ones for embedded systems programming and that happen to have very recently become a great inspiration. I'd like to work on robots and cars software one day. My doubt and the point of this Reddit is that I begin studying CS because my dream is to understand and work on artificial intelligence technologies. But I got told that the two things I'm interested in are quite different and don't have much in common/there are no jobs that require both. I just wanted to hear some opinion from experienced people, any feedback is appreciated!</p> <p>Edit: a more specific question is on the time I'm dedicating to studying C in depth. I'm spending a lot of time on it and I'm really enjoying it. But if the distance between embedded systems and artificial intelligence/machine learning/deep learning is so wide I may decide to give it less effort. Is C employed in anything artificial intelligence related?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Fit-Presentation2348"> /u/Fit-Presentation2348 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fmpz4/embedded_systems_and_artificial_intelligence/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtificialInteligence/comments/17fmpz4/embedded_systems_and_artificial_intelligence/">[comments]</a></span>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>